Over the hills and far away...
...Teletubbies come to play.
One.
- Two.
- Two!
- Three.
- Three!
Four!
And the Teletubbies
love each other very much.
Aw.
Big hug.
It's not allowed.
Why did you take so long?
They're not coming by.
Doesn't matter,
it doesn't matter!
Where are the others?
They were right behind me.
Time for Teletubbies.
Let's take
all the kids in one car.
Time for Teletubbies.
Sit here. Sit!
Auntie, what's going on?
Jimmy, sit still, keep quiet,
and do not move
from this spot.
We have got to get
the kids into the car!
What were you doing?
- I told you to hurry up!
- For God's sake!
Uh-oh!
Jimmy?
What is that?
Where have
the Teletubbies gone?
Dad?
- ♪ Tinky Winky ♪
♪ Dipsy ♪
Jimmy, run.
- Mum?
- Run! Run!
Run!
Run! Jimmy, run!
Go!
Dad! Dad!
Dad!
Jimmy.
Dad.
Dad, what's happening?
Nothing that hasn't been
most perfectly foretold.
I'm so scared, Dad.
I think Mum and sis
might be dead.
Oh, no, son.
Not dead.
Saved.
For this is a glorious day.
The day of judgment.
Here, my son.
Keep this with you always.
Have faith.
Yes.
Yes, my children!
Yes!
Father,
why have you forsaken me?
It's your big day, Spike.
Up you get.
See ya later.
Got your torch?
Jumper, whistle...
water bottle?
Here y'are.
Got your knife?
Good lad.
Put that away.
We're having bacon?
For breakfast?
Dave and Rosey
brought it round last night.
Where's yours?
Had some already,
while I was cooking.
Yeah, right.
Spikey.
It's all yours.
I'll go see to your mum.
You finish up.
Put your plate on the side.
I'm coming, love.
Here y'are, love.
What's the matter, what's up?
Jamie...
You've got
to ride it out, love.
- You gotta stay here and rest.
- Oh, I can't. No.
Oh, Spikey.
Hiya, Mum.
Oh, me baby.
You know,
I didn't mean to make a fuss.
- It's me head. It's...
- It's okay.
It's just pounding.
Oh, why don't you tell me
how school was today?
I haven't been to school, Mum.
It's the morning.
Is it?
Uh, yeah,
it's the morning, and, uh...
Isla...
d'you remember?
Spike's not going
to school today.
Why not?
Is it the weekend already?
Nah, it's Friday.
So why isn't
he going to school?
We spoke about this.
Few times.
Spoke about what, Jamie?
Me and Spike
are going out.
It's his first time.
First time?
Do you mean
you're going off the island,
to the mainland?
- Yeah.
- What?
Isla.
What the fuck
are you talking about?
All right.
Don't swear. Come on.
Have you gone
fucking crazy?
He's a fucking baby!
- Mum...
- He's twelve.
Are you trying to kill
our fucking baby, you cunt?
Spike, will you go back
downstairs, please?
You crazy fucking
sick baby-murderer.
No, Dad, you go down.
- If me dad was still here...
- No, I'm telling you.
...he'd skin you alive,
baby-murderer!
It'll be better if...
All right!
- Cunt!
- All right. Isla,
- it's all right.
- Cunt!
- All right. He'll be fine.
- Mum...
- No.
It's me.
Spike... Spikey.
Oh, what's going on? I'm hot.
Why... Why am I
feeling so hot?
It's just the weather, Mum.
So hot.
It's all right.
I got you some breakfast.
It's a bit of bacon.
Eat a bit
when you feel like it.
Are you off?
- Yeah.
- Where?
- School.
- Oh.
Okay, Spikey.
Oh, I love you.
I love you, too, Mum.
Morning, kiddo.
Sam.
Just restrung this for you.
Did it need a restring?
Nope. Did it
for my own sake, really.
He'll be fine, Sam.
Have a draw, son.
Feel the weight.
Hold it.
No shake at all.
Strong lad.
Howay then, son. Let's go.
All right.
I'll see you tonight.
- Lives are at stake.
- Cheers, lads.
- Go on, Jamie!
- Good luck, Spike.
Glad you're getting on now,
Spike.
Go on, Spike!
You go well, lad.
This is from Mum.
- Thanks, Betty.
- Your big party tonight,
our Spike. Don't be late!
Bring him back safe, yeah?
Come on, Jamie!
Look after him, Jamie!
Good luck, Spike.
All right, Jacob.
Look at that, Spike.
You got the whole
leadership committee.
You just smile and be polite.
Had to see you off.
We're all excited for you.
Even though you know
I feel he's a bit young.
Fourteen or fifteen is more
in keeping with practice.
He's ready, Jenny.
Go on, lad.
You know the rules
of our community, Spike.
If you leave,
you can come back.
But if you don't come back,
no one is permitted
to go and find you.
There are no rescues.
No exceptions.
It was something
we learned the hard way...
On account of all the people
we lost in the past.
So once you walk
onto that mainland,
you're on your own.
You understand?
Yes, Jenny.
You seen anything
this morning, Ant?
Nothing.
Fully quiet.
All clear?
All clear.
Open up for them.
Good lad.
Mind how you go,
lads. Don't miss the tide.
Seven, six, eleven, five,
nine-and-twenty mile today
Four, eleven, seventeen,
thirty-two the day before
Boots, boots, boots, boots,
moving up and down again!
There's no discharge
in the war!
So, what's this, Spike?
It's the causeway.
Talk us through it.
It's the only way
to the mainland.
But we can only get here
in low tide.
In high tide,
the sea covers it.
Can we swim it
in high tide?
No.
The sea has a current.
It'll push us past the island
and pull us out to sea,
and we'll drown.
Don't, don't, don't,
don't look
at what's in front of you...
Boots, boots, boots, boots,
moving up and down again
Men, men, men, men,
men go mad with watchin' em...
We'll have four hours
before high tide.
Are we doing this?
Can't go back now, Dad.
Why?
Everyone'll think I'm soft.
Aye, they will.
Can't have that, can we?
Come on, then.
Count, count, count,
count the bullets
in the bandoliers.
If your eyes drop,
they will get atop of you!
Boots, boots, boots, boots,
moving up and down again
There's no discharge
in the war!
This is where
we get all the fuel.
You'll be working here
one day.
Ain't so bad by day
because o' company,
But night brings long
strings
o' forty thousand million
Boots, boots, boots, boots,
moving up and down again.
It's so big.
If we kept walking,
would we get to a place
where you can't see the sea?
Wey aye.
You'll walk for days or weeks
without seeing the coast.
There's nothing out there,
Spikey.
Nowhere to aim for.
There's other villages.
Aye, but none have
anything we don't have.
And we stay out
the towns and villages.
I have marched
- six weeks...
- Howay.
...in hell an' certify
It is not fire,
devils, dark, or anything,
but boots, boots,
boots, boots,
moving up an' down again.
Try, try, try...
...try to think
of something different
Oh, my God,
keep me from going lunatic!
Boots, boots, boots, boots,
moving up and down again!
There's no discharge
in the war!
There, look, look, look,
look, look, look.
Slow-low.
Not fast.
Doesn't mean
they aren't dangerous.
And if there's one visible,
probably a couple more
in the trees.
Your bow
isn't strong enough
for the chest.
You need to hit it
right in the neck.
Okay, Dad.
You scared?
Only a little bit.
Are you?
No. I'm good.
You like this range?
I think so.
Let's go get your first kill.
Get him in your sight.
Calculate for wind.
All right.
He's yours.
Anything that comes out
after him is mine.
Send when ready.
Send it.
Dad!
Get in here!
Hey!
Beautiful kill, Spike.
You feel good?
Yeah, I think so.
Aye, you should.
I'm proud of ya.
Now come on, we gotta move.
The screaming
would have alerted
the other infected
in the area.
Go on. Let's keep going.
They're amazing.
They're beautiful.
Here.
Check this out.
Good lad.
Shit.
It's always worth looking
around for summat useful.
People would have searched
this place a hundred times,
but you never know.
Fuckin' hell.
Oh.
Are these useful?
Nah. Got plenty of that.
But this is.
What is it?
A frisbee.
You never seen
a frisbee before?
Aw, it's great.
You're gonna love it.
Come here, son.
Don't look away, Spike.
- Dad, please.
- Spike!
Do as I tell ya.
There's a lesson for you here.
What happened to him?
Looks like he got tied up
and left for the infected.
And now he's infected.
He's infected?
Aye.
Why would anyone do that?
Maybe a punishment.
Maybe a warning.
There are strange people
on the mainland.
Roaming.
That's why our home
is so precious.
Is that the lesson?
No.
Kill it.
The more you kill,
the easier it gets.
Don't feel bad about it.
The infection
takes away their minds.
It's got no mind,
it's got no soul.
Spike.
Kill the bloody thing.
Kill it!
What are you waiting for,
Spike?
Now, son!
Spike, finish it!
For Christ's sake, Spike,
fuckin' kill it!
Good lad.
♪ Abide with me ♪
♪ Fast falls the eventide ♪
♪ The darkness deepens ♪
♪ Lord, with me abide ♪
♪ Where is death's sting?♪
- Head. Heart.
- ♪ Where, grave ♪
- ♪ Thy victory? ♪
- Draw...
♪ I triumph still ♪
Release.
♪ If Thou abide...♪
There's another kill
here if we're lucky.
Come on.
Oh.
This wasn't slow-lows.
This were
the fast ones, Spikey.
You smell that?
It's the intestines.
I weirdly like it.
Dad.
What?
An Alpha did that.
This way, Spike. Come on.
Spike! Move it!
We're going back?
Aye. Got your kills,
that's what we came for.
Won't it look like
we left early?
Don't talk, Spikey.
Just keep your eyes peeled.
Looks clear.
Let's go.
Stay really still.
Alpha.
Fuck.
Get back to the trees.
Get back, let's go.
Dad!
Let's go!
Move, move.
Keep moving.
Let's go, let's go!
Here, defense.
Get your breath back.
I'll take the first,
- you take the second.
- Yeah.
Slow your breathing.
Slow it down.
Shit!
Go! Move, move, move!
Just go!
Fuck!
Right, two-man drill. Defense!
Right. Shoot!
Head and heart.
Head and heart, Spike.
Get in there.
Go up!
- Go on, son!
- Come on, Dad!
Where?
Shit.
Da, what...?
The loft!
Check the loft!
Oi. Come here.
Go on.
I can't get back up.
- Oh, fuck.
- Dad! Dad!
Push!
Oh, fuck.
Fuckin' hell.
Mind your backs, boys.
Coming through!
Tea time.
Tea time. Well done today.
Great stuff.
Chop chop before it gets dark.
It's waitin'.
Alphas aren't like the others.
Not just bigger. Smarter.
What are we gonna do?
Well, we're not fighting it.
I've got no arrows left.
And anyway...
I've seen it take a dozen hits
to drop one of those things.
So, we'll wait, too.
I'm really sorry, Dad.
What? What about?
This is all my fault.
- I couldn't hit anything.
- What are you talking about?
I tried but I was too scared.
And I kept missing.
What are you talking about?
This is not your fault.
And you kept shooting.
I've seen adults who canna get
an arrow in the bow,
they're shaking so hard.
Not you. Hey, hey, hey...
Spike, you did well.
Honestly.
We're gonna miss
the low tide.
Yeah. Yeah.
Aren't we?
There'll be another.
Hey, look out to sea.
Here.
Just there.
Quarantine patrol.
Probably French.
Dad...
What's that?
Fire.
Something's burning?
Yeah.
Something.
Is it another village?
Nope.
What is it then?
I don't know.
I've never been there.
Does it always burn?
I just said
I've never been there, Spike.
Spike.
There she is.
Spike, I'm drowning.
Get out! We gotta get out!
Oh, fucking hell.
Get up! Get up, Spike!
- Get your bum down.
- Wake up, we've gotta move!
It's all right, son.
It's all right.
Aah! Fuckin' hell!
What happened?
Old building.
I dunno.
Chimney fuckin' died on us.
The noise will bring 'em.
We gotta move.
Is it low tide?
It'll be low enough.
We move fast but quiet.
If you see the Alpha,
just run straight
for the causeway
and over it. All right?
You stop for nothing! Go on!
- Where will you be?
- Right behind you.
No sign of the Alpha.
It's still high tide.
Only just.
The water will be shallow.
But we can make it.
Shin-deep.
We're good. All right.
Take your boots off.
Aye. Line up the gates.
That's our path.
It's okay. Just breathe.
Here. Let's go.
You go first.
Go on, son.
How about that day, Spike, eh?
First time to the mainland.
First kill. First run-in
with the infected.
Saw an Alpha!
And missed the tide.
I've got so much
to tell Mum when we get back.
Dad.
Run, Spike!
Run!
Go! Go, keep going!
Keep moving!
- Oh! Oh, God! Get up!
- Dad, I can't!
- I can't!
- Spike! Get up, now!
Spike, go! Go, go, Spike!
Fucking go!
I can't!
Yes, you can!
Oh, shit!
Incoming!
Open up!
Help! Jenny! Jenny!
Wakey, wakey!
Up, up, up!
Incoming!
- Wakey, wakey, boys.
- Ant, who is it?
- Everyone up! Eyes on!
- Form up, boys! Get ready!
Eyes on, eyes on!
Incoming!
Alpha!
Open up! Fucking open up!
Alpha! Alpha!
Fuckin' Alpha,
get that light on!
Keep the fuckin' light on him!
Fire!
Get down!
Go, go, go, go, Spike!
Go, go.
Keep
that fuckin' light on him.
Load it, load it, load it!
Oh, fuck.
This is it, Spike.
Breathe!
Shit! Oh!
♪ Oh me lads,
you should've seen us gannin'♪
♪ Passing the folks
along the road ♪
Open up!
♪ Just as they were stannin'
All the lads and lasses ♪
♪ There all
wi' smilin' faces ♪
Jenny! Open the fucking gate!
- ♪ Gannin' along ♪
- Wait.
♪ The Scotswood Road ♪
No, fucking open up!
Fuck's sake!
- Wait.
- No.
- Fuckin' hell, Jenny!
- Please, please.
- We're fuckin' good.
- Wait.
Look at me fuckin' eyes,
- we're clean.
- Wait.
Look at him.
- Look at his eyes!
- Jenny.
- He's clean! We're clean!
- Jenny, please.
All right, open up,
let them in.
Go. Go.
♪ To see the Blaydon Races ♪
Spike! Spike! Spike!
Hey!
There were 25, 'bout 30 yards.
Tall grass. Wind.
And where does that arrow go?
Right through
his fuckin' neck!
That fat bastard, he stands up
and lets out one
of them girly screams...
and then drops
like a sack of fuckin' shite.
Next thing, we've got
eight fuckin' infected...
Dad, swearing.
...running right at us!
I'm thinking,
"Oh, shit, here we go."
Benny Big Bollocks here
is just fuckin' taking shots.
♪ She stood there laughing ♪
- No, I kept missing 'em.
- Nah, you didn't.
He's humble.
Our humble Spike.
♪ I felt the knife
in my hand ♪
♪ And she laughed no more ♪
The fuckin' giant killer!
♪ My, my, my Delilah ♪
♪ Why, why, why, Delilah?♪
Go on. Go on, go.
♪ So before they come ♪
♪ To break down the door ♪
♪ Forgive me, Delilah
I just couldn't take any more ♪
♪ Forgive me, Delilah ♪
♪ I just couldn't take
any more ♪
I gotta go.
In here.
Go on, Rosey.
What... What are you...
What are you taking us here for?
Oop.
Oh, Rosey.
Oh, fuck.
Oh.
Spike.
I didn't expect to see you
until past midnight.
Just came to see me mum.
How was she? She all right?
She's better than all right.
We were up and about.
We walked to the fields.
She's got a lotta life in her
when she's not having a turn.
But what about your day? Eh?
More to the point.
Dad's made it out
to be something it's not.
Like what?
Like I'm a hero.
I expect you are, to him.
Just feels like he's lying.
So what did happen out there?
- I shot one of the fat ones.
- Ah.
It was hardly moving.
But then we got chased
by some of the fast ones,
and I couldn't hit a thing.
Then we just hid
until it got dark.
I was just scared.
Felt sick.
I wanted to be home
with me mum.
Your dad
probably felt the same.
Tell you what, though,
never seen so much land.
- Mm.
- It was so big.
What did you see?
Well, hills...
Forests...
And a fire.
A fire?
I wonder if you saw
old Kelson.
Didn't imagine
he was still alive.
Was it southwest?
Christ. That'll be Kelson.
Believe it or not,
he used to be my GP
some 30 year back.
- What's a GP?
- A doctor.
- A doctor?
- Aye.
Had his practice
just outside Whitley Bay.
Dad said that he didn't know
what the fire was.
And he says
all the real doctors are dead.
That's why no one knows
what's wrong with Mum.
Just feels like
he's lying about everything.
Nah. You know what?
He probably
didn't wanna spook you.
Dr. Kelson is...
odd.
How is he odd?
What's so special
about the fire?
If your dad
doesn't wanna talk about it,
I don't think I should.
Why don't you go back
to your party? Eh?
I'm fine here wi' your mum.
No.
You go.
I'll look after her now.
Okay.
Got ya.
They're all lying, Mum.
Spike, will you go
to the shops for us?
I need some Nurofen.
Nurofen?
It's me head. It's just...
Never mind. It doesn't matter.
Hello!
We're up here, love.
Well, that was some party.
Absolute carnage.
You look...
You look like you've been
dragged through
a hedge backwards.
Maybe I did.
I woke up in a wheat field.
And where did you
disappear to, Spikey?
Looked around and the guest
of honor had vanished.
Just came home.
Hey, giant-killer.
I'll make some breakfast.
What's going on, Spike?
Why didn't you tell us
there was a doctor
that could see Mum?
Doctor?
We don't have a doctor.
Haven't had a doctor here
in forever.
Dr. Kelson, Dad.
The fire. On the mainland.
Who've you been talking to?
So he is a doctor.
Was it Sam?
Bloody fool.
Putting ideas in your head.
He's not a doctor, Spike.
Maybe he once was. Years ago.
But he's long
since gone insane.
What do you mean?
Is he a doctor or not?
Before you were born,
we used to forage.
But it got harder, you know,
so you'd have
to travel further.
And one day, it took a group
of us close to Kelson's.
Right?
Aye. 500 yards out,
we started to smell death.
Now understand, we were
well used to that smell.
Back then,
the dead were everywhere.
But this...
this was totally different.
This stench was like...
it was like a wall.
You could touch it.
And we got
to the brow of this hill,
and we looked down...
I've never seen
anything like it.
Corpses.
Hundreds.
Just arranged in lines.
Men, women, children.
And in the middle,
was this fire.
Stood by it, was Kelson.
For some unfathomable purpose,
he'd dragged
all the bodies there.
And a few seconds later,
he turned around
and he looked right at us
and he waved.
Casually, like,
"Hey. Wanna come down, lads?"
Yeah. We turned and ran.
And in 15 years,
none of us have been back.
Like I said.
Insane.
Oh, fuck.
Do you want Mum to die?
'Course I don't.
Ah, Spike,
what sort of question is that?
What's really wrong with her?
I don't know.
Is she dying?
I think she's dying.
And so do you.
If she dies,
are you gonna be with Rosey?
Watch your mouth.
What would her Davey
think about that?
I said,
watch your bloody mouth!
Son...
Jamie!
Spike!
Oh, it's pounding, Spike.
Pounding.
I know, Mum. I'm sorry.
Need some water, love?
I'll go get you some.
Get the fuck away from us.
"From us"?
You heard us.
Just go away, Dad.
There's a fire!
There's a... Run!
Fuckin' smoke, look.
Ant, Mark!
- There's a fire!
- Go, go, go on! Go on!
There's fire
in the main barn!
You've got to go!
I can't leave the gate, Spike.
You have to.
That's why they sent me.
I'll be on the siren.
But you've gotta go now.
They need every man,
they said!
- Go!
- For fuck's sake.
Hurry. Go.
Fuckin'...
Keep your eyes on the horizon.
And stay on that siren!
Gonna get more water!
Fetch more water!
Fire!
Get more water. Go!
Come on, Mum. Let's go.
Get water! Water!
Get some more water
from the sea!
Where are we going?
The beach.
And the fields.
- We're going to the beach?
- Yeah.
This is the mainland.
Yeah.
But we can't...
We can't be on the mainland.
It's too dangerous. It's...
- It's okay, Mum.
- No.
- I know how to keep us safe.
- No, no, no, this isn't right.
It's not right. Where's...?
Jamie?
Where's...
Where's Dad?
- Dad's not here.
- Then we...
Then we have to go back now.
Back home.
We have to run, or we...
Mum...
We can't go back. Tide's in.
Oh, God.
Going to see a doctor.
What? A doctor?
- A real doctor.
- No.
From the old days.
Something wrong with you, Mum.
The doctor's
gonna make you better.
Okay?
Okay.
Okay, Mum.
We'll stop here for the night.
We'll stay there.
Is your dad silly?
- Dad?
- Yeah.
Silly with ya. Jokey.
Your granddad was so silly.
You wouldn't believe how much.
Everyone else thought
he was so serious...
but around me, he was daft.
Is your dad like that...
you know, when it's just
the two of you?
No.
Just wanting to make sure
you're tough enough.
Like him.
You know,
when I look in your face...
I see your granddad's eyes.
It's nice.
Exactly.
You should get some sleep.
I'm gonna stay awake.
Keep watch.
Okay, Dad.
What?
What happened?
I don't know.
Here.
Gotta go.
Oh, look.
The Angel.
Do you remember the first time
you showed me the angel, Dad?
We drove near here.
Left the car.
We walked until we spotted it
rising over the treetops.
You said it would stand
like this forever.
Like the pyramids.
Or Stonehenge.
So when you look at it, you...
You're seeing into the future.
Do you remember that day?
I couldn't have been more
than, what, seven or eight?
Us two are real-life
time travelers, you said.
Fallen into the future.
And I got...
I got scared.
Because I thought
you were being serious
and we really had.
How many hundreds of years
have we fallen this time?
Is it thousands or more?
Mum?
Spike.
Your nose is bleeding again.
Keep still.
Don't move.
No, no, no!
Wait! Don't blink!
You're fine.
Shit. Come on, Mum!
Keep going, Mum!
Don't stop!
Run! Run!
Don't stop, Mum! Get in!
Go, Mum, go!
Get inside! Get inside!
Get inside!
Fuck! Fuck!
Go! In! Get in!
Spike, I can't breathe.
Spike, it's gas!
- Can't breathe!
- No, Mum!
- Don't...
Get off her!
Spike...
Spikey!
Get off her!
Get down! Now!
Go on!
What happened?
Benzene.
Vaporized.
Built up over the years.
Oh.
I'm Spike.
And this is me mum.
I'm Erik.
What's wrong with her?
I don't know.
I'm taking her to a doctor.
Right.
What happens now?
What do you mean?
Well, you live here,
don't you?
On this fucking island.
You're a... You're a native.
- A native?
- Hey,
what the fuck happens now?
Do more infected come?
I don't know. Probably.
They would've heard the noise.
Of course, they'll come.
The barsark will come.
They'll rip
our fucking heads off.
Do you understand?
- You're not from here.
- Will you shut her up, please?
Wait, where are you from?
I'm from Sweden,
now can you make her shut up?
- She can't help it.
- She... She can't help it?
You can't help me?
Why the fuck
did I help you, huh?
I could've saved my bullets!
I gotta get outta here.
- I'm gonna leave.
- Well, you can go.
I'm not leaving her.
Thank you, Daddy.
Jesus Christ. Can this get
any more fucked up?
Fuck's sake.
My best friend from school
is a delivery driver.
You don't know what
a delivery driver is.
He, um,
delivers packages.
You know,
people order stuff online.
I bet you don't know
what online is.
Uh, it doesn't matter.
He's a... He's a driver.
And I told him...
you're wasting your life,
Felix.
You only get one life,
and you're pissing it away.
And he said...
"Yeah, what are you gonna do,
fuck nuts?"
So I joined the navy...
to prove a point.
Now who's pissing away
their life, huh?
I don't understand
what you're saying.
I'm saying I should have been
a delivery driver.
Right now, I'd be stuck
in traffic somewhere...
or driving too fast down
a narrow street or something.
Then why are you here?
My fucking boat sank.
We were patrolling
on the east coast of Scotland
and we hit something.
Scotch on the rocks.
Doesn't matter.
Few of us found a life raft.
We didn't wanna make it
to shore, obviously,
but the wind blew us.
Eight of us made it to land.
Now I'm the only one left.
Will you be rescued?
You do know the whole island
is in quarantine, right?
What do you think
the patrol boats are for?
Well, I know
there's a quarantine.
But I thought
it was only for us.
Quarantine is
for any poor fucker
who puts one toe
on this island.
You hit land, you never leave.
You can come to my town.
After I take my mum
to the doctor.
Yeah, where is this doctor?
There.
Not far.
"Not far"?
Hey, hey, you try carrying
your mother around for a bit.
I'm gonna take a break.
First meal
in a day and a half.
Have another.
Seem to really like apples.
Yeah.
One percent.
No signal.
What's that?
Soon, it's a brick.
But for a few
more moments it's...
something like a radio.
But with photos.
Do you have radios?
Do you have photos?
Some people have old ones.
There.
Take a look at that.
That's a new one.
It's my fiancee.
Or ex...
I guess.
What's wrong with her face?
What do you mean?
She looks weird.
You're weird.
She's gorgeous.
What's wrong with you?
Tsk. I know what it is.
There's this girl in my town
who has the same thing.
Thing?
She's allergic to shellfish.
So, if she eats scallops,
then her whole mouth
- gets dead fat and swells up.
- Give me that.
Yeah, there it goes.
Don't hook up with Felix.
Dad...
I'm cold.
Why does she call you "Dad"?
That's weird.
I mean, I'm sure
there's a lot of inbreeding
around these parts...
but this seems unlikely.
She's just confused.
She wasn't always like this.
Most of the time she's just
like she always was.
Who's like she always was?
You, Mum.
Oh.
Who are you?
I'm Erik.
And this is your father,
Spike.
What?
- He's just being silly, Mum.
- He's being a dick.
Mum!
Sorry.
He saved our lives.
I know a dick when I see one.
God, remind me
where we're going, again?
The doctor.
Right. Okay.
Well, let's go.
Mum...
She can walk?
Why do they get so huge?
The barsark.
Well, Sam says,
on some...
the infection kinda works
like steroids.
Yeah?
I mean, I don't know
what steroids are.
I'm guessing that's what
turns them Alpha.
Alpha. You make them
sound like stock brokers.
Or fucking Wall Street guys.
What?
You know what barsark is?
Barsark is better.
It's like...
Crazy fucking
Viking warrior. You know?
I'm actually a Viking.
Maybe if I get infected,
I'll turn into one.
What the fuck was that?
I don't know.
No, no, no. Hey, hey!
Where are you going?
I'm not leaving her.
Hey!
Mum!
- Spike, wait!
- Oh, fuck.
Mum, what are you doing?
Stop!
Don't touch her.
Fucking shit! Holy fuck, shit.
What are you doing?
Fucking drop her.
Cut it, Spike.
Spike, cut it.
Right. Where?
Here.
No fucking way.
- Water.
- Yeah. Here.
What the actual fuck?
Wash your hands.
What the fuck?
You're all insane.
Here. Well done, Spike.
Right.
Put it down.
Put it down!
- It's a baby.
- It's a fucking zombie baby!
Just put it down.
We can't let
these fuckers breed.
We need to kill it!
It's a little girl.
Put it on the fucking ground!
- She doesn't look infected.
- She's not infected.
If you don't put it
on the ground right now...
- Look at her eyes!
- I'll kill you both!
- She's not infected.
- I'll kill all of you!
You got five seconds.
- Five!
- Get up, Mum. Move!
Four!
Three!
No!
Alpha.
Move, Mum!
- Move!
- Yeah. Right.
Shit.
Run, Mum!
Mum! Get off the train!
Mum! Run to the smoke!
Keep running!
Fuck.
Morphine, xylazine.
It's extremely fast-acting.
Excuse my appearance.
I paint myself in iodine.
It's an excellent
prophylactic.
The virus
doesn't like iodine at all.
Oh.
Think I'll take this, Samson.
Let... Let go.
I call this one Samson.
He's lived in the area
a good three years now.
I usually
keep my distance from him,
of course.
Sir...
"Sir."
Oh.
Such good manners. Huh.
Are you Dr. Kelson?
I am.
I'm Spike,
and this is me mum, Isla.
Spike, Isla.
And this is a baby.
We need your help.
Come on, then.
We need to go
before he wakes up.
What's that?
I've been...
I've been waiting almost
13 years for someone
to ask that question.
I often thought
I would die here alone...
of age or starvation
or violence...
never having had the chance
to reply.
Do you know the words
"Memento Mori"?
No.
It's Latin. Ironically,
it's a dead language.
It means "Remember Death."
Remember you must die.
This helps to keep them out.
There were so many dead.
Infected
and non-infected alike.
Because they are alike.
Here, careful.
Every skull
is a set of thoughts.
These sockets saw.
And these jaws
spoke and swallowed.
This is a monument to them.
A temple.
- Sorry, sorry.
- Oh. Don't worry.
No, it's... it's not precious
in that way. It's, uh...
The structure is solid
but the bones
will fall apart due to...
time, or the elements...
or Spike's hand.
The Memento Mori is...
is actualized.
Do you know this man?
His name was Erik.
He saved our lives.
All right,
let's find Erik a home.
Keep going, that's good.
Good lad.
Alas, poor Erik.
Choose a place for him.
Very nice. Well done, Spike.
The baby is a newborn.
It was from an infected.
But she's not infected.
We took her from the mother.
How interesting.
The magic of the placenta.
I'd wondered
if that might happen.
But she'll need milk.
Water will keep her alive
for a few days at most.
Is that why
you came to see me?
The baby?
No.
Take your right forefinger,
put it on your nose...
and from there, try and touch
my forefinger here.
Okay.
Isla, it would be helpful if
I could check your breasts...
and under your arms.
Is that okay?
Is that tender?
Your feelings of confusion...
do they feel like episodes?
Phases?
Or does it feel more constant?
It was waves, but...
I think the tide's coming in.
I asked you
to remember a word.
Yes.
Do you remember what it was?
A word...
Isla...
I have
no diagnostic equipment...
and I can't take a biopsy.
But from what I can observe,
I think you have cancer.
It may have spread
from your brain to your body,
or your body to your brain.
Either way,
it has metastasized.
It explains your symptoms,
and, I'm afraid...
the masses on your breasts
and lymph nodes.
I... I am very sorry.
When I'm confused,
I know I'm confused.
I feel surprised at meself,
when I...
you know,
when I say strange things.
But I say them anyway.
But not all of me is confused.
I thought it might be cancer.
Didn't know how to tell you,
Spike.
I was too scared.
I needed someone else
to tell you, but no one did.
I don't understand.
Are you saying
you can't make me mum better?
I wish I could. But I'm afraid
it's not possible.
What does that mean?
Is she gonna die?
Is the cancer gonna kill her?
Yes.
When?
It's hard to say.
Soon.
Will it hurt her?
Spikey, me love.
Already hurts.
This can't be happening.
Doctor, please, please.
You must be able to help her.
You need a medicine. One...
One of the old medicines
from the hospitals.
If you tell us
where one was I can...
- I can go, and I can get it.
- Spike. Spike. Listen to me.
Just tell us, please.
There is no medicine
that can cure her.
Doctor... Doctor, please.
It was so hard to get here.
- So hard to find you.
- Spike, come here.
Now he's saying
we can't help it.
- Mum.
- Come on. Come on.
- Mum...
- Should've told ya.
Should've told ya.
Please...
Spike.
The doctor
can't make me better,
but he can help me.
I don't understand.
I do.
I want you to try
and always remember that.
I understand.
Mum. Mum?
You're all right.
Mum. Mum.
Shh. Just rest. It's okay.
Hey.
Look who it is.
Spike...
Memento Mori.
What did it mean?
Remember we must die.
And it's true.
There are
many kinds of death...
and some
are better than others.
The best are peaceful.
Where we leave each other
in love.
You love your mother.
I love her.
And Isla, you love Spike.
So much. Mm.
Memento Amoris.
Remember you must love.
Isla.
Come.
Stay here with the baby.
- Mum?
- Love ya, Spike.
Mum?
Spike.
Find a place for her.
The best one of all.
Mum.
Love you, Mum.
Get in! Hurry!
Stay down.
Stay still.
Thank you, Spike.
I think...
I think it's time
for you and the baby...
to go home.
Yeah.
That's it. There.
It's all right, darling.
Dad.
I'm okay.
You don't need to look for me.
I'll come back when I'm ready.
I wanna keep walking...
until I can't see the sea.
We found Dr. Kelson.
He's not insane.
He's a kind man.
A baby?
Come on!
Yeah.
The baby's from an infected...
but she's not.
She's okay.
She was left
just outside the gates.
Please be kind to her.
Her name is Isla.
No!
Spike!
Fuck.
Oh!
Wonderful shot.
It was real poetry.
Though, I think there's
a few too many coming now.
Even for a fine young warrior
like yourself.
Would you mind
if we stepped in?
It would be our pleasure.
All right.
Hold.
Fucking go.
Howzat?
Howzat!
Hello.
My name's Jimmy.
Let's be pals.