Run, I'm going to catch you.
No, don't go in there.
Your mother is going to kill us.
Come on, drop it.
- I'm going to catch you!
- I don't want to go to sleep.
Hey! Come on, to bed now.
The Three Kings are going to come
and catch you still awake.
No, I'm not sleepy.
Yes! Buddy,
your aunt and I have to go home.
Good night.
Uncle, can I see Lúculo?
- All right, but only for a minute, okay?
- Okay.
Come on, and then go to sleep.
Look here, press the button to call him.
Lúculo! Lúculo!
Look, he's coming to see you...
Do you see him? Here?
Can I feed him?
Do you want him
to swell up like a balloon?
To not be able to move,
to get chubby like you?
- I'm not chubby.
- Aren't you?
He'll never be able to move again.
Come on, off to bed,
before your mother gets back.
Come on, Uncle! Five more minutes!
I'll wait up for you.
As long as you're here tomorrow
to open the presents.
Little brother...
It was difficult, but it looks like
he's finally asleep.
In two hours, he'll be in my room,
asking me if the Three Kings have come,
you'll see.
You're sure you don't want
to stay a little longer?
No, no, no, no, no.
Better get home before traffic gets bad.
Sorry you didn't get to see Mario.
He's still at the station.
It's okay. Tell him
he's still my favorite brother-in-law.
All right.
- Okay, guys. Thanks for coming. Bye.
- All right. Bye Belén.
Bye.
We'll talk, okay?
- Okay, I love you.
- I love you, too.
- Be careful, okay?
- Yes.
Are you going to tell me?
- Júlia?
- You know what's wrong.
Stop it.
- This isn't the right time.
- When is the right time?
If you don't want kids, just tell me.
Stop messing with me, please.
Júlia, please.
I'm tired of feeling like
you're stringing me along, my love.
You tell me you don't know
if you're going to be a good father.
That I won't be able to handle it.
- You keep giving excuses...
- Watch out!
Are you okay?
Yeah, yeah. You?
ONE YEAR LATER...
So, we continue to await the result
of the special meeting
of the Council of the European Union
where the possibility of border closures
is being debated.
I'm not sure how you all view the issue.
We should be prudent and wait
to see what the experts say.
Excuse me for a second,
because we are connecting with
Daniel Romero...
THE TSJ VIRUS SPREADS:
EUROPE CLOSES BORDERS WITH RUSSIA
...security expert. He's advising the EU,
specifically, the Directorate-General
for Safety and Public Health.
Good morning, Daniel. A complicated day
in Brussels today, I understand?
Good morning, Antonio.
Well, yes, very, very difficult days.
For hours, we've been receiving
very difficult images from the borders.
You've all seen them.
There are rumors that they intend to adopt
a border closure policy
similar to the one currently
being debated in the European Union.
How likely is it that we'll see
border closures globally?
Very likely.
We're seeing that the incidence of
the TSJ virus is absolutely devastating,
with a total failure of
prevention measures so far.
Considering what we saw
during the Covid-19 pandemic,
I believe we're only a few days away
from more drastic measures.
Guidelines are being considered for...
Deputy González Escalón,
welcome to the program.
Thank you.
You can probably guess
my first question,
why does your party distance itself
from the bioweapon theory?
We don't understand why
the natural origin theory
has been revived so quickly.
So, I understand that you don't believe
the United Nations report...
WELCOME TO THE BEGINNING
OF THE END
...that places the origin in
abandoned labs from the Soviet Union.
That report has
a number of glaring errors.
Errors, like...
Okay, well, for example, it talks
about three abandoned laboratories...
- Combarro.
- What?
- I think it's him.
You're selling the Corinto?
Pleasure to meet you. This is María.
Pleasure to meet you.
Hi.
Where's the boat?
Can't wait to see it.
- Right over here.
- Here?
I think everything was in the ad.
It's nine meters long,
the engine has
a little over 2000 hours on it,
but it's up to date with servicing.
FOR SALE
Yeah?
The sails haven't been used in a year,
but they're in perfect condition.
Thank you.
Do you have any invoices?
Yes, I think so.
Check it out, inside it has...
Does it or does it not suit me perfectly?
It doesn't suit you.
- What do you mean? Look at me.
- No, I don't like it.
- But it's exactly my size.
- Actually, I want to take it off.
Love... I'm stuck!
- It's my favorite bracelet. Careful.
- Okay, okay, don't worry.
- Don't worry.
- Okay. Now.
- I'm sorry.
- No, you broke it.
You broke it, handsome.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry...
Dear customers, we are opening
two additional cash registers.
In order to facilitate your shopping,
our new hours will be from...
Dear customers,
we are working to restock all shelves
as quickly as possible.
We remind you that the government
recommends that you not purchase
more than two unit of each product.
Thank you very much.
Good evening to you all.
To explain the situation we're facing,
joining me is the head of the Ministry
of Health, Fernando Aguirre.
Thank you, Mr. President.
First of all,
we wanted to inform you that yesterday,
the government of La Rioja
contained two cases in the town of Haro.
Also, the government
of the Balearic Islands has informed us
that no cases have been registered
since the incidents at Cala Ratjada
and Inca, both in Mallorca.
Come here. Easy, relax.
These two news items tell us
that right now,
all cases are controlled in Spain,
which is to say,
we are containing the disease.
Lúculo! Lúculo!
Where's Lúculo?
Please leave Lúculo alone.
I have to talk to your uncle.
Mario, please. Take him.
- Go on.
- I want to see Lúculo.
- Let's go.
- Not, but I want to see Lúculo.
- Where's Lúculo?
- There we go.
- What's up?
- I called you a bunch of times.
I was showing the boat to a couple.
Tell me you sold it
and they paid a lot of money.
They were looking for something
a little more modern.
Listen. I have a proposition, okay?
Just a moment.
This morning they called Mario.
They're transferring us
to the Canary Islands
while all this is going on.
He thinks it's to check
information systems,
but they haven't told him anything more.
And when do you leave?
Well, tonight.
And they notified you today?
Listen. Why don't you come with us?
- They're giving us a house.
- I can't. I'm sorry, Belén.
Yes, you can. I checked.
There's a flight tomorrow from Vigo.
- You're not going to be left alone.
- No, I'll be okay.
Come for a few days at least, okay?
Wait for everything to calm down
and then if you want to go back,
- you can grab--
- Belén, please, don't insist.
Imagine we're confined,
like with COVID,
and you're there alone, stranded...
Well, I'm with Lúculo.
Okay. Do it for me.
Do it for me, please.
Come on.
It's only going to be a few days.
Multiple sources are
now confirming alarming news,
the emergence of a new variant
of the TSJ virus,
which has put European authorities
in a tight spot these last 24 hours.
This mutation,
still without an official name,
seems to redefine what we know
about the virus.
It drastically shortens the
incubation period to only a few minutes
from the moment of contagion
to the appearance of severe symptoms.
FORGIVE US LORD
The mode of transmission may be
through contact with blood,
especially caused by subcutaneous
wounds and bites,
ruling out airborne transmission
as a means of infection.
Thanks. No.
Passengers on flight KTV043D
to Barcelona,
board at gate number four.
Your first flight.
Are you nervous?
Passengers on flight VTL290J
to Grand Canary Island,
- board at gate number three.
- Let's go.
Passengers in group number one
may begin boarding.
Please have your boarding pass
and your ID ready.
Thank you.
Yes. Through here.
BARCELONA
BOARDING
Thank you. Have a nice trip.
Hi.
- Perfect. Have a nice trip.
- Thank you.
Hello. How are you?
Wait over here.
Come this way. Go ahead.
I'm boarding now. I'll let you know
when I've landed, okay? Bye.
Thank you. Have a nice trip.
I don't know what's happening.
- Could you step aside one moment?
- What's this about? Why?
We'll figure this out, okay?
One moment, please. We don't...
Okay.
Could you stand there with the gentleman?
One moment.
- Don't worry. I'm asking you...
- No, no. I'm already getting agitated.
CANCELLED
I'm asking you for a little patience.
GRAN CANARIA
CANCELLED
Okay. A little bit of patience, please.
We're trying to find out
what's happening.
CANCELLED
- We'll give you an explanation.
- There aren't any flights?
Please, a little patience.
We're going to look into what's happening.
- We don't know. Calm down, please.
- How do you not know?
You know perfectly well.
- I don't know.
- You're lying.
Please, sir, calm down.
They're messing with us. They want...
They want us all to die here.
CIVIL SECURITY ALERT
TEMPORARY STATE OF ALERT
Sir, return to your place.
I want to get onto that plane! Let me go!
Security!
- Yeah?
- Listen, they're closing the airspace.
Yeah, they're announcing it now.
There's a variant
with a few minutes' incubation.
Go home and lock yourself in
until we know more, okay?
Okay.
- Clear out! Let's go!
- Clear out!
Freeze! Drop the weapon!
Drop the weapon! Now!
News of the state of emergency
has be accompanied by incidents
like the one at Vigo Airport
where a man has been arrested
after stealing a gun and
threatening security personnel,
as well as the disturbances we've been
seeing in various locations.
Meanwhile, we continue to wait
for the president's appearance,
where it is expected he will explain
whether the sudden declaration of
a state of emergency
is related to the possible occurrence
of the new variant in Spain,
and whether there will be
any last-minute directive...
6,4 KM TO PONTEVEDRA
...regarding the restriction of movement
due to the new situation.
We return now to Galicia,
where the regional government's Department
of Infrastructure and Transportation
reports heavy traffic
on all road networks.
The Ferrol-Villalba Highway may be
experiencing a backup
of several kilometers as it passes
through Puentes de García Rodríguez.
Indeed, all highways are showing
significant backups.
We recommend finding alternatives
for your travels.
24/7 News, Galicia.
Concern among the residents of Santiago
over the soldiers who deserted...
Hey, do you need something?
We have to get to Chantada.
My husband's family is there.
Well, honestly,
I think the best thing is to turn around.
What?
The best thing is to turn around
while you can.
Because we're not going to be able
to continue this way.
- Okay. Thanks.
- Thanks.
...tried to take by force
a Maritime Rescue vessel
that was providing them food and water.
To these various disturbances
we have to now add
a group of protesters
who attacked a truck
bound for Zaragoza Air Base,
believing that military personnel
were being evacuated.
We are connected with our correspondent
in Aragon for more on this.
Judit, have you been able to find
any more information
about this attack outside the base?
Good Morning, Saúl.
We've learned that two Air Force officers
have been hospitalized
after the attack...
Let's go home.
- Stand back, please.
- But how can we stand back?
- What's going on? Tell us something.
- Back, back.
- Sir? Move away.
- Can you tell me what's going on?
Move away, please.
Spread out. Clear the area. Go.
- Attention!
- Careful! Careful!
- What's going on?
- Please. Please, it's my...
We'll proceed to...
Clear everything.
- My love! Please! No!
- Keep walking, please. Disperse!
Disperse! Out!
There's nothing to see here, folks!
It's Joaquín Teban!
...serious condition.
We're asking for help with the delay.
BELÉN - ANSWER
Hello.
How are you?
Did you take something to calm down?
Have they told you
when they're going to open the airspace?
Well, it's just that with the new variant,
there are no plans for the short term.
Look, listen, this is important.
They're organizing safe zones
to redistribute the population.
They want to move us?
Yes, well, they want to set up
quarantine zones to control the virus.
But, there are critical voices
inside the army.
The greater the number of people,
the greater the number of infections.
And things have happened in Belgium.
So, no matter what, stay at home.
Understand?
No matter what.
- Hey, do you promise me that?
- Yes, of course. I promise.
Keep me posted.
Mario is on alert and he's bringing you
with us as soon as he can.
- I love you very much.
- I love you, too.
Good morning. The latest news.
Germany declares a quarantine in Munich.
As of a few hours ago,
It is forbidden to enter or leave
the 11th most populated city
in the EU.
Not the first city of the continent
that has been confined, but the biggest
in which there is a total closure.
In fact, it is still not known
how the government is reacting.
Oh, my God! What's he doing?
Is he eating it? It's...
Should we help him or what?
What should we do, help him? Oh fuck.
...areas of the federal state of Bavaria
will be evaluated every eight hours.
You can use things like this as armor.
Durable.
If they come to bite, they bite here.
They're fucked.
See? Foolproof.
What? Over here? Over here?
Where are they going to get in? Okay?
STATE OF EMERGENCY
A State of Emergency is declared
in all national territory
due to special circumstances
in order to preserve order and integrity.
Measures and restrictions
will be implemented:
FROM 2:00PM ALL COMMERCIAL ACTIVITY
IS SUSPENDED.
THE POPULATION MAY BE MILITARIZED
Comply with authority
for your safety.
I don't know, I don't know.
No, I don't know what's happening.
Let's go.
- Run, I think someone's coming.
- Run.
- Open the car.
- Let's go.
What's wrong with you, crazy?
You're crazy, dude!
Let's get out of here!
Help!
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey!
Help! Help! Help! Help!
Come on, fucker.
Help!
No, no, no.
- Are you okay?
- Don't come any closer.
Don't come any closer.
Good evening.
Apologies for the late hour
at which the cabinet meeting ended.
I am appearing before you very briefly
because in half an hour
we'll be meeting again
again to continue coordinating efforts
with our European partners.
As of today, the incidence rate of TSJ
is out of control across the globe,
and Spain is no exception.
Yesterday at 8:00 pm, my government
ordered the temporary evacuation
of several population centers
on the Mediterranean coast of Spain
and extended the lockdown
of cities with more than
400,000 inhabitants.
The remaining population centers
will be moved to safe zones.
To this end, citizens must follow
the guidelines
issued by the regional control units
and the security forces
acting under their authority.
All citizens are reminded
to comply...
EVACUATION
VEHICLE
...with their orders.
Failure to do so will result
in criminal consequences
once normalcy is restored.
As a matter of fact, from the temporary
command center
at La Graciosa in the Canary Islands,
we'd like to pay tribute
to the hundreds of men and women
of law enforcement
who are giving their lives
to save as many citizens as possible.
You have the respect of the Crown,
the government and the country.
And lastly,
the CECOP has stated
that given the lack of maintenance
and as a failure prevention
of the usual means of communication,
communications will be made
only on the emergency radio network.
Thank you very much.
Prepare to be evacuated
to the nearest safe zone.
You will remain there
until the health emergency is over.
Refusal to evacuate will be considered
a violation of National Security Law.
Please, please.
Go up, please.
I don't know, ma'am. Please.
- Ma'am, you can't lock the car. Ma'am...
- Shut up.
Prepare to be evacuated
to the nearest safe zone.
Don't get on that bus
Please, stay in the house
We'll come find you
soon
Stop already. Enough, please.
I'm coming, I'm coming,
I'm coming. I'm coming.
This is the Army speaking.
We must evacuate.
Shut up!
We know you're there! Come out!
We have orders
to evacuate the area immediately.
Open the door!
Come on! We're going to come in!
We can't waste any more time.
We have to move you
to a safe zone immediately.
Come out immediately. This is an order.
Open the door!
I'm coming in there!
This doesn't open. Let's get out of here.
Hi, Belén.
I hope you're okay.
TWO WEEKS LATER...
I hope TSJ
hasn't reached the Canary Islands,
I'm incommunicado, but I'm okay.
NOTICE OF MANDATORY EVACUATION
My only problem is that
I'm starting to run out of food.
I've been thinking about
taking my chances and leaving the house,
but I don't know how dangerous
it might be.
The good thing is that between
the solar panels and the batteries,
I can still stay here for a while.
ENERGY STORAGE SYSTEM
LITHIUM BATTERY
And well, never mind...
let's see if I get a signal again.
And we can finally speak.
I love you all.
I don't have anything.
They said they were just going
to get the children to safety,
and he'd be back soon.
But after half an hour,
his phone had already been shut off.
Why didn't you go with the soldiers?
My brother-in-law is in the military
and advised me not to go. And you?
The bus was faster than I was.
You did well.
Imagine what would happen if there's an
outbreak among the people they've taken.
You did well too.
I'm sure they wouldn't have let you take
that beautiful cat you have.
He watches me from the window a lot.
Forgive me for asking you like this...
Do you have anything to eat?
I could barely buy anything
before all this.
And there might be infected people
outside of the residential area.
That's why you're dressed like a diver.
- This? It's--
- So they can't bite you, yeah.
It's well-conceived.
And you haven't even found
a box of cookies?
All the houses I've looked at are empty.
I think I can help you with that.
That one.
That's the Fidalgos.
They went with the soldiers.
But the day before,
I saw them come home with bags.
I doubt they ate everything.
That's the Arnaiz family.
They had five children. So, there may
still be a lot of stuff inside that house,
but hardly a loaf of bread.
The Rosales family.
The youngest was my daughter's friend.
A piece of work.
You might walk in
and find their abandoned parents.
IT WON'T DEFEAT US
There were bigger houses
at the back.
I'm sure you can find us
something to eat there.
- You know everyone.
- Are you calling me a gossip?
I'm calling you my savior.
Walkies.
If this is all we can get,
you should have gone with the military.
We'll end up eating each other here.
That, or the Santa Compaña
will come for both of us.
There might be a house
with food left.
Which one?
- I'll keep you informed, okay?
- Okay.
Gabriela, I'm going in.
I'm sorry.
- I thought no one was here.
- No, no, I...
- I'm leaving. I'm leaving now.
- Wait, wait, we can...
Do you miss them?
I miss that they didn't say goodbye.
Gabriela.
I'm sorry, but I don't think your family
treated you well, not at all.
They did the best they could.
Sometimes things can be done better.
And you? Don't you miss that girl?
I haven't seen her in a while.
- Forgive me for asking, I didn't want...
- No. No, no.
I'm sorry, Gabriela.
She died a little over a year ago.
In a car accident.
I'm sorry.
I don't know, Maybe it's better
she didn't live to see this.
Do you have photos of her?
Yes, of course.
Here.
How lovely.
You should meet my neighbor.
In one week, I have anecdotes to tell
for the rest of my life.
Belén...
Nothing, I just wanted to tell you that
I'm sorry.
For not having come to visit
this whole year.
You only lived half a hour away and...
I've been an idiot.
That's all. It's just...
Sending a kiss.
Are you there?
Can you hear me?
- Yes?
- It's Gabriela. Do you have a radio?
On 100.
Okay. Okay, okay.
I think I have something.
- They're playing music.
- Wait.
This message is for all survivors
who are listening.
You can find us in the Arousa Estuary,
- coordinates 36 degrees 37-31 to 72 W.
- What do you think?
- We're sending survivors to the Canaries.
- I don't know.
I don't trust the estuary.
If people gather there,
there will be more risk of infection.
Yeah, but we're running out of food.
We could try.
I don't know, son. I don't know.
And how would we get there?
We could take my boat.
I can't.
What do you mean, you can't?
Of course you can.
I'm barely capable of going out
to the street.
No. Don't worry.
I'll help you. Whatever it takes.
Gabriela.
Can you hear me?
I'm here.
Okay.
If you think I won't be a burden,
I'll go with you.
We'll make it, Gabriela.
You'll see.
Gabriela, I'll be there in five minutes.
Gabriela, can you hear me?
Gabriela?
Gabriela!
THANK YOU FOR THESE DAYS
NOW YOU HAVE TO SAVE YOURSELF
Gabriela.
Belén,
infected people are showing up and...
I don't think I can
wait for you any longer.
I received a message over the radio
from a group of survivors
at the estuary...
who from there are going
to go to the Canaries.
I'm going to meet up with them.
With a little luck,
I'll find a location with coverage
and I'll be able to send you
all this at once.
Don't worry if it takes a few days
to hear from me, okay?
Lúculo! Lúculo!
Are you okay? Okay, okay.
Okay.
Let's go.
Fuck!
It's all right. Easy.
That's it.
It's all right, that's it. That's it.
Come on.
Damn it!
Hi, sister.
I still haven't found coverage.
You were right not to trust
the safe zones.
Leaving the housing development,
I saw an abandoned military detachment,
or something like that.
And now I'm going down
the Pontevedra Estuary and...
it's all destroyed.
I just want you to know I'm okay,
and I'm strong.
I think I found a way
to get to the Canary Islands.
I love you all.
And I really miss you.
Hey! Hey! Hello! Hello!
Help! Help! Here!
Relax. Relax.
Hello.
My name is Pritchenko. Viktor Pritchenko.
He's Ushakov, captain of the boat.
The captain wants to know
if you're from around here.
Yes. I live very close to Pontevedra.
In a kind of residential development.
And where are you from?
What were you doing in the estuary?
I've been following the radio message
- to go to the Canary Islands.
- The Canary Islands?
Yes. The government, the military,
everybody's there.
If you want, I can take you.
I know the route.
The ship broke down
just as the "viys" arrived.
The police didn't let anyone disembark,
that's why they're all here.
I'm sorry.
- What do you do?
- I'm a lawyer.
Well, and I have a small
solar panel company.
I said you're an engineer.
Nobody likes lawyers.
I came from Ukraine to pilot firefighting
helicopters a few months ago.
And to see the famous Vigo Christmas.
Well, for a Ukrainian,
you speak Spanish very well.
Yeah, yeah. My mother was Mexican.
I learned to speak Russian in school.
Over there, it was like English.
That's all we can offer now.
- Thank you very much.
- Tomorrow we'll need you
you to identify locations in the area
where we can find materials,
provisions.
- Okay?
- Of course, whatever you need.
- Okay.
- Excuse me...
Haven't you found any more survivors?
No, I'm afraid you're the first.
Rest up, okay?
How did you sleep?
Don't run up the stairs,
they're very slippery.
The captain wants to talk to you.
Hey, last night,
I saw new people arrive, right?
Nobody came last night.
What do you mean? There were two men,
and a woman and a girl too.
Hey...
Nobody arrived last night, understood?
This is a car factory. Do you know it?
I'm sure it's been ransacked,
but you could find
all kinds of materials there.
Concrete. Is there concrete around there?
I don't know. Concrete?
There's a plant on the way to Vilagarcía.
The ones who arrived last night
are downstairs, right?
Ushakov wants your help.
Say thank you and forget everything else.
What the fuck is going on here?
Viktor, tell me truth. Are we prisoners?
The interrogation is over.
Listen, I know where there's a helicopter.
At a hospital,
on the outskirts of Pontevedra.
We can take it and fly to
the Canary Islands. You're a pilot, right?
Do you want to stay alive?
Keep your head down.
Don't ask any more questions.
The vacation at sea is over.
Please don't hate me, okay?
My wife and my daughter!
- Calm down, please. Calm down.
- Please.
Calm down. Calm down.
I don't know where they are.
I told you not to get into trouble.
I hope what you said
about the helicopter is true.
Hurry up! Faster!
Come on, Viktor.
Hold on, fuck.
CHARGING
There's a heliport at a hospital
very close to here.
You'll see, we'll be in the Canary Islands
before you know it.
- Viktor, answer me. Viktor, wake up!
- I'm here. I'm here.
Thank you.
Thank you for saving my life, Viktor.
Ushakov is a monster.
This hell fits him like a glove.
And what did he do
with the families of these men?
He's building a refuge
on the island of Sálvora.
He only lets those who serve him live.
When all this ends, people will have to
answer for what they've done.
Look around you.
This will never end.
No, no, no, no.
Where is it? No, no, no, no, no.
What about the helicopter?
Okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay.
Easy. No. No, no, no, no, no.
Let's go, Viktor. Let's go, go, go, go.
Wait here.
Let's go.
That's it.
Let's go. Let's go. Let's go.
Wait.
Let's go.
Come on.
Hold on.
Let's go.
That's it.
- Take it out.
- What?
- I don't understand.
- You have to take the bullet out.
You have to take the bullet out.
Okay.
All right. One moment.
Hold on. Hold on, okay?
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
Don't move from here.
Stay with him, okay? Go on.
Max, please.
Go away, they're here!
Hello?
Me, Leila.
It was me, Lucía.
Iria, you'll get caught!
Hello?
Hello? Is someone there?
- Hello?
- Hi. Where are you?
- There's a man here.
- Where? Down there?
Yes, down there.
- Please.
- Hello.
There's a man here.
Yes, and you can hear him
- Hello! Please, here!
- Is someone there?
Yes, yes, hello.
We're in the operating room.
Hi? We're here. Can you hear us?
No, no, no, no!
Over here! Come on!
Let's go.
- Help me.
- Yes.
Wait.
- Come on, Viktor.
- Careful with his neck.
Let's go.
The legs.
He's in bad shape. Come on. Let's see.
- Okay. Quickly
- Yes.
To the back.
Lucía.
Help us. He's wounded.
- What happened to him?
- He's been shot.
Come on, let's go.
Kids, move aside.
Do you think it scratches?
- He looks nice.
- Yeah.
- Do you think he'll let us pet him?
- I don't know.
You ask.
- You go, you go. I want to pet him.
- Yes, me. You go.
- You tell him.
What's his name?
- His name is Lúculo.
- Lúculo?
He was a Roman soldier who ate a lot.
But, don't ask me anything else,
I didn't name him.
- Is he very old?
- Four years.
Do you want to pet him?
Come on. Let's go.
It's okay.
Relax, they just want to meet you.
Carefully. Very good.
- Like this, carefully.
- He's so soft.
- Very good.
- So soft.
He's very beautiful.
Stay calm, it's okay.
We just want to meet you.
We've removed the bullet.
He has a slight fever,
so we have to wait.
Thank you. Thank you very much.
We didn't know there was anyone in here.
We were looking for a helicopter,
but we were too late.
Are you a pilot?
It was the triage and quarantine area.
It didn't last half a day.
Is there any way to get down there?
Not from this building.
The courtyard is full of them,
and without weapons,
we wouldn't last long.
Below are the boilers,
which have access to the courtyard,
but a few days ago,
we heard an explosion and I...
I don't know,
it is dangerous for the children.
Can your friend really fly
that helicopter?
Yes. If he recovers, yes.
We're almost out of food.
And their parents?
They died. They worked here.
It's been very difficult for them.
Poor little angels.
Iria didn't speak for a week.
Leila is still getting used
to the situation.
Some days, she still asks
when her mother will come back.
- And what do you tell them?
- The truth.
In their way, with their words.
We always try and find moments
during the day talk about their parents.
We ask them to remember
happy moments they shared with them.
Sister Cecilia, I'm thirsty.
Okay.
The key is not to resist the pain
and to learn to live with it.
It's the only way
to let it go, little by little.
If only it were that easy.
My wife died here.
- A little over a year ago.
- I'm sorry.
...is going into cardiac arrest.
I'm sorry, Júlia.
I thought we had
all the time in the world.
Forgive me.
NOTIFICATIONS
BELÉN
- Mom, come to the pool. Come on!
- Just a minute.
Carlos, wait, I'm calling your uncle.
Well, I haven't heard from you
for two hours.
Mario says it's normal,
that the networks fail, and...
- Let's go! Mom, come to the pool.
- Carlos, please, wait.
Well, I'll try later, okay? Bye, bye.
Guys!
They left me alone, at home.
They're setting up some games
on the beach for the kids here.
I'm really worried, little brother.
I hope you get this message
and remember how much I love you.
I don't know when we'll be able to
talk again. Take care.
When will you come to us?
Because we...
- We miss you a lot.
- A lot.
- And we... love you. Very much!
- We love you.
Bye.
And Lúculo? How's Lúculo? Where's Lúculo?
Lúculo? How's Lúculo?
Maybe he's gone out...
Come here. Will you quit stealing my...
Stop stealing my phone!
Belén.
I'm doing well.
I'm doing really well now.
It's just that...
You wouldn't even believe
where I ended up.
- Very dangerous people are coming.
- Did they follow you?
They're looking for supplies in the area.
You've put us in danger.
We have to reach the helicopter
before them. Where are those tunnels?
- Let's go.
- What's wrong, Lucía?
- Let's go change.
- Where are we going?
- Let's go, let's go.
One last effort. I promise.
Your mouth. Tightly.
Like that. Very good.
How are you doing? Ready?
Don't take it off, okay?
No matter what happens. Let's go.
Careful. There are stairs.
Slowly. Slowly.
Hey kids, don't look.
We're sticking together closely.
- How much left?
- Just a little, I think.
Did you hear that?
Let's go, quickly.
Come on.
The heat must have warped the door.
Max.
- Carefully, okay?
- Okay.
Hit it with the axe.
Sister Cecilia.
No. Don't come any closer.
Save the children.
Please, save them.
Okay. I think the door is locked
from the outside. I need to open it.
Okay. I'll cover you.
Mom.
Let's go.
Are you okay? Are you okay?
Are you okay?
- Leila! Oh my God.
- That's it, kids.
- Hey, please... Are you okay?
- Lúculo.
- That's it...
- Are you okay?
That's it. That's it, dear,
we're going now.
Are you okay?
One last effort.
What happened?
How much time do you need
to start the helicopter?
It depends on the shape it's in, but...
Just a little left, let's go.
I have a plan.
They're coming!
I'm going.
Quickly.
Come on, let's go, run!
- Lucía, run!
- Lucía!
- Lucía! Lucía!
Lucía, run!
Run, come on! Lucía!
Lucía!
- Let's go!
- Lucía, run!
Run, run!
Run!
What's wrong?
I don't know.
- No, no, no, this can't happen, Viktor.
- Let me think.
There's no time.
Stay calm.
Let's go!
How are you doing?
Alive.
- And you?
- Barely.
BELÉN - ANSWER
- Belén.
- Manel?
- Manel! Can you hear me?
- Yes.
Manel, where are you?
- I'm on my way.
- On your way?
- In a helicopter, yes.
- What? Say again?
On my way to the Canary Islands.
I made it, Belén.
No! No, no, no!
- No! Don't come!
- What?
No! Listen to me!
Don't come to the Canaries.
For the love of God! Manel!
Manel, don't come to the Canaries.
Turn back around! Turn around, don't come!
Please don't come to the Canaries!
Fourteen to Base...
APOCALYPSE Z
THE BEGINNING OF THE END