Day 34 of observing Eun-seo
via the smart home system,
and behavior observation cams.
The cause of her symptoms
may have stemmed from
the panic disorder five years ago,
after our mother's passing,
and the stress of moving
along with the stress of
practicing all day
for her audition by herself.
A fallen angel who rules Hell
A demon that
devours child sacrifices
Chief lieutenant of Lucifer
A fallen angel
who became Hell's guardian
Leader of the worshipers
overseeing the entire ritual
Followers of the Devil
The act of freeing someone
from possession by an evil spirit
DEMON HUNTERS
All done!
Evening, Kim.
- Det. Choi, welcome.
- Good evening.
Hey, Sharon.
Is Ba-woo in?
Yes, he is.
He's a client.
- Good evening.
- Hello.
You may go inside.
Boss, Det. Choi is here.
A month ago, my daughter
became unreachable,
I think she went missing.
She'd never just disappear.
Something is definitely wrong here.
Three of my men were assaulted
while searching for her.
Two are dead, and one's in ICU.
As usual, I need your help on this.
If the detectives were harmed,
I realized it was more serious.
So I asked him for a favor
and came to you for help.
Don't worry too much,
we'll look into this case closely.
Kim, get something to drink.
Sure, one moment.
I'm okay...
Pardon me...
Sorry about that.
Do you have any leads?
We secured a location
from a photo we obtained,
but my team got attacked
and we couldn't rescue her.
Here, Sharon.
- Here you go.
- Thank you.
Thanks.
- Go inside.
- Okay.
Would you like some water?
Don't worry, we'll do our best.
Detective...
Can I trust them...
You can absolutely trust us.
We may look shady,
but we're professionals.
Please find her for me.
- We'll do our best.
- Yes, sir.
Thank you.
Here's the payment,
in cash as usual.
You didn't skimp some
like last time, right?
What do you take me for?
I'm a cop.
How many clients
have I brought you so far?
For your kids.
What do you take me for?
Don't want it?
This is serious.
A lot of people have been killed.
I hear you.
All right, guys.
Let's go to work.
Murders and assaults are
taking place
by unknown assailants
across the country,
leaving the public in fear.
Bold Murder in the City Center
– Police Helpless
The police believe that
a mysterious group,
along with organized criminals,
are involved.
A special task force has been formed,
but the criminals have brutally
murdered officers at the scene...
In my 30 years as an officer,
I've never seen
such vicious incidents, Father.
They talk about demons and devils,
and as we witness
unbelievable events,
we can't handle this with
the police force alone, Father.
They blindly devote themselves
to a devil worshipper,
and obtained superhuman strength
by drawing on the Devil's power.
Ordinary people can't stand up to them.
That's why we need him.
Kill them!
You vile demon.
I command you.
Return to hell!
You are Bael, the Commander of Hell's Army.
Return to hell at once!
Return!
I command you!
Return to hell!
Return to hell immediately!
I command you.
Return to hell.
Return to hell immediately!
Let's see.
Okay.
Everything all right?
I'm fine.
No, not you, her.
The evil spirit hadn't fully
possessed her, she'll be okay.
That's good.
Um, boss...
Things got pretty hairy earlier,
I missed some shots in the end.
What should I do?
Have another take?
Should I wake them all up?
No, we can't do that
but we need a proper ending.
You should've shot properly!
Yeah...
Is Det. Choi on the way?
Yes, he's heading over.
I got a lot better thanks to you.
I can breathe better,
thank you so much.
I'm glad to hear it.
You should still take your meds,
and I'll drop the dosage
as I monitor the progress.
Check up on her every 2 hours.
Yes, doctor.
Suspected of Schizophrenia Day 142 /
Exorcism Treatment Day 7
The Man Who Punched Out
Four Gangs and Illegal Fight Clubs
Are They Devils? Or Messiahs?
Catalina, it's fine.
I'm making money to build
a Catholic orphanage.
No need to thank me.
Yeah, Catalina, okay.
Boss, I found out who
those guys served.
Who?
Beelzebul.
Chief lieutenant of Lucifer
Who's their leader?
I haven't found their archbishop yet,
but I got informants all over the place.
Ton of high-ranking demons
like Beelzebul are popping up,
a massive crisis may be on the horizon.
I've seen them countless times,
but they still scare me.
We're scared too.
They're powered by demon's energy,
so always keep your guard up.
You still have a bright future.
And me?
Me?!
Is my future bleak?
So hot today...
Excuse me.
Be gone!
My apologies, who are you?
May I help you?
Could I meet the owner?
Yes, I'm the owner,
what can I do for you?
My sister is really sick.
I came here because
I'm at wit's end.
Did Det. Choi tell you about us?
No, Father Mar...
Father Marco recommended us?
My apologies, we do not
work with them.
I'm sorry.
My sister is in danger!
If you help us,
I'll do anything.
I brought money too.
Here.
If...
If she's sick,
take her to the hospital.
She should see a neuropsychiatrist.
I'm a neuropsychiatrist!
Christ...
Please...
This contains her videos,
please give it to him.
I'm begging you.
I understand.
Han Eun-seo
This is my sister and my home.
Jung-won and Eun-seo's home.
Let's live happily here.
- Let's never fight.
- Yeah, let's not fight.
Don't steal my clothes.
Don't use my make-up.
We moved today,
so let's be happy.
Let's be happy.
- Thank you, sis.
- Not at all.
You like it?
Yeah, the air is so nice here.
As a fellow doctor, I couldn't
believe it until I saw your sister.
Since the Church officially
prohibits exorcism,
I suggested you go to him.
Of course, as a doctor, I know
you must have had doubts...
Devil, exorcism,
I don't know about these things.
I simply want to save
my sister, Father.
- Hey.
- Yes?
Where did Sharon go?
She should be in her office.
By the way, boss,
do you want to see the footage
that pretty doctor brought?
Nah, forget it.
But if Father Marco sent her,
it could be something big.
Don't ever mention
his name to me again.
I'm sorry.
Where's Sharon,
I need to give this to her.
I'm right here.
Holy Jesus!
She's right here...
Could you stop sneaking up on us?
- Sharon
- Kim Goon
Here, here.
Your salary,
thank you as always.
Good work.
Here.
Put it away.
Why is mine so thin?
Sharon's work is a lot tougher.
She's gotta perform rites
on blades and stuff.
When do I ever do that?
Anyway, she does a lot
of really difficult tasks, thanks.
Take it.
Thank you, bud.
Wait a minute.
Demons and their worshippers
are increasing and getting bolder.
They flex their shit
in the middle of the city.
More and more people
are dying, am I right?
And our workload is growing too, right?
So, how about a salary bump?
It's been a while, hasn't it?
10 years already.
You haven't changed at all.
Of course, I've had this face
since I was 19.
Your sense of humor
hasn't changed either.
Dr. Han Jung-won came by,
didn't she?
I know you refused
because of me, but her sister...
I no longer want to
get involved with you.
I know you still resent me.
I struggled too, so many lives
were lost back then.
But I didn't want to accept
that Joseph was involved.
The Joseph we knew
no longer exists.
Only Lucifer, who killed
our angelic children and nuns, remains.
The demon you raised.
I prayed with regrets and tears.
The will of God--
Those children...
are all dead, is that the will of God?
Even if you can't forgive me,
can't you help her?
Eun-seo!
Park, Kidnapped by
Mysterious Group, Found Dead
I came to thank you.
If it wasn't for you, I might not
have said good bye to my son.
If only we acted sooner...
No, thanks to you,
we recovered his body,
and comforted his soul,
I'm just so thankful.
Archbishop
The Domestic Activities of Unknown Cult.
Lucifer - Joseph
Let's not look at it.
Holy shit, Sharon!
7 years ago, the boss saved
our lives from the demons.
Spare us!
He saved us from Lucifer,
along with Sister Catalina.
If it wasn't for him,
we'd already be dead.
What do we have to be afraid of?
Let's help that doctor.
I really want to help her too.
Observation day 34.
The cause of her symptoms
may have stemmed from
the panic disorder five years ago,
after our mother's passing,
and the stress of moving
along with the stress of
practicing all day
for her audition by herself.
Eun-seo, med time.
Eun-seo...
Eun-seo?
Don't talk to me!
I've got a good feeling about this.
Wish me luck.
Parcel delivery!
I'll leave it here!
Eun-seo?
Eun-seo!
Blair! All lights on!
Eun-seo?
- Eun-seo?
Where are you?
- Where are you?
Eun-seo?
- Eun-seo?
Eun-seo!
- Eun-seo!
This is the police,
what is your emergency?
I...
I'm sorry.
Eun-seo, what are you doing there?
Eun-seo?
Are you okay? Eun-seo...
Eun-seo...
Eun-seo!
Eun-seo! Are you okay?
Crimes committed by
a mysterious group are increasing.
Over 30 police officers
have died in the line of duty,
and countless civilians have
either died or have gone missing.
Kim!
Yes, boss!
Show me the footage.
I want to go home,
let me go home!
I want to go home!
You bitch!
Fire will rain down from heaven,
and demons from hell
will drag people into pits of fire...
Jung-won...
Despite all the treatments,
her deviant behavior must be
attributed to...
my shortcomings...
Take a look at this.
I found another video,
there's a bigger problem.
Thank you so much.
As the landlord,
it's the least we can do.
We aren't anal landlords!
We moved all our big furniture
into the shed out back.
It's really dusty,
and there's still so much stuff...
All done?
Yes, smart home monitoring system
and CCTV are fully operational.
Look at that.
What's happening to her
must be connected to Lucifer.
A fallen angel who rules Hell
Joseph...
Ba-woo grew up in the orphanage
with Joseph,
a boy 3 years younger than him.
Sister Angela raised them both
like her own children.
They were both among the chosen few.
Ba-woo had the physicality
and strength like a rock,
while Joseph had the ability
to draw demons out of people.
Other kids were scared of Joseph
and shunned him,
but Ba-woo always protected him,
and they grew as close as brothers.
Joseph chose the path of priesthood,
while Ba-woo used his fists to earn
money in the underground world,
and always looked after
the orphanage and Joseph.
Ba-woo would visit the orphanage
every Christmas...
No!
But 15 years ago,
Joseph summoned the devil,
and massacred the orphans and
Sister Angela before disappearing.
Ba-woo miraculously survived
but consumed by the guilt
for failing to save his loved ones,
he began hunting down Joseph
and slaying demons.
Help me...
Joseph absorbed the vitality of others,
to increase the evil power
inside him.
Foolishly, I didn't want to believe
he was capable of such evil.
That's why I could not
disclose this to the Order.
During that time, he disappeared,
and Ba-woo found out later,
and it's very likely he rejected you
because of me.
Hello?
This is Holy Night's Kang Ba-woo.
Could we meet for a bit?
Catholic Seoul Hospital
Neuropsychiatry Center
The exorcism will be
performed by Sharon.
And Kim will assist you
by your side.
I didn't get to tell you earlier,
but in cases like this,
demons and their worshippers
could appear near Eun-seo,
so I need to keep them at bay.
She has a special ability
to sense evil.
She knows how to fight them
better than anyone.
Turn your eyes white,
you know, to show her we're legit.
I can't do that now.
Right...
It's a dangerous ritual,
you and Eun-seo could be at risk.
We're always risking our lives.
Are you still willing to do it?
Yes, if it means saving my sister.
Our lives are on the line too...
- Anyway, Kim.
- Yes?
Get the briefing ready.
What's certain is, a demon has
settled in her body.
Why did this happen to her?
Have any strangers
ever enter your home?
No, it's a remote house,
we don't have any guests.
It seems these people
summoned a demon through her.
We don't know who these people are
until we figure out their symbol.
They're always around us
posing as good neighbors.
We call them 'worshippers'.
They worship the devil,
obedient to demons,
cause harm to people
and spread evil.
These worshippers are trained
like soldiers and harm people.
So-called 'Demons' are bishops
that control various regions,
and they're closer to
evil deities than humans.
They follow the archbishop's orders
to select the sacrifice and lead all rituals.
But why go after Eun-seo?
For thousands of years, they've used
pure and vulnerable souls like Eun-seo
as a medium to summon demons
and reshape the world.
Anyone can be a target.
We'll have to meet her.
Eun-seo, are you awake?
Can you hear me?
Yes...
I came to help you,
could we chat for a bit?
Yes...
Aside from me, is there
anyone else talking to you?
Yes...
Who is that?
I don't know...
I can't tell you.
Could I talk to that person?
You can't.
Why not?
I'm scared...
If he responds to me,
he will leave your body.
Don't you want him to leave?
I'm... so scared...
I'll begin.
Who are you?
Answer me, who are you?
Answer me!
Do not hide behind the child,
and answer me, who are you?
Why are you doing this to me?
I haven't done anything wrong.
Vile demon.
Reveal your name
and return to hell.
Vile demon.
Reveal your name
and return to hell.
Eun-seo...
No, doctor!
Vile demon!
Reveal your name
and return to hell!
Vile demon!
Reveal your name
and return to hell!
and return...
Where is she right now?
It's near the entrance.
What do we do?
She's trying to get out!
Get off me!
Get going!
Doctor!
Eun-seo!
Wait!
Jung-won!
No!
Eun-seo!
It's too dangerous!
I'll come to you,
stay right there!
Sis, I'm scared...
Eun-seo!
- Jung-won!
- Doctor!
Jung-won, are you okay?
Sir, are you hurt at all?
The demon is so deeply entrenched,
I can't tell what it is.
We must end it where it all started.
Staying at the hospital will put her
and other patients at risk.
Yes, let's do that.
We have to move,
there's no time.
Eun-seo...
Hang in there a little longer.
Dammit!
I just can't tell
where they'll come from.
It's no use.
Eun-seo...
Mister...
Save me...
I'll save you no matter what.
There are 6 stages of exorcism.
The goal of each stage is to
make the demon reveal its name,
and expelling it from Eun-seo's body.
Please follow my orders
at every stage.
Once we start the exorcism,
it must not be stopped.
If it stops, her life and ours
may be in grave danger.
Presence
The first stage is 'Presence'.
We force the demon
to reveal itself.
Sis, I'm scared...
Please send them all away...
I'm so scared...
Eun-seo, it's okay.
Doctor, don't answer the demon.
Kim, everything ready?
Yes.
Jung-won.
Jung-won?
I mean, I'm not a demon.
Yes?
Turn on the machine.
Okay.
Her vitals are within normal range.
Let's begin.
You must answer all my questions.
Or you will feel intense pain.
A bamboo that wards off
evil and malevolent energies
Do not touch me, no!
A bamboo that wards off
evil and malevolent energies
Tell me your name!
Tell me!
What happened?
We're entering 'Deception' stage.
Deception
The evil will try to deceive us.
Jung-won...
I'm so scared...
Could you untie me?
A small mirror
imbued with the shaman's soul
An act to convey
the words of the guardian spirit
You want to know my name?
Should I tell you?
The demon isn't pretending.
Before existence,
I was the first being.
I am both one and infinite.
I am eternity and finality.
I am within you,
I am not within you.
The interior lights are being shut off.
Something's odd.
I'll look into it,
stay on guard.
Okay.
There you were.
Dammit...
I exist everywhere, and nowhere.
You vile demon.
Reveal your name at once,
and expel from the girl.
You're too chicken shit
to come in here.
Come in, do it.- Come in, do it.
Petty priests like you
can never defeat us.
The demon within,
release her at once!
Expel yourself!
The demon within,
release her at once!
Expel yourself!
Hey, it's me.
Boss, are you okay?
Yeah, I'm fine now.
Boss, I told you once before,
always watch out for
the powder they throw at you.
It could paralyze you,
and you could even die from it.
All right, get on with it.
Okay.
Now it's the third stage,
'Break Point'.
You should use this moment
to get some rest.
Break Point
Jung-won?
Are you okay?
I command you
in the name of our almighty creators,
return to the netherworld!
Return at once!
Jung-won, wake up!
Doctor, it's okay,
everything's fine.
The demon entered
your body momentarily.
They sometimes target
a family member during the exorcism.
There's something else
in the house.
- Bud.
- Yes?
Don't read that.
Okay.
What does it mean?
I'm not sure.
It's an ancient language called 'Igbo'.
This is why all these unexpected
events kept happening.
There is a curse
on the entire house.
What do we do then?
We have to remove
all of these symbols.
Did something happen to me?
It felt like something
left my body.
Eun-seo, are you okay?
Feeling better?
Wait.
Jung-won...
Could you untie me?
Eun-seo, is that you?
Do you recognize me?
Hold on.
This bitch will die
one way or another.
Remember?
You let all those poor children die.
'Voice' stage has begun.
Voice
Mister, save me...
Help me, Mr. Ba-woo!
Joseph killed them?
No, you killed them.
They all died because
you couldn't stop him.
Let's go visit him together.
Then you can achieve eternal life.
If not, you'll end up killing
this child too.
Just like you killed Sister Angela,
your mother figure.
Kill! Kill! Kill!
Boss!- Kill!
- Boss, boss, no!
- Kill!
Sharon!
Boss, I'm okay.
Do not fall prey to its delusion.
Daggers imbued
with a divine spirit
Why are you siding with humans?
Your power did not come from him,
but from my brother!
If my power came from your brother,
it proves he couldn't defeat me.
Do you think you can handle
that much power?
Here you go.
What's this?
A lid.
Why did you bring a lid?
You said to bring
something to cover.
I meant a coat to cover
her body, you moron.
Why do you waste your life
on these pathetic beings?
You know it eats away your body,
as you use your power.
You've felt it,
is it worth saving these humans,
who are wicked and greedy?
Be with us, sister.
Be with us.
I am not your sister.
Get out of my head!
Reveal your name!
I'll make this pain go away!
Tell me your name, now!
Tell me your name!
Tell me!
What's your name!
Jung-won, please...
Save me...
Stop it! Please!
- Jung-won!
- You can't!
It's not over yet!
The boundary...
Wait.
Step back.
This bitch is mine now.
We're now in 'Clash' stage.
We need to find her quickly.
Clash
Sharon...
With your power,
we can rule the world.
Be with us, sister.
Be with us.
Boss, we're locked in!
Move out of the way.
I'm doing a lot of
home degrading today.
Wait, boss!
What is it?
It's an automatic door.
Dammit...
Jung-won...
Eun-seo, are you in there?
Eun-seo!- Jung-won!
Hey, hey!
- Are you okay?
- You good?
I'm fine, doctor...
Is there a room
we don't know about?
We moved all our big furniture
into the shed out back.
Shed...
Over there!
What's that?
The demon is taking
more control over her.
Eun-seo...
Doctor, no! No!
So, this is where you hang out.
Wounded soul,
why do you use the power
devil has given you on humans?
Are you Korean?
If you interfere with us,
only death awaits you.
Go, kill Sharon.
Die, die, feel the terror.
Ba-woo! Die!
Die!
Sharon!
Boss...
Blood, you're bleeding!
What do we do, boss?
I am your Omega.
You are my Alpha.
I am the new path.
With my kingdom
created with blood of children,
I will rule you all.
Now I get it.
I know who you are.
We're in the final stage, 'Expulsion'.
Expulsion
After this stage,
we can save Eun-seo.
Expulsion
A foul deity of death
that takes child sacrifices.
Moloch!
Your time is up.
Return to where you came from!
I expel you, Moloch!
Return to hell at once!
Return to hell, Moloch!
Return to where you came from!
I expel you, Moloch!
Return to hell at once!
Return to hell, Moloch!
I expel you, Moloch!
Return to where you came from!
Return to hell!
At once, Moloch!
I expel you!
- Eun-seo!
- Not yet!
The demon is being expelled.
Defeated by petty exorcists!
I will one day shred you all!
And I am taking this bitch to hell.
She's mine.
Eun-seo!
Sharon!
Eun-seo! No! No!
No!
Sharon!
I am the Grim Reaper!
Leave the child alone,
Valac's incarnation is ordering you!
Return to hell!
Your time is almost up!
If you want to live,
accept the power of hell!
Return to hell, Moloch!
Eun-seo...
Eun-seo?
Can you hear me?
Jung-won...
I'm so sorry...
DON LEE
SEO HYUNDAVID LEE
GYEONG SU-JINJUNG ZI-SO
Grand Opening of Angela Orphanage
I'm taking the photo, look here!
Everyone, smile!
One, two, three!
That's enough, kids.
Ba-woo, please come by
when you get a chance.
- Let's move.
- Okay.
Yes, sir.
DEMON HUNTERS