Ladies and gentlemen.
Get ready and hold your breath.
Here we go!
Ride the wind!
Some roads lead into the fire.
Some roads lead into the sea.
Some roads lead into the light.
Some roads lead into a fight.
Some roads lead into your heart.
Some roads shake you.
Some roads take you
to the start.
Everyone has an identity.
In different times and places,
we all play different roles.
Are you crazy?
A student, worker,
father, daughter, and hero.
You have good luck!
My name's Li Yunxiang.
Right now, I'm a motorcycle racer.
The one who's about to win the race.
Not yet, though.
Each person finds their own place
Along the path
I'm still not the rider
Who has won your heart yet
My bike's roaring
The wind's soaring
Blow away all the numb indifference
In this troubled world
God knows if I am
How I should be yet
I know I just
Can't stand the way you look at me
I risk my life finding myself
In chaos and speed
Only if I give it my all will I succeed
-That's amazing!
The competition just now was so exciting!
Hurry up!
Let us congratulate Li Yunxiang
for winning
the Underground Street Race again!
Thank you.
That was close,
but you managed to save yourself.
Li Yunxiang,
your condition today is not bad.
Show some respect.
Don't you know who I am?
I thought I was doomed. I have no idea
how the motorcycle flew across.
You didn't know,
but I was so anxious up there.
I know you want to impress her,
but there's no need to risk your life.
She is a tough competition.
I had to pull out a wild card.
Haven't you always liked her?
-Go talk to her then. This is typical.
-Get off.
What are you scared of?
GASOLINE
True, she is a bit older than me.
Soon,
you'll be calling her Aunt.
Cut it out.
You don't get it, silly girl.
You choose love over friendship.
I'm still standing here.
We met again.
That was extreme, right?
Great work on the motorcycle.
Hey, I still don't know your name.
You are upsetting your girlfriend.
-She is not--
-See you next time.
Let's do this again soon!
You are bad at flirting.
Hey, kid, your motorcycle looks good.
Help me with mine someday.
Why should I do that?
You are going? I run this place!
I live here!
Come hang out when you are free.
Make sure you modify my motorcycle!
THE NEW ORDER OF THE GODS
AROSE FROM CHAOS.
3,000 YEARS AGO,
HAVOC REIGNED AMONG GODS AND HUMANS.
THE GODS FOUGHT FOR SUPREMACY.
THE WORLD SETTLED
UNDER THE NEW CELESTIAL ORDER.
ANOTHER ERA OF CHAOS
AND CONFLICT BEGAN.
IN DONGHAI CITY,
AN UNEASY TRUCE REIGNED.
DE, LI, SONG, AND SHUN,
FOUR CLANS RULED.
AMONG THEM,
DE CLAN WAS THE MOST POWERFUL.
IN RECENT YEARS,
DONGHAI HAD RUN OUT OF WATER.
Water is gold.
Donghai has affections.
Donghai's De Group brings you water.
-We believe that De Group…
-Extra!
-Everyone must conserve water!
-…will create a better tomorrow.
-Crackdown on smugglers!
-Only half a pail left?
-Boss De invests widely in Donghai!
-Give me some.
Newsboy, give me a copy!
Your paper!
Extra! The water shortage worsens!
-Kid, give me a paper.
-Here.
Thank you, boss!
Extra! The water shortage worsens!
-The people are--
-Tiger.
Tell me, is there any money
in water speculation?
If I knew,
I wouldn't have to sell newspapers.
Get lost.
Crackdown on water smugglers!
Be careful, kid. It's a new dress.
Ms. San, you look so pretty.
You might catch the boss's eye
and go from crow to phoenix.
You little shit, so I'm a crow?
No, you are a phoenix.
Thank you, Ms. San.
-Extra! The water shortage worsens!
-Tiger, I'll take one.
Here, catch!
Here.
Extra! Donghai…
-Be careful!
-Mrs. Liu.
-Mr. Cheng.
-Six.
You are back early.
Six!
-Thank you, Six!
-Do you know how to kick?
Six, good timing,
take this too.
Sure.
SPEEDY COURIERS
The four clans own this place.
Everyone knows their word is the law.
Imagine working for them.
Easy money and status too.
-Yunxiang, are you fixing it up?
-Not smuggling like us.
-I'm just adding in some bits.
-Six, give me a hand.
-I'm coming!
-Liang, I won't work for them.
-To the warehouse.
-Once outlaws come clean,
some die, and others run,
but it's always a bad ending.
You have to be given that chance first.
Have you seen those guys in the clans?
You see a dragon's head
and never see its tail.
That's just sour grapes.
Who would smuggle
if you could go the legal way?
What are you talking about?
We have nothing to do with the clans.
-Boss.
-We smuggle
-to survive in a waterless world.
-Yes.
Being able to put food on the table
is good enough.
-Right?
-Sure.
-That's if it is enough to survive.
-Come and get the goods.
-Get the goods.
-Take it up to Song territory.
Okay.
For you two.
Yunxiang, this is for you.
It's risky lately. Stay calm.
I'm off.
I've never been to other cities,
but I know
all cities are the same.
Just different people in different places.
In some places, it's so green
like each leaf was soaked in water.
But in other places…
Water!
Come on, give me some.
Spare me some money.
That's it for today.
-Go home.
-Sir.
I have water coins.
Can't you give me a few drops?
What did I say?
Come back tomorrow.
It shouldn't be like this.
Yet it has always been this way.
-However, it's the only world we have.
-It has always been this kind of world
Same air
Different fates
Begin to feel
Don't live in this kind of world
DE WATER INDUSTRY
Starting today
We live in this kind of world
NO ENTRY
Over there!
Be who you are
-There's water!
Yunxiang, how did it go yesterday?
-They increased the patrols.
-We can't do this.
It's getting tougher all the time.
You want a decent living,
but there are no easy jobs.
-You have no choice.
-Where should I put this?
There's a kitten!
-A kitten?
-Six, where did it come from?
I'm not sure about it,
but there's a delivery address.
We should put a sign to tell people
we are a fake courier service.
Contraband only. That's it.
-Should we just throw it?
-Don't do that.
I'll deliver it.
Someone didn't want it,
so they gave a fake address
and threw it our way.
Handle it yourself.
Fake address.
Okay. You may go.
See, you don't need an owner.
There's no one bossing you around.
You are lucky!
It's a big world.
You'll be fine on your own.
Go. Hurry up and leave.
Sending a tiny cat,
like you, into the world
is indeed crazy.
PALACE OF HAPPINESS
PALACE OF HAPPINESS, NIGHTCLUB
Ms. San.
Such a big world
So many places
A free spirit like me
Could linger anywhere
Such a big world
So many young men
A free spirit like me
Could find love anywhere
There's a place
I cannot go
There's a young man
I can't even say hello to
That place is home
That man is you
But young man
What do you know?
Life and death go on
Flowers bloom and fade
But young man
Why are you hesitant?
Flowers will bloom again
Youth comes only once
But young man
Why are you hesitant?
What do you know?
Yunxiang, what are you doing here?
Why? Am I not allowed to come?
Don't mess up my hair.
Why is it a small crowd tonight?
Someone sabotaged the sluice gates.
They say that until he is found,
there will be no more water. So--
Is this for me?
-Yes.
-It's such a cute kitten!
What made you think of this?
Are you delivering again?
If Old Li finds out he will be pissed.
Only I can call him "Old Li."
Speaking of Old Li,
let's have dinner there tonight.
Last time, you had a fight
and said you wouldn't see him again.
-You are using me as an excuse.
-Cut it out!
-I'm driving.
-How will you thank me?
This building will do.
It's higher than
the second building by 20 stories.
Won't the other three clans
build a building too?
They are too busy
fighting with each other.
Their finances are a mess.
Dad says to keep the people in line.
You can't let them get too comfortable.
Full bellies
foster random thoughts.
-Donghai lacks water.
-Let's go.
-From lack comes the need.
-Okay.
Grasp what they need,
and you will rule over them.
-Your dad knows human nature.
-Okay.
Controlling the water
-means controlling Donghai.
-Follow us.
Nice motorcycle.
Nice car.
He's the third son
of the De Group's owner.
Really?
Sell him the motorcycle.
State your price,
our master will give it to you.
Old Li, it's us!
I'm back.
Kasha, you haven't visited in ages.
-Well, I'm here now.
-Look at you, calling him "Old Li."
Jinxiang, are you the cook tonight?
Forget it. You boys have a good chat.
I'll cook.
Jinxiang, why are you here today?
Anti-Smuggling Bureau
busted another smuggling ring.
I had to deliver the report.
The place was close by.
How have you been?
Is your courier job still going well?
-It's still the same.
-Hand me a Number 5 wrench.
Okay.
Yesterday someone broke
the sluice gates of the city.
Distribution has been halted
while authorities investigate.
Enough with the bad news.
The bastard is causing trouble
for all of us.
If I find him,
I will break his legs.
You can pour yours, Yunxiang.
Dad, a toast to you.
Amidst the chaos and taxes,
we are not rich, but not poor either.
In any case,
it's better to have a proper job.
-Here is the soup!
-All right.
Here, Dad.
Have some soup.
The bureau still has water
so I brought you two buckets.
Otherwise, there'd be
no dinner tonight.
The soup is delicious.
Our area is under De Clan.
We are in the best shape economically.
Elsewhere, it's chaos.
People are living precariously.
The De Clan is tough but meticulous.
Life isn't easy,
but we make ends meet.
I'm not worried about you.
Shady business never ends well.
I've had enough.
Old Li is just worried about you.
Worried, my ass.
Cats have better lives.
They have no one to nag them.
You can live your own life.
Come on.
You have a dad and a brother.
I wish my folks were still alive
to nag me every day.
I won't mind if they scold me either.
Kasha is right.
You know what Dad is like.
The De Clan sent down orders
to clamp down hard on smuggling.
Be careful with the stuff you do.
You know that our bureau
practically works for them.
I'm off.
It can't last.
-Get out while you can.
-Goodbye, Jinxiang!
Someone is following us.
I like
this motorcycle.
I like it too.
Whatever it is that I like, I will get.
Not this time.
I'm not giving it to you.
Hold on tight.
Kasha--
Try and run now.
Do you think what's yours is yours?
As long as I want it,
it is mine.
Third Prince.
-Master.
-Let's go.
Yes, Boss.
I think it's him.
I know.
It has been so many years.
Yes,
a wall of red flame.
If it's really him,
it's your son
who provoked him again.
Nurse, this medicine is spilled.
I'll change it for you right away.
-That patient is improving.
-Keep him under observation.
-Doctor, his fever is gone.
-Monitor him. I'll see him later.
Dr. Su, please sign here.
-Water's short. Use it sparingly.
-Okay.
Come, I'll give you an injection.
It's you.
Why are you--
I'm Su Junzhu, a doctor here.
How did I get here?
A masked man brought you in last night.
I was on duty.
Don't move. You are badly injured--
How did it heal so quickly?
What is it?
Kasha!
Where is she?
When she arrived,
it was already too late to save her leg.
She is still not out of danger.
CIJI HOSPITAL
DE GROUP
DONGHAI AUDIT
Why are you outside?
-You look okay.
-I am okay.
How's Kasha?
Kasha…
The De Clan?
Hey, that's…
That's Boss De.
I apologize on behalf of my son.
Young men can be wild.
He has done wrong against you.
Please forgive him.
He has offended you.
We respectfully return your motorcycle.
Here's a small token of respect.
Kindly accept this gesture
and let us move on.
Boss De,
this is so--
You--
If you want to apologize,
give me your son's leg.
Boss De, I'm so sorry.
My little brother has a bad temper.
I'll try and talk to him.
Boss,
is it really him?
It might just be someone
with a superpower,
but it might also be him.
In every reincarnation,
it's the same story.
But why?
It's the Will of Heaven.
You can't fight it.
It must play out, cycle after cycle.
Before he is fully awakened,
let's get rid of him.
Just like the last few times.
The plan is in place.
They are onto him.
Don't be like that.
Boss De is such a big man to be so polite.
Do you know what happened to Kasha's leg?
Yes, I know.
The doctor phoned me.
All that gold
could buy her the best treatment
and she will be set for life.
What can people like us do?
Donghai City is like that.
Why can't you accept reality?
It's because I can't!
It's up to you to accept
but think of Kasha.
What about her future?
Also, it's all because--
-Jinxiang, hop on!
-Okay!
Jinxiang, quick!
CLIFF! DANGER!
The cliff!
-Who are these monsters?
-Move!
Do it.
Down!
I love the smell of grilled fish
in the morning.
Who are they? Who are you?
Nezha, you are--
a scatterbrain.
What did you call me?
We know each other, Nezha.
Me calling him "Nezha"
makes you excited, right?
It must have shocked him.
See you later!
Doctor! Dr. Su!
-Hurry!
Take him to surgery!
Move!
Who are these monsters?
-Who are you?
-I live here, Nezha.
Our total defeat
doesn't surprise me.
Dad, even if he has special powers,
I started this,
so I should finish it.
You will, will you?
Dad, he hurt you too?
Yes, he did.
Me, the Dragon King of East Sea.
It has been 3,000 years
and it's still not healed.
He is crazy.
Full of magical powers and violence.
He would kill both god and demon.
Gender and relations won't matter.
He would even kill his own dad.
He is
Nezha.
You came.
Why do you call me Nezha?
Because that's who you are.
Let me ask you.
When you were a kid, did your dad ever
tell the story of Nezha and Dragon King?
Of course I know the story.
Well, you are that
chaos-creating,
sea-churning,
insufferably arrogant Nezha!
You are Nezha!
A bachelor has to do everything himself.
What was I saying?
-That I'm Nezha.
-Right.
Each reincarnation
means a new name and identity,
parents, family, friends,
and all the normal mess of life.
Do you have a girlfriend?
Do you?
Boss De is the Dragon King of East Sea.
His son, that little bastard is
the Dragon King's Third Prince, Ao Bing.
So in past lives, he killed me.
Your dad used all his powers
to forge you a steel dragon spine
and bring you back to life.
But the injury
wiped your memory of past lives.
Three thousand years ago,
the four Dragon Kings
stopped fighting each other
so that united, we could make him
kill himself in the atonement.
Who knew that after his death,
his soul evaded Heaven's dragnet
and reincarnated again and again.
The one beside Li Jing in Heaven
is just a clay effigy, a fake Nezha.
The real Nezha
has escaped.
So for 3,000 years,
we have kept an eye on Donghai.
Anyone who appears
to be his reincarnation,
we will kill him.
It's better to kill in error
than take chances.
My luck is good today.
Let's drink this one.
The flames from my body
and that huge shadowy figure behind me.
They're all…
That's his original god-body.
You are Nezha reborn, my dear brother!
Cut it out. Come drink.
Nezha was born with that fire
hardcore, tough as steel.
But once released…
My goodness.
Not even you can control it.
See?
That fire of his scares even me.
If I'm Nezha, who are you then?
Me?
I'm not going to tell you.
This time his awakening is more powerful.
Don't provoke him.
If I don't take revenge,
I'm not Dragon King's Third Prince!
Shut up.
Leave.
I--
My Dragon Pearl is still powering up.
It's not time yet.
I'll hire someone
to take him out.
The pillars of the Heavens
are collapsing.
-The world is falling apart.
-"My god-body"? "Uncontrollable"?
Who is he kidding?
You want someone killed?
Old pal,
you have worked for me before.
Don't act so surprised.
This fish looks familiar.
It's cooked now. Have some.
You were there.
Sure, I was passing by.
He is just a kid.
What's the big deal?
Besides, you have plenty of men
and I'm expensive.
He is Nezha.
Ao Guang.
You really have a problem.
You couldn't tell he was Nezha?
There are others who use fire too.
For example, the Fire Imp.
But if it's really that killer, Nezha,
I'm no match for him.
You concealed your identity and powers.
You have plenty of tricks up your sleeve.
Yaksa, you know a lot of things.
But if you know so much,
why do you always get beaten up?
We all have our roles.
Mine is to get beaten up,
yours is to hide.
Still,
if your enemy comes knocking,
you can turn yourself into a rat,
but they will still find you.
A rat…
Good idea!
A rat!
You know,
the old Order of the Gods is meaningless.
A new one will arise sooner or later.
Then, the Chan and Jie factions
will battle to death once again.
No one gets to keep their hands clean.
Where will you hide then?
Help me now
and we will look after you then.
Goodbye, old pal.
Will he do it?
He always agrees if the price is right.
These demons
are only after profits.
Be patient.
Don't worry. He is in here.
-I--
-Get out.
-Father--
-Admit you're wrong!
-It's not my fault!
-You are a bad seed!
Fire!
-Fire!
-Bring the fire extinguisher!
-Hurry!
Call for help to put out the fire!
Dr. Su, there's a fire down here.
Over there!
Hey!
Will you be my teacher?
No.
Don't you want me
to modify a motorcycle for you?
I'll help you.
Just teach me how to control the fire.
A motorcycle cooler than yours?
It's not a problem.
Okay, but you might not
be able to learn it.
I'm telling you now.
Either way,
you have to modify my motorcycle.
Let me try.
Let's go.
You were born
with an internal god-fire.
But you are just flesh and blood now.
The fire is too fierce.
So you need some iron
to channel it outwards.
Put out the fire.
What will happen if I don't?
If you don't--
It will burn the heart
and split the skin.
Your body dies and your spirit flies away.
So you need a suit of armor
to direct your internal fire.
Once you master True Fire,
you can survive in both sea and air.
Are you sure about this?
You have to maintain your focus.
Don't let the fire control you.
I'm sorry.
What?
Keep going!
Come on.
YUN
That was fun!
Who are you really?
I am
Six-Ears Macaque.
Six-Ears Macaque?
In the legends, he tricks people.
He is not a good person.
How are you qualified to say that to me?
How much harm have you caused?
How many disasters?
How many deaths?
How many of your friends
and family got hurt?
You are the bad one, Nezha.
Who are you talking about?
It has been a long time, Nezha.
You still have a lousy temper.
Why can't I get him back?
You're not yet united
with Nezha's god-body.
So naturally, you can't just call him up.
"United"?
Listen.
Nezha was reborn as you, Li Yunxiang.
But he has been reborn many times
and will be back many more times.
Zhang Yunxiang, Zhao Yunxiang,
Wang Yunxiang, Sun Yunxiang…
But until now,
there has been no reincarnation
that's worthy of his name.
Some of them
didn't even realize they were Nezha
as their life went past.
They weren't up to it
and weren't Nezha enough.
Also,
if you want Nezha's full powers
you have to get back your Astras.
Astras?
What Astras?
Jinxiang. It's the Sky Ribbon
and Cosmic Ring.
This armor
is a bit slapdash.
Keep at it.
SPEEDY COURIERS
Your dad has arranged everything.
He is a clever strategist.
We don't move until the time is ripe
so that there are no slip-ups.
We will take whatever help we can get.
I want my revenge now.
Third Prince, if we need to attack,
leave it to me.
After all, one of the Nezhas
was killed by my hands.
Yunxiang, that's so cool.
-Let me see.
-What a poser.
Li Yunxiang.
Dr. Su, what brings you here?
I've come to tell you
your brother's on the mend.
-You should visit him.
-That's great! Thank you.
I'll leave now.
By the way,
could you fix up my motorcycle one day?
I'll never win against you then.
Is that so important?
-I can't tell.
-Exactly.
-Who is she?
-Watch out!
Yunxiang!
Six!
Bastard.
It's just a pile of scrap iron.
Scrap iron or not,
I'll kill you!
Li Yunxiang!
Get lost!
So, Third Prince,
I wanted to see you.
I was once young and naive.
I thought if I worked hard at smuggling,
I would make something of myself.
I was duped.
-Duped?
-Well,
who knew that brat Li Yunxiang
was hiding so much?
It turns out he is a big shot.
He is a hero. But what about me?
My business was ruined.
The real thing.
You know what you need to do, right?
Third Prince, I'm smart and diligent.
All I lacked was starting capital.
If my dad was rich,
I would be like you.
I have money,
but what's your life worth?
Being a traitor doesn't worry you?
What's a traitor who succeeds?
A successful man.
You can just wait and see.
That thing that appears behind him,
maybe I have one too.
Your dad's with your brother.
You should go and see him.
I'll keep watch here.
There were so many wars then.
We were fleeing from them…
when your mom got sick
and died.
I had a shoulder pole
with you in the front basket
and your younger brother in the other.
The night was dark, the hill was steep,
and the baskets were heavy.
I tripped and rolled down the hill.
I was so scared.
I scrambled back to the baskets
and saw
your brother laughing
with such joy.
He thought it was fun.
The years have passed
so quickly.
Your brother was always causing trouble.
I thought that when he grew up,
he would be more sensible.
I didn't expect him
to cause bigger troubles.
Now you too…
Your friends are all out of danger.
You can relax.
I have always wanted to be a doctor.
Because I thought
I could help a lot of people that way.
I thought I could do that.
Later, I realized
a doctor can't help everyone.
However, you can.
Me?
I bring nothing but trouble.
Don't blame yourself.
It wasn't you who hurt them.
But it was because of me.
You know,
the first time I saw you,
I knew you were different.
Cheer up.
What I saw just now
was a hero with a body of flame
and boundless powers.
-Kasha!
-Kasha.
-You need to be careful.
-I'm fine, I want to walk by myself.
You…
What are you doing?
Six.
Keep quiet.
-You'll wake people up.
-Let me go!
Who's that?
Help!
There's a murderer!
Come on! This way! Come!
Kid!
Stop it!
Help!
-Run!
-Help!
Pay your blood debt with your life,
Nezha.
There's someone here.
-Bear with it.
-Let's go over there.
-I can't.
-Don't move.
-Your wound will tear.
Li Yunxiang, hurry!
Your dad, he…
Old Li!
Doctor.
Doctor, hurry up and save him!
Hurry up and save him!
Aren't you a doctor?
Why can't you save him?
Why?
Yunxiang.
Whatever trouble
you get into in the future,
I won't nag you over it anymore.
Don't worry, we are in the hospital.
You'll be okay.
I always knew
I had
an amazing son.
Stop talking,
it will be okay.
You,
together with your friends,
your brother,
and yourself…
Don't talk.
Old Li, don't talk.
Keep living well,
for everyone's sake.
Live…
Dad!
Where are you going?
I'm going to kill them!
There are still so many of you.
What a warm welcome.
Disgusting!
Let me see.
Dead Man's Hand.
Use the joker, dumbass.
Take a good look.
I'm underdressed.
How powerful are these beasts of mine?
Now I get it.
Donghai's water vanished in a blink
on account of these two guys.
That's because I have their pup.
They don't dare disobey.
The surging East Sea
draws on countless rivers,
taking in even the narrowest streams.
That's how it grows.
Brilliant.
So brilliant.
I asked you to my humble home
to ask about the progress of that favor.
I've been busy, but I'm onto it.
Really?
I'm very curious about one thing.
That brat has advanced so quickly
that he even beat Yaksa.
I wonder who trained him.
Maybe his internal fire was so strong,
it just came naturally.
Maybe.
But maybe you taught him.
Me?
Why would I do that?
-Impossible.
-Anything is possible.
For instance,
you fear I'll reveal your identity.
So you want him to kill me
and seal my lips.
Six-Ears Macaque.
It really is you, you demon.
So Monkey King didn't really kill you.
He really did.
Now I'm just a nameless demon with a mask.
Dragon King,
these last few years,
Donghai's fresh water sources dried up.
The river dragons in charge disappeared.
What funny business…
Six-Ears Macaque,
those six ears
really don't miss a single piece of news.
There will be a new Order of the Gods!
The Dragon Clan of East Sea
won't have its tail trod on again
and be at the bottom of the Order.
I need all that fresh water
to enhance my powers
and rule the new Order of the Gods.
The Order of the Gods…
That old nonsense.
You have brought such suffering
to the people of Donghai.
Ao Guang.
What if they sue you in Heaven's Court?
It's chaos up there right now.
No one has the time for it.
Besides, who would take me to court?
People are like grass.
They need to be pruned well.
If grass won't bend in the wind,
I will mow it down.
You're impressive and harsh!
I'm not harsh.
Why are they fighting for position?
Fighting for position?
So she is now working for you too.
Nezha has enemies
well beyond the East Sea clans.
Don't you see?
Even the red ribbons can't hold him.
In the absence of the Dragon Pearl,
we will retreat for now.
Let's go.
Useless.
Dad.
I…
I'll stop him.
My son,
don't make me lose face.
Nezha.
This time,
I won't humiliate myself
like I did in my past life.
Come on.
This will be a fight to the death.
I won't back off.
Prepare to die!
Die!
Ms. Cai Yun,
ambushes aren't nice.
Wait.
-Are you talking to me?
-Who is she?
Her? A disciple of Demoness Shiji.
You are the kiss of death.
You bring disaster wherever you go.
-Disaster?
-You arrogant piece of work.
Playing with your master's bow and arrow,
you killed my sister-in-arms
from 1,000 miles away.
You ripped out Third Prince's Dragon Spine
and harmed Chentong's innocent people.
Whatever incarnation you take,
you hurt those closest to you.
-You are the kiss of death.
-Nezha, you killed my son!
I'll drown everyone in the town!
Father, where are my Astras?
Where did you hide them?
Apologize, Nezha!
Give me back my Astras!
-You are a bad seed!
-Nezha, you are a villain.
-Apologize!
-If you don't, everyone will die!
My son, stop it!
It's not my fault!
He needs to apologize!
You!
You are a bad seed.
Dragon King,
do you want me to apologize?
-Go.
-What?
Let her go.
Go.
He is letting you go.
You will always be the kiss of death.
Nothing can change that.
If I'm the kiss of death,
why are you helping me?
I'm not helping you.
I'm helping your ancestor.
Nezha.
An earlier one than that.
We were leftover stones
from when the Goddess Nüwa
patched the sky.
You?
Six-Ears Macaque?
Actually,
I am…
Sun Wukong, the Monkey King!
Back then, I saw how useless
those Buddhist scriptures were.
They can't cure
the world's pain.
But you, the Monkey King,
proved your power in the Sky Palace.
Where there's suffering,
your Gold Cudgel could fight it.
What would that do?
Injustice is like the waves of the sea.
It comes and goes, goes and comes.
The stupid Order of the Gods.
From order to chaos
and from chaos to order.
I've been around for millennia.
I couldn't change anything.
I'm completely useless.
You are the same.
The Dragon King thinks
I'm hiding from enemies.
I'm just tired.
I don't even know
where I left my Gold Cudgel.
Li Yunxiang,
the red ribbon was your Astra.
The Sky Ribbon.
This hole leads to the East Sea.
Under a waterfall at the bottom of the sea
is a palace
of the Dragon King of East Sea.
He keeps river dragons captive there,
harnessing their strength
to empower the Dragon Pearl.
The thing about river dragons
is that they need fresh water to live.
So he stole Donghai's water.
Exactly.
Nezha's Sky Ribbon is down there,
tethering those dragons.
It's too bad, Li Yunxiang.
You can't do anything about it.
You can't use the Sky Ribbon.
You are not Nezha.
I'm not?
That kid behind you
appears when you are murderous.
But when you want to help people,
the kid is nowhere to be seen.
That scary, demon-killing,
and death-defying Nezha.
But where's the "soft heart"?
You are not Nezha.
You are not Nezha enough.
Yunxiang,
your brother woke up.
Jinxiang.
I'm so sorry.
Why are you pretending?
Six's death is on him as well.
Who knows who is next?
It's true.
I'm so sorry.
What use is that?
You upset the De Clan.
They're bound to make trouble for us.
Look. Look around this room.
There are dead
and wounded people everywhere.
Isn't it all his fault?
He is a walking disaster.
-It was you who killed Six!
-Why are you still alive--
-You are lying.
-I saw you kill Six myself!
And you sabotaged Yunxiang's armor!
So it was you.
Don't move!
Stand back!
One step forward and she is dead.
All these deaths are all because of him.
He just wants to be the big hero.
But what about us?
Kasha!
Such a big world
So many places
A free spirit like me
Could make memories anywhere
But there's a place
I cannot go
-That place is home
-I can't change anything.
Is it all useless?
That place is home
But young man
Why are you hesitant?
Flowers will bloom again
Just as they fall every year
Maybe nothing can be changed.
It's like our patients in the hospital.
Whether we cure them or not,
they will still die one day.
But if they recover,
they have more time in this world.
I'm sure that this time
isn't useless from their perspective,
or that of their family and friends.
Li Yunxiang, pull yourself together.
I also think you are a hero
with a body of flame
and boundless powers.
I know what I have to do.
I can't control the waves of the East Sea,
but I can go down to the Dragon's palace
to defeat the Dragon King
and get back the water.
So many people were born
and lived in this world.
The ones yet to be born
should still be able to live.
I'm doing this
for them.
That's enough for me.
Come out, kid.
We need to talk.
Are you really me, kid?
You look like a child,
yet we are the same person?
Listen, I'm going to save people.
Not just one person,
but the whole city.
Anyway, you don't know them.
It's a pretty lofty and abstract goal.
I assume that eons of selfish behavior
mean that you won't be helping me.
So I, Li Yunxiang,
will go on my own.
The armor is a bit crude, but it'll do.
I made it myself.
You can just hide and leave me alone.
Little punk.
He really went when I said, "Get lost."
Thank you.
You have really come to kill us all.
There's no need to hurry.
I have a special guest for you.
Yunxiang!
Dr. Su!
You are despicable.
Woman, you are only here
so I could mess with his head.
Yunxiang!
Do you think you can defeat me?
You meager ant.
I should finish you off.
-Apologize!
-Shady business never ends well.
-You are a bad seed.
-You are the kiss of death.
You bring disaster wherever you go.
-All these deaths are all because of him.
-Who are these monsters?
He is a walking disaster.
-Yunxiang…
-Yunxiang.
Li Yunxiang!
Thank you.
Do you think that's the end of it?
I haven't wasted these 3,000 years.
I've mastered the Tao of Transformation
just for this day.
Nezha,
you are forcing me
to swallow the Dragon Pearl.
This will unchain the river dragons.
As they go,
they'll stir up a giant tsunami
that will engulf
every living thing in Donghai.
You will have hurt
countless innocents again.
Hurry up!
-Run!
-Be careful!
Yunxiang.
Kid,
do you hear that noise?
It's the sound of the tsunami.
Donghai will be submerged.
You are an ordinary mortal.
Stop struggling.
Relax.
Give up.
Your fate isn't in your hands.
It's assigned by Heaven.
Let Old Man Heaven
take you back.
Let me go.
You are not Nezha.
Tiger!
Run!
It's mine.
This life that was given to me
is mine.
I don't need you
to tell me
who I am.
I'll show you!
You can't die.
You won't die.
Aren't you Nezha?
Kid.
We meet again.
I thought you left.
What are you doing here?
I did my best.
That tsunami…
Donghai…
All those people there,
can you save them?
Hey.
You…
should find your next incarnation.
-The tsunami has receded.
-Thank goodness!
-That's great!
Ms. San, is this rain?
I got my Astra back.
I am Nezha.
Don't forget to return the motorcycle.
Thank you.
He acquired the Sky Ribbon.
There should be many other Nezha's Astras.
Let's see.
Cosmic Ring,
Fire Wheel,
and Dragon Catcher.
What were the others?
The others…
In the moment of death,
I became Nezha.
-Because the first Nezha…
-Well, Yunxiang?
…he was like this too.
-Are you ready?
-He and I both know,
in this world,
-if you don't want to accept fate…
-What's this?
-…you have to fight as hard as you can.
-So cute!
In my dream
There were you and me
It never seemed real
From the beginning
When a true heart
-This is my world.
-Can't betray the power of youth anymore
This is our world.
Tomorrow, today, and yesterday's fate
I am Li Yunxiang.
-Had been decided at that moment
-I am Nezha.
NEW GODS: NEZHA REBORN
How many souls are at war?
After saying goodbye
To the confusing youth
How many still hold onto dreams?
The wind blew past the seasons
Flowers bloomed and faded again
The rain seeped into my heart
Wandering in the vast sea of people
A pure heart
Spends the entire lifetime
Pursuing a dream
A sincere person
Is willing to end with a good dream
One burns for his dream in this life
It's what he yearns for in this life
A dream comes true in this life
It comes from what the heart wants
STAY TUNED FOR POST-CREDITS SCENE
Walking through a bustling city
Slowly ignoring worldly affairs
A sigh by the window
Reveals whispered dreams in this life
Pondering under the moon
Who decides what happens in life?
The loyal heart of a child is unstoppable
Showing his ambition
Yesterday's flowers
Faded without regrets
Fallen leaves have wilted
Who else but me?
MO LIQING
AO BING
ORDER OF THE GODS
STAY TUNED FOR POST-CREDITS SCENE
Such a big world
So many places
A free spirit like me
Could linger anywhere
Such a big world
So many young men
A free spirit like me
Could find love anywhere
There's a place
I cannot go
There's a young man
I can't even say hello to
That place is home
That man is you
But young man
Why are you hesitant?
Flowers will bloom again
Youth comes only once
It has always been this kind of world
Same air
Different fates
Begin to feel
Don't live in this kind of world
Starting today
We live in this kind of world
Be who you are
Verta.
Blanca…
THE WHITE SNAKE TEAM CONTINUES
THEIR DESTINY FROM THE PAST
You'll be imprisoned forever
in Leifeng Pagoda!
Verta, persevere.
Blanca!
Can you break what destiny binds together?
I'll kill you, you stinking monk!
I'll send you to your next reincarnation!
WHITE SNAKE 2
DISASTER ENCOUNTERED
BY THE GREEN SNAKE
COMING SOON IN 2021
NEW GOD LIST: YANG JIAN
PLEASE LOOK FORWARD TO IT IN 2022