Blessed by heaven and earth,
the Chaos Pearl was born.
The Supreme Lord split it into two.
The celestial energy within became the Spirit Pearl,
while the demonic energy formed the Demon Orb.
A Wrath of Heaven curse was cast on the Demon Orb,
set to destroy it with lightning in three years.
Later, because Shen Gongbao intervened,
the Demon Orb reincarnated as Nezha, third son of Li Jing in Chentang Pass.
The Spirit Pearl became Ao Bing, third son of the Dragon King.
By fate,
the two became best friends.
Nezha, influenced by his parents,
shed his demonic nature,
and saved Chentang Pass.
Together with Ao Bing,
they faced the Wrath of Heaven,
and at last
changed their destinies.
Though you've survived the wrath,
your bodies were destroyed...
without which
the soul will soon fade into oblivion.
The Sacred Lotus protects and nurtures spirit.
I will now use it to recreate
your physical forms.
- Wow
- Stunning
Let's get to work!
Something's off...
Is it?
The lotus root must be powdered
to make your bodies.
Did you just scratch your feet with that hand?
Oh, don't worry.
My foot is Just a little sticky.
It just needs a quick wash.
I wasn't worried about your foot.
Did you just blow your nose with that hand?
No, not me.
It's just lotus powder.
See?  Lotus powder.
It's ready to go.
Here, come on.
One booger for each of you.
I mean one serving.
Chop chop! Let's save your souls!
I'd rather...
Pain the neck, you little fools!
It worked!
Hang on.
What is this?
Oh, thank you,
I've been looking all over for that.
Time for shaping.
Flying Pig's memory is unmatched,
so is his skill at carving.
Perfect recreation, right?
Thanks, Piggy.
Don't move, your body's not ready yet.
Master Immortal,
I've mobilized all of Chentang's forces
to guard Shen Gongbao and the Eastern Sea dragons.
Not to worry,
the dragons are watching the Abyss monsters,
none of which can escape.
Shen Gongbao is no threat on his own.
Take a look at this!
Isn't this incredible?
Whoa!
He learned from the best.
But,
do we have to be exactly the same?
Can't you make me look better?
Huh?
That's right.
Parents always want the best for their kids, right?
Right.
Make me tall and hunky.
Also hauntingly handsome
A man must be strong and striking,
as well as demure and mindful.
But also cute and lovable.
Can you just make up your minds?
Tall and hunky,
With a touch of handsomeness.
Strong and striking.
Yet super adorable.
What's this?
He says... "Get to work, then"
Right!
I should've taken over earlier.
DIY is always the best.
This could take awhile.
Let's finish you first.
You were born of the water element,
so you must be tempered by pure water.
Open Lotus!
There we go.
Are you finished?
Almost...
This version is surely the most dazzling,
but fine-tuning will take a long time.
How about we just use the first one for now?
Yeah, the first version will do.
I agree.
Right.
You were born of the fire element,
so you must be refined in pure flame.
Sir!
An enemy has been spotted at sea.
It seems to be Shen Gongbao.
How many are with him?
Just him.
What shall we do?
Carry on with your spell.
We'll handle the intruder.
Master Immortal,
let me go plead with my master.
Don't move!
Until another incense stick is fully burnt,
your body won't be ready.
Shen Gongbao,
to what do we owe this honor?
Now that you know of my plan with the dragons,
I can't help but feel un...uneasy.
Chentang Pass is heavily guarded,
and Master Taiyi is within the city.
You, alone, can't accomplish much.
Who... who said I'm alone?
[Two hours ago, Dragon Palace]
If they find out about the Spirit Pearl,
not only will you fail to avenge your son,
[Queen of Western Sea]
but the entire Eastern Dragon Clan
[Dragon King of Eastern Sea]
will bear the blame.
When the truth comes out,
you'll be cast into the abyss of purgatory,
[Dragon King of Southern Sea]
surrounded by all your old "friends".
Let's see how they welcome you.
Let's see how we welcome you.
[Dragon King of Northern Sea]
Stuck as you are in Dragon Palace...
How could you avenge your son?
Even I feel nervous for you.
You fools are in no place to gloat.
I was simply trying to help.
But it seems that you
don't appreciate it.
Hmm?
You must've forgotten what I'm capable of.
Ah!
I know this one.
The Sky... Sky... Sky...
Sky Splitting Claw.
Thank you.
Master Shen can take this claw to Chentang Pass,
and use it to tear open a rift leading back to me.
The Abyss Monsters can then help you destroy your enemy.
[Sky-Splitting Thunder Whip]
The Abyss Monsters
How... is that possible?
They've been trapped by the Suppression Seal for a thousand years,
how could they possibly escape?
The dragons... have they already released them?
Even with the Sea-Stabilizing Chains binding us,
and no way to escape,
this tactic will guarantee victory.
What do you say, my brother?
Surely you wouldn't help out of generosity
Get to the point.
What's your price?
In this purgatory,
where flames burn our bodies,
every day feels like a year.
If you could lower the lava's heat a little,
to ease our suffering,
we'd serve you with all our might.
What's going on?
What is Shen Gongbao up to now?
Finally, we're out! Yay!
Bye-bye!
Vile.
We're doomed.
How will we explain this to General Li now?
Luckily no one saw us.
Here.
What's this for?
I'll break your arms
and then you break my legs.
We'll say the Yaksha did it.
Oh.
When the general sees how badly we're hurt,
he won't blame us.
Give it your best shot.
Hit me hard!
Hey!
Hey, you two!
Master Immortal,
you're here!
Hee hee hee!
Ha ha ha!
He let the Yaksha get away!
What?
It was all your fault.
Who are you to point fingers?
Who are you to play innocent?
Oh my,
Dumb and Dumber!
Hey!
You two boneheads!
Get over here and guard me!
Yes, Sir! Right away!
Show no mercy.
Shen Gongbao!
Ao Bing is not dead.
Chentang Pass and the dragons will not fight when they learn of this.
Taiyi is rebuilding Ao Bing's body right now.
Liar!
Hmm?
The shield...
No!
Master!
Ao Bing!
Master Taiyi has built me a new body.
Cease fire! Please!
Shen Gongbao,
I saved your disciple.
How will you thank me?
So,
that must be Nezha in there.
Why, you ungrateful scumbag!
Master!
They must die!
Ha ha ha!
You think you can break this shield?
Hit me! Come on!
No!
That aura...
Ao Bing!
Father!
[Ao Guang]
I failed the mission to save our kind.
No.
None of that matters.
I just want you to be safe.
As long as you're here,
that's enough for me.
Open Lotus!
Your body, what is wrong...
Please, he's literally a newborn.
How could he take a hit like that?
Ao Bing!
Wait! You're not ready yet!
Don't move! Don't move!
Ao Bing, what's going on?
Never move before your body's finished!
If your body exceeds its limit,
it will collapse!
For heaven's sake...
Fatty!
Make another bod... body for Ao Bing, now!
Huh?
Making two bodies back-to-back
has completely drained the Sacred Lotus's energy.
Without a body, won't his soul scatter?
Master, do something!
Without the Sacred Lotus,
there's nothing I can do.
It's okay.
I took your place as the Spirit Pearl. I deserve this.
If my sacrifice
can bring you back to life,
then it's a fair price to pay.
Nobody asked for your help!
I was happy being the Demon Orb.
Don't you dare die!
Father,
please spare Chentang Pass.
We should stop making these terrible mistakes.
This is my final wish.
There has to be some other way.
There has to be.
You! Try harder!
Let Ao Bing share your body for now.
Share your body.
Two souls sharing one body,
rejection is inevitable.
The Spirit Pearl and Demon Orb come from the same source.
Sharing one body
for seven days shouldn't be a problem.
That's it!
Ao Bing, come over!
Quick!
Okay.
This feels... strange...
Ao Bing, are you here?
Yes, I am.
I can hear your voice in my head!
This is fun!
But this is only a temporary fix.
What happens after seven days?
There's a potion in the vault of Yu Xu Palace, Elixir Reparo.
It can restore the divine power of magical items.
With it,
the Sacred Lotus will bloom again.
But how will you obtain it?
I'll go to the Supreme Lord himself and beg for it.
Or are you planning to
report on me and the dragons?
The Supreme Lord wouldn't say... save a son of the dragons.
If asking doesn't work,
then we'll just take it.
Yu Xu Palace is at the core of the Chan Sect,
protected by formidable powers.
For my son,
I'll break into the Court of Heaven if I have to.
Your Majesty, calm down.
I might have a plan.
Chan disciples who excel in their training
can participate in the Ascension Trial.
Passing the trial grants not only immortality,
but also the right to choose one
ma... magic item from the Yu Xu Vault as a reward.
Are you suggesting
Nezha should participate in the trial
to obtain the elixir?
No, no, no!
He's beaming with demonic energy!
As soon as he uses his powers, he'll be exposed!
Isn't Ao Bing sharing Nezha's body?
His divine aura can completely mask the demonic energy.
As long as he passes the trial within seven days,
not only will we have the el... elixir...
But he will also
become immortal.
Then I wouldn't be a demon anymore?
This will save both Ao Bing and Nezha.
Eve... everyone is happy.
That wouldn't be right.
Then what do you suggest?
Follow the rules.
Come clean with the Supreme Lord
and trust his judgment.
My wife and I will also plead for mercy,
so the sins of the parents don't affect the children.
Mere mortals,
you have only decades of life experience,
how dare you lecture me about morality?
I've lived for thousands of years.
Let me tell you one truth and one truth only.
If my son dies,
Chentang Pass dies with him.
Stop!
Ao Bing is my friend.
Of course I will save him!
But if you think of harming Chentang Pass,
I'll smash your Dragon Palace
into P.I.E.C.E.S!
Except for Nezha and Taiyi,
no one leaves Chentang Pass from now on.
If in seven days I don't see Elixir Reparo,
or if the news of my clan gets out,
I'll let Chentang Pass
sink forever.
I don't trust my siblings,
and I can't stay out of my body for long.
The fate of Chentang Pass
is in your hands.
Yes.
Exactly.
There's no message that can't be conveyed
with just a nod.
Lord Li,
we're all here to say goodbye to Young Master Nezha.
We want to thank him for saving the entire city.
You're too kind.
My son has caused enough trouble
over the years.
We always knew the Young Master was destined for greatness.
Look at him,
a wide forehead,
broad face,
prominent nose,
full cheeks and thick lips.
All signs of a true hero!
I've never been wrong in reading faces.
Young Master, remember to brush your teeth after meals!
Boss!
the Demon Slayers is now re-branded as the Nezha Gang.
All members will follow your orders.
Young Master, want to practice calligraphy?
I'm here for you!
Young Master, you're three years old now.
It's time to get a girlfriend.
Would you like to learn an instrument?
We're proficient in all of them.
I want to
play shuttlecock.
What?
It's fun.
Anyone?
I'll play with you.
Didn't you always want to play shuttlecock with me?
Well...
he's a bit rough with his kicks.
Ha ha ha!
I'm a general of war!
Dad.
That's my boy!
How about...
we do it another day?
Nonsense!
Why stop when you're having fun?
It's fine. I'm fine.
I'll join too!
My lady, you don't have to do this.
Are you looking down on me?
I'm also a general of war!
Nezha,
catch this!
Kiddo,
how did you miss that?
If only I weren't the Demon Orb...
What was that?
Nothing.
It's time to go.
Before you go,
will you give your mother
a big hug?
Please, people are watching.
Wait.
Here are some snacks I made.
For you and your master on the road.
Okay, okay.
We need to go.
Hey!
I'm not on board yet!
Your body isn't fully fixed.
Don't use too much force.
Okay, okay.
And watch your temper.
Try to stay calm out there.
Without me and your father by your side,
take care of yourself.
You silly child.
What's wrong with just a hug?
It's too cringey.
It's not a farewell anyway.
Let's move.
Why are you sighing?
Does it taste bad?
Food, food, food.
All you know is food.
Look at me,
I'm too worried to even eat!
Have you thought about how to pass the trial?
What is the trial anyway?
It'll test the progress of your cultivation.
In front of the judges,
you must defeat, barehanded,
three demon kings of earth-monster level.
Fighting...
That's my specialty!
But as soon as you give off demonic energy,
your identity will be exposed.
Just let Ao Bing control my body.
His divine energy
will be just as powerful.
Sounds easy.
Let's try.
Nezha,
fully relax your body.
Let Ao Bing take control and fight me.
Ao Bing, what are you doing?
Steady!
When a soul inhabits another body,
unless its willpower is much stronger than the host's,
it won't be able to fully take control.
Nezha, back off and relax.
The harder you push,
the less Ao Bing can control.
Use your leg!
Sweep him, sweep him!
Don't panic!
I'm coming...
for you.
Having fun, eh?
We're almost at Yu Xu Palace,
and you're still messing around.
Look at yourself,
what kind of mentor are you?
Stand here and reflect on your mistakes.
No meals until you figure it out!
You're a grown man.
Stop acting like a reckless teenager.
I got it!
The Sleepy-Slumber Pill.
What's that?
Take this, and you'll fall asleep immediately.
Once you're asleep,
Ao Bing can fully control your body.
Brilliant!
One is enough!
Should've told me...
earlier.
Perfect.
Master Taiyi?
Now this feels like the real deal.
What's wrong?
Don't worry.
I see you've completely taken over Nezha's body.
Let's go again.
This time, I won't hold back.
You'd better give it your all, too.
I humbly seek your guidance.
Not bad.
You're barely able to match my skills.
Master Taiyi,
your nose is bleeding.
Oh, it's been too hot recently.
I need more water.
No big deal.
Kunlun Mountain! We're here.
I heard that a day here
is the same as a year in the mortal world.
Don't worry.
We're not in the celestial realm yet.
But all these people?
They've all come to seek immortality.
The Chan sect is famous across the world,
and everyone wants to join.
Look at this.
The jasper.
It's a credential of a Chan Sect immortal.
With it,
you'll receive respect everywhere you go.
I'm telling ya.
Being an immortal is amazing.
Both of your brothers have ascended.
You'll have no problem either.
I mean Nezha's brothers.
His two brothers
are among the best of the third generation disciples.
You know how...
Nezha always misbehaves, right?
That's why I often tell stories about his brothers
to serve as a good example for him.
Let me tell you something,
Nezha idolizes his brothers.
Oh wow, you're lucky
to see the famous Demon Hunters.
Demon Hunters?
They roam the land, hunting down
demons that wreak havoc on humanity,
keeping the world at peace.
The current leader of the Demon Hunters
is the top disciple of Immortal Wuliang.
Wasn't his predecessor Shen Gongbao?
[Yu Xu Palace]
Master Taiyi,
what's that smoke over there?
Oh.
That's the most precious treasure of Yu Xu Palace.
The Tianyuan Cauldron.
Brother Taiyi.
[Immortal Wuliang]
It been so long!
Brother Wuliang!
I heard that during Master's seclusion,
you've been in charge of Yu Xu Palace.
I've brought my disciple to attempt the Ascension Trial.
Nezha,
Pay respect to Master Wuliang.
Master Wuliang.
So, you're Nezha?
The reincarnation of the Spirit Pearl?
Oh my!
How remarkable!
The Supreme Lord has great expectations for you.
And you sure don't disappoint.
Look at him.
So full of robust vitality,
giving off a righteous vibe.
The boy's been over-training lately.
His state is a bit unstable.
What do you think you're doing?
This is Yu Xu Palace!
I need to pee!
Crana!
Here!
[Crana]
Take the child to the restroom.
Restroom?
I didn't say anything about resting.
Idiot!
Restroom
is where you pee.
The boy's a bit rough.
Please forgive him.
Wow!
So white!
Is the entire palace made of jade?
Where did they get so much money to buy jade?
The "Yu" in Yu Xu Palace means jade, right?
Then what does the "Xu" mean?
Humble?
Guilty?
Or emptiness?
Is the restroom also made of jade?
Even immortals need to pee, don't they?
Does Immortal Wuliang also poop?
This is a place of cultivation.
Lower your voice.
How much further is the toilet?
I can't hold it anymore.
Hey, sister, wait for me!
You!
I didn't mean it.
I need to change my skirt.
Go by yourself.
But I don't know where the toilet is.
Go through the corridor, turn right, then left.
Oh.
Wow.
It's so fancy!
Radical!
Weird.
Am I lost?
Where are you going?
Oh.
I got lost.
Follow me.
Brother, you've done a good job raising the Spirit Pearl.
Another great achievement for the Sect.
Not at all.
It's all thanks to Master's guidance.
This Kunlun Dew is a rare elixir.
Normally, it takes six months to fill a basin.
But today, when I sent someone to check,
it was already full!
Your timing couldn't be better.
Brother,
luck sure favors you, doesn't it?
What's wrong with you?
Can't even drink water properly.
My disciple is a bit crude.
Please forgive him.
My pee is in the water.
My master is a bit crude, too.
Please forgive him.
Brother,
time is of the essence.
I think Nezha should go through the trial immediately.
Why the rush?
Let's finish our drinks first.
No, no thank you.
Alright, then.
My disciple Deero will be the judge.
The next target of the Demon Hunters
can be captured by Nezha.
Brother, excuse us.
Taiyi, my brother,
always so impatient.
The taste of the Dew this year
is especially rich.
Keep using this method in the future.
Yes, master.
Why have you stopped?
It's been six hours,
Master Shen.
We're too tired to continue.
Rubbish!
Cultivation allows no laziness.
Without my permission
you do not stop!
General Li Jing of Chentang Pass is here to see you.
Master Shen,
yesterday's battle
left many soldiers and civilians of Chentang Pass injured.
We've run out of medicine.
I humbly ask you to open a path
so that a few doctors can leave the city to buy supplies.
How bold!
No wonder you're...
Who did that?
You son of a...
I...
St... stop, stop, stop!
Bring me the one
you caught earlier.
He escaped the city during the battle.
General Li, please,
take him ba... back with you.
This is a misunderstanding, Master Shen!
I'm a demon too!
I captured this Yaksha
to clear my son's name.
Now that it's settled,
and since he hasn't done anything worse,
just let him go.
Yes, exactly.
I'm a nobody.
Insignificant.
I don't think you understood me.
No one leaves here, not even a demon.
Let alone humans.
Master Shen, please have mercy.
I'm a demon, too.
We are both villains!
Pfft!
I'm n... not a villain.
Everyone who knows the secret of the Spirit Pearl
must stay here.
Without medicine,
the injured won't survive.
Master Shen, please,
I'm only asking to save lives.
Sir!
We caught a spy.
This creature came from outside the city,
and injured some of our soldiers.
Lock... lock him up too.
Brother.
Brother, is that you?
You...
Brother, it's me!
[Shen Xiaobao]
Xiaobao?
You haven't been home for centuries.
I missed you so much.
What are you doing here?
Father sent me to find you.
Look,
the compass you gave me.
It tells me where you are.
Father,
how is he doing?
He's great.
Ever since you entered Yu Xu Palace,
father's been full of energy,
like he took some miracle tonic.
You are the only one from our village to ever
to make it as a Chan Sect immortal.
Now, demons from miles around
are pouring in to train with father.
By the way,
why are you here?
Didn't you promise me before,
once I had achieved human form,
you'd get me into Yu Xu Palace?
Look!
I can turn into a human now!
All these years, I've trained so hard,
and never slacked off.
You're my role model, big brother.
Glory to Yu Xu, answering heaven's call.
Travel the world, bringing justice to all.
Say, brother,
what are you doing here?
I... I...
Are these sea monsters your subordinates?
Why are you surrounding Chentang Pass?
Well, about that...
Th... this is...
Master Shen is defending Chentang Pass.
Huh?
Evil forces invaded the city.
Master Shen and the sea clan came to our aid.
On behalf of my people,
thank you for this noble act.
Don't mention it.
Wow!
Brother, you're incredible!
Is this the demon attacking Chentang Pass?
Ah!
You are a disgrace to all demons!
Shame on you!
Hey,
Xiaobao,
can you
wait a few more years
before going to Yu Xu Palace?
Huh?
Why?
I can transform into a human now!
It's just that...
I'm preparing for my promotion to the Twelve Golden Immortals,
so I can't be distracted.
Twelve Golden Immortals?
Once it's done,
I'll take you there,
okay?
No problem, brother!
Your promotion is more important.
I can go to Yu Xu Palace anytime.
Besides,
I haven't quite mastered the shape-shifting.
I'll go back and practice some more.
Practice more.
Xiaobao,
this is what I have saved up since entering the Palace.
What is it?
Yu Xu Palace gives all disciples these immortality pills.
Take one
and you ga... gain ten years' worth of cultivation.
But...
this is too precious.
Brother, you're training for a promotion.
You should keep them.
I don't like how they taste.
I prefer cultivating my own.
You... you take them back.
Share them with the family.
No, I can't.
Father will blame me.
Xiaobao,
are you not obeying your big brother?
Take the pills and leave now.
This is the front line.
If... if you stay,
I'll be distracted.
Then...
I...
I'll leave.
Brother.
You must make it into the Twelve Golden Immortals.
I'll keep training!
I appreciate your help,
but the stakes are too high
for me to let anyone through.
This Yaksha...
you... you take him back, too.
I wasn't helping you.
I was helping the young one.
A good role model
can change his life.
Wait.
Le... leave me a list of medicines you need.
[Level 1: Bandits Hill]
I am Nezha, the Third Prince bold.
I slay the demons, I write in rhyme untold.
Today I come to rid the evil's breath.
You wicked fiends, prepare for death!
Still eating?
You are doomed!
Ahhh!
Who do you think you are?
Barging into our Bandits Hill?
So you're in charge?
Come forward
and have a taste of my power.
You arrogant spoiled brat.
Boss,
teach him a lesson.
Show me what you got.
You go.
No, but, boss...
how dare I steal your thunder?
Fighting a child is just embarrassing.
When I say go, you go.
Hey, k-k-kid.
Since you're young and naive,
I'm willing to let this slide.
You, you...
It's still not too late to run home to mommy.
What's wrong?
Why are you awake again?
I don't know.
I'm a light sleeper.
All that shaking has jolted me awake.
Darn it.
He took too much of that pill
and now he's immune.
Increase the dose then.
If you insist to stay, you might get hurt.
I was going to dodge to the right.
Sorry, I thought it was left.
So weak.
Master Taiyi.
Maybe I should cut in.
He could use a few more years' training.
Not so fast.
He was just teasing the demon.
The boy likes to...
play dumb.
Pills.
I need pills.
I gave you a warning.
Now you know who you're messing with.
Oh no!
The pills have dissolved in the soup!
Then I'll drink the soup.
And you're trying to steal our soup?
This calls for a beating.
So gross.
Super Mighty Club Strike!
See!
I told you he was pretending.
I wasn't paying attention.
Impossible!
You suck!
Step aside!
Watch me kick his butt.
Why did you spit it all out?
The taste is too strong.
I couldn't help it.
Check this out!
Funny!
This isn't working.
We can't win without the pill.
Deero is watching.
I can't give you the pill.
What do we do now?
I got it.
There is another way.
You're not suggesting...
We can eat the puke.
But,
it's disgusting.
What's the big deal?
I've drank Yaksha booger before.
That explains a lot.
No pain,
no gain.
That's how Nezha defeats fate.
The lives of my parents and friends are at stake,
and the people of Chentang Pass too.
This is E-A-S-Y P-E-A-S-Y!
Ignoring prejudice,
and overcoming inner fears,
I will change my destiny.
I've kept a low profile
until today's show.
Master Taiyi...
I'll save Nezha first.
Then we'll figure out a way to get Elixir Reparo.
No way.
I don't believe this.
Kid,
let's go another round.
Fake death?
I'll smash you!
Good thing Nezha got knocked out.
You do suck!
Let me avenge you!
Invincible Whirlwind Punch!
Ahhh!
Do we have to catch them all?
Even leaving one behind
could harm the people here.
Take them all back to Yu Xu Palace.
The Sect will guide them to the right path,
turning evil to good.
Your face...
No biggie.
He's sometimes ugly, sometimes handsome.
Spirit Pearl, you know,
not like normal people.
Be more careful next time.
You scared my soul out.
Who's this kid?
Nezha, possibly.
Jinzha and Muzha's younger brother.
He's the Spirit Pearl reincarnation appointed by the Supreme Lord.
But his looks aren't much, huh?
Hunched back.
Wobbly pace.
Sinking brows and drooping eyes.
Rude face.
Not to mention the dark eye circles.
He's like a ghost.
Don't stir up trouble now.
Brother,
Six stars in alignment,
what's the star sign tonight?
once in a decade.
Whenever six stars align,
this Jade Podium can transmit sound and images across thousands of miles.
Though our brothers are scattered all over the world,
we can finally gather together.
Tonight is the night,
the Golden Immortals shall meet.
I haven't ascended to the Twelve yet.
Maybe I shouldn't be included.
It's only a matter of time.
No la, no la.
It's not appropriate at all.
I can't do it, really.
Then why are you sitting up there?
Shut up!
Would it kill you to see your master thrive?
A sauna!
Shh!
Brothers and sisters, I humbly welcome you back to your places.
Greetings, Brother Wuliang!
Allow me to introduce a new member.
Brother Taiyi.
He has fulfilled the master's expectations.
and successfully nurtured
the Spirit Pearl reincarnated.
Pay your respect.
The Deification War is imminent.
We are here to discuss the preparation.
[Immortal Guangcheng]
Chan Sect is the orthodox of Tao,
so we're destined to win.
[Immortal Chijing]
But as Jie Sect has risen rapidly these years,
we must remain vigilant.
[Immortal Ju Liu Sun]
Jie sect,
is where furry and horned beasts gather
and creatures born of mucus and eggs.
This war concerns the survival of our sect.
[Immortal Huanglong]
We must be careful.
Strengthening our power
[Immortal Huanglong]
is the key.
Precisely,
That's why I began preparing early.
Immortality pills,
a total of nine thousand,
could be allocated according to merit.
This will definitely boost our strength.
[Immortal Daoheng]
How are there so many?
For a hundred years,
our master has tirelessly refined pills using the Tianyuan Cauldron,
working day and night,
at the cost of his own cultivation.
[Immortal Lingbao]
Brother Wuliang has dedicated himself to building our sect,
his contributions are to be praised.
Aye, aye.
[Immortal Cihang]
Besides the Jie Sect,
are there other evil forces plotting against us?
[Immortal Cihang]
Master Cihang,
as soon as menacing demons are discovered,
the Demon Hunters will immediately be sent out.
So, most stray demons pose no threat.
But,
there is one exception.
[Immortal Yuding]
Oh?
Who is that?
The Eastern Sea dragons.
Dragons?
[Immortal Qingxu]
Didn't they surrender to the Court of Heaven long ago?
We can't trust any but our own kind
To me,
their surrender is merely a facade,
hibernating for a moment.
The dragons have helped subdue the abyss monsters for thousands of years.
What's their crime?
They have great strength.
If they betray us in the war,
the whole situation could be reversed.
But we still can't attack them.
[Immortal Wenshu]
Our reputation of righteousness and justice is known to all.
If we gratuitously
[Immortal Wenshu]
attack the surrendered,
How will anyone ever trust us?
Aye.
We must not act rashly.
Further deliberation is necessary.
But...
Enough.
The point has been made.
And you don't have to be bigoted.
OK.
The time of the six-star alignment is almost over.
Since there are no other topics,
let's adjourn the meeting.
Brother,
Jinzha and Muzha,
are disciples of myself and Brother Puxian.
They have been cultivating here for many years away from home,
and have never even met Nezha,
their younger brother.
[Immortal Puxian]
Since there's still time left in the six-star alignment,
why not let them
[Immortal Puxian]
meet for awhile?
Great idea.
Oh no!
What should I do?
What's wrong?
Look at me...
Will my first impression...
be bad?
Of course not!
Really?
Though slovenly,
you've got strong will.
Though short,
you've got a big heart.
Though ugly,
you're kind inside.
Though you have black eye circles,
a piggy nose,
and a missing tooth,
I still think
you're truly incredibly great.
And I'm sure your brothers will agree.
Thanks for the compliment.
What are you doing?
You go meet my brothers for me.
Seriously?
How can I do that for you?
No, Nezha.
Nezha!
The boy is a bit shy.
Brother!
Ao Bing,
you cried?
This reminded me of my two brothers.
You have brothers too?
Mmm hmm.
I used to.
You're so lucky
to have two such wonderful brothers.
What were you talking about just now?
They said
they're sorry for not checking on you all these years.
They asked
how things have been at home,
if your parents are well,
what hobbies you have,
and who your friends are.
They also said
whatever problems you may have in the future, you must tell them.
And remember, you have two brothers
who will always, always help and protect you.
Why are you...
Nothing.
It's just eyes in my sand.
You sure it's not the other way around?
I already said it's nothing.
OK. You are the boss here.
I'm not talking to you.
Fine fine,
I'll stop laughing.
Are you still mad?
Nezha?
Nezha!
Ao Bing,
I've been violent and unruly since I was young,
making my parents worry all day.
Your father,
though he attacked Chentang Pass,
I know he only risked everything
for your sake.
And today,
my brothers were so kind to me.
Our families have sacrificed so much for us.
You're a monster,
and I'm a demon.
We're both burdens for our families.
So what if we were born as demons?
Immortal or demon, I make the choice.
Once you're saved,
we must win ourselves a place among the immortals
so our families won't have to worry anymore.
Yes!
Only by becoming immortals,
can we have everyone's respect.
Deal!
I'm going to become an immortal!
Only with courage and diligence can great progress be made.
[Level 2: Ascension Falls]
At this speed, cultivating
a hundred more years would still be in vain.
About cultivating,
the priorities are vitality, energy, and spirit.
If you feel it's difficult,
or you feel exhausted,
it's because you were born demons.
Only by giving it your all
will you have a chance to change your destiny
and achieve immortality.
Life or death, of none I'm scared,
defying authority is what I've revered.
My fate is mine, not heaven's plan.
This bad boy will become a godly man!
Bravo!
Just a few lines, yet so powerful,
truly inspiring.
A great poem, indeed.
This is something all of you should learn from.
Really?
Is it that good?
I just made it up.
It is good.
Every word counts,
and it's inspiring.
A poem like this
shows your ambition, young man.
A true young hero
with a bright future ahead!
Oh, come on. It's just fine.
Actually, it still has some tiny flaws.
More like plenty of flaws.
Let me ask you,
what's with those dark eye circles?
It's obvious you stay up late all the time.
Your life is undisciplined,
your diet unhealthy,
and you can't even manage basic self-control.
How can you dream of becoming an immortal?
I was born with dark eye circles.
Appearance reflects the heart, don't you know?
Take a look at yourself in the mirror.
Ridiculous, reckless and sloppy.
If you were my disciple, I'd make you rebuild your human form.
Can it be rebuilt?
Then there's hope for my looks, right?
Teach me, please.
I knew you came to find yourself a master.
Listen, kid,
I see you have great ambition,
so I'll take you as my disciple.
Cool!
Master!
Come,
train with your brothers.
Train for what?
Immortality, of course.
I don't need you to teach me that.
Teach me how to be prettier.
Ridiculous!
You're putting looks before cultivation?
Get your priorities straight.
Are you teaching me or not?
We're no longer master and disciple.
You deserve to have panda eyes for life.
That's too much.
I was going to go easy on you!
What's this?
Are you challenging me?
Three pills should be enough.
Kid,
go back where you came from.
If you keep disrupting our class,
this could end badly for you.
Apologies.
You're no match for me.
Impressive, kid.
I underestimated you.
Try this!
Yeah, teach that ignorant brat a lesson.
Master will surely win!
So fast!
You saw it?
We have no grudges between us.
You'd better go.
I cannot lose.
You can't even touch me.
Let alone fight.
Smart move!
Hold him tight, render his speed useless.
Surrender?
Wait, you are...
Finally figured it out?
It's not that I'm fast,
I just transform into electric currents,
traveling instantly to any location.
In water,
I am invincible!
Impressive cryo power.
Stay calm.
Go too hard and your body will collapse!
Ice doesn't conduct electricity.
Let's see what else you've got.
Lakes and seas.
Clouds and sky.
By this divine talisman in my hand.
Wind is to rise and rain is to fall.
Swift and Uplift!
Father!
Damn it.
The Rain Summoning Spell.
End this now!
Too late.
You're doomed.
Master!
Master, are you all right?
I wasn't going to take your life.
You didn't have to sacrifice an arm.
All disciples, listen.
Take the demons back to the palace.
Yes!
Stop!
Put them down.
All of you, put them down!
May I ask if you are a member of the Chan Sect?
That's correct.
Ah.
These are all immortals from Yu Xu Palace.
You must not be disrespectful.
Entering Yu Xu Palace
and receiving the teachings of the righteous path
may not be a bad thing.
All of you, drop your weapons!
Father!
Xiaobao?
Why have you returned?
Xiaobao,
stand down!
Xiaobao!
Impudent!
How dare you hurt our Sect members?
No!
Father!
Nezha,
freeze the river now!
You can't escape!
Father!
Go!
Go now!
Run!
Father...
There's no escape.
Step aside.
He's just trying to save his father.
You didn't have to be so brutal.
Hmph.
Panax notoginseng,
cattail pollen,
munjeet,
borneol,
dragon's blood.
One more basket.
Safflower,
angelica,
pseudo-ginseng powder,
sappanwood,
poison nut.
My lord,
we now have everything on the list,
along with a hundred extra baskets of sea products.
However, we are running out of food in the city.
Master Shen, a moment, please.
We've prepared a meal.
Would you honor us with your presence?
You...
Thanks to Lord Li's kindness,
I've been taken in as a servant.
He may be a demon,
but he has a good heart.
As long as he behaves,
there's no reason he can't have a future.
I wonder if the dishes suit your taste.
Not...
Not bad.
Then have some more.
Try this liquor as well.
I quit long ago.
Cultivators must sup... suppress desires.
As the saying goes,
one must cut off urges to perfect the spirit.
Another saying goes,
one must practice kindness to polish virtue.
Talking won't help.
I've already re... reached the point of no return.
You can't hide forever.
The truth will come out one day.
If you continue to make the
mistake of harming others,
even if you can deceive everyone,
you won't be able to fool yourself.
And you will not be able to further your cultivation,
the essence of which
is doing good deeds and walking the righteous path.
Enough!
What nonsense!
You know nothing
about cultivation.
Sir!
Someone is here to see Master Shen.
Brother
Who did this to you?
Some Taoists.
They attacked us.
Father...
had one of his arms
cut off.
Who did it?
His name is...
Ne...
Zha.
Congratulations on passing Level 2.
Please inform Brother Wuliang.
Master is in seclusion refining pills
and has not emerged yet.
Before Level 3,
why don't you rest for a few days?
We only have two days left.
No need.
I'm totally fine.
Let's continue the test.
Well,
as you wish.
The final test
is the demon Queen of Skull Mountain,
Shi Ji.
Someone is requesting an urgent meeting with Master Taiyi.
Huh?
Please help us!
It's Chentang Pass.
Something happened!
Dad.
Mom.
Dad?
Mom?
Dad!
Mom!
Calm down.
Let's keep looking.
Keep looking.
I received an urgent report as soon as I ended my seclusion.
Who could have committed such a horrendous crime?
Master,
The Shieldos said
they were struck by a tremendous force
and lost consciousness.
When they woke up,
people of Chentang Pass had already been slaughtered.
We haven't obtained the elixir yet.
Why would they do that?
Brother,
any clue?
No, no.
I was just thinking,
where did all this lava come from?
Exactly.
There are no volcanoes for hundreds of miles around.
This is truly bizarre.
Everyone, come quick!
What demon is this?
This was...
left by a dragon's claw.
Impossible!
The dragons are all in Eastern Sea,
guarding the Suppression Seal.
Not a single one could have left.
Master,
if I remember correctly,
Queen Ao Run of Western Sea
has a special skill
called the Sky...
Sky-Splitting Claw.
Are you saying she used the Sky-Splitting Claw
to cross into Chentang Pass?
That explains the lava.
It must have been transported from the purgatory.
But she's watched by the Dragon King of Eastern Sea.
It's impossible for her to cross over.
Then there's only one possibility left.
The thing I worried most about
has happened.
The King of Eastern Sea has betrayed us?
This is too serious an accusation.
Could we be wrong?
No.
It's them!
What are you doing?
Don't be impulsive.
Are you going to the Dragon Palace?
That's the direction of Skull Mountain.
The dragons slaughtered innocent civilians,
committing this unforgivable atrocity.
No need to consult with fellow Golden Immortals.
I'll strike first and explain later.
Crana,
back to the palace with me.
Summon all the Demon Hunters.
Roger.
Brother,
Nezha's parents were killed by demons.
We can't let anything happen to the child.
Take Deero and go for him now.
Yes.
I know you're heartbroken right now
but can you please
calm down for a moment?
Can you
take me to the Dragon Palace first?
I'll confront my father and master
to get to the bottom of this.
Will that bring my parents back?
[Level 3: Skull Mountain]
Mirror mirror on the wall,
who's the fairest within ten miles and more?
It's you, my lady.
[Lady Shi Ji]
And who is the fairest within a hundred miles?
It's you, my lady.
What about a thousand miles?
It's you.
And ten thousand miles?
And in the whole world?
Still you.
Do you think I'm stupid?
Lie better, at least.
No, no.
I was just trying not to upset you.
You know what?
Telling the truth won't make me mad.
Seriously?
I, Lady Shi Ji, am indeed a stunning beauty,
but I know there's always someone better.
Go on and ask then.
Am I the fairest of them all?
No.
Fair enough.
Am I the fairest within ten thousand miles?
No.
What about a thousand miles?
Hundred miles?
No.
Ten miles?
Nope.
Am I even the fairest on this mountain?
Screw you!
There isn't any other female in this mountain.
I'm female, too.
You promised you wouldn't get mad.
You are prettier than me?
Help!
How on earth?!
Demon, show yourself!
Who are you calling demon?
It's Lady Shi Ji.
Darn kid.
Have we even met?
What on earth are you doing?
You will be exposed.
Let me.
Stay out of it.
You think you can defeat me?
The entire mountain is my body.
You'll see that you can't destroy me.
If you use more force,
your body will collapse!
I said
stay out of it!
It's already started!
Crap!
I'm so screwed.
Luckily there's some left.
I shall live to fight another day.
Darn kid.
Just you wait.
Nine-Dragon Fire Trap!
No escape!
Oh my!
Reckless child.
You body has almost gone.
Are you trying to kill yourself?
Was that fire earlier?
Isn't Nezha
a frost mage?
Who... who said that?
Frost, flame, I taught it all.
His powers are...
a combination of ice and fire.
Is that possible?
The Spirit Pearl is endowed with unparalleled talents.
Can't judge him by normal standards.
Which one of us is the teacher?
You think you know better than me?
I wouldn't dare.
However,
I did sense a strong presence
of demonic energy earlier
About that...
Shi Ji must have released it.
What are you saying, fatty?
I did not...
Was it you? Was it you? Was it you?
Say it!
It was me, it was me!
Stop shaking!
I'm about to throw up!
See? I told you.
Nezha,
you've passed three levels.
Today,
I will personally cast
the Ascension Spell for you.
I went through all of this long long ago.
I was probably too nervous.
The Ascension Spell is longer than I remember.
From now on,
you're an Immortal of the Chan Sect.
This, Yu Xu Treasure Vault
houses all sorts of rare magic items.
Elixir Reparo.
You can only pick one.
Don't you need more time to decide?
Elixir Reparo.
Yu Xu Palace has sent messengers
to inform the Twelve about what the dragons did.
However, due to the great distance,
[Tianyuan Cauldron]
my brothers and sisters can't make it here sooner.
This time,
[Tianyuan Cauldron]
I will personally lead the hunt
on the dragons.
[Tianyuan Cauldron]
Nezha,
I will you fight alongside me?
Let me go back to Chentang Pass first.
Then we'll seek revenge on the Dragon King.
OK.
With your extraordinary combat skills,
you'd be a great help in destroying the Dragon Palace.
I've paid back
everything I owed you.
Wait.
Wait until my body is restored.
Let's go to the Dragon Palace together, okay?
You know well what I'm going to do.
You being there will only make it harder.
Next time we meet,
it will be as foes, not friends.
Ugh...
Karma it is.
No, you can't leave!
Your soul will scatter before you get to the Dragon Palace.
Nine-Dragon Fire Trap!
Calm down, will you?
Going now
won't change anything.
Leave me alone.
I promised Nezha I'd save you no matter what.
Pah! Pah!
Suffocating!
[Relic of Dragon Palace]
Who's there?
I'm Immortal Wuliang of the Chan Sect.
Ao Guang,
do you admit your guilt?
So,
you've found out?
Is
Ao Bing still alive?
I'll accept whatever punishment you give,
but please spare my son.
Nonsense!
The Court of Heaven ordered your clan to suppress the sea monsters.
Instead, you colluded with them
and slaughtered Chentang Pass.
Chentang Pass?
The dragons have committed an unforgivable crime.
Today,
justice shall be served.
Around the earth and skies of light.
Unleash the power with boundless might.
Let the Tianyuan rise, stand tall.
Reign supreme above them all.
Open Cauldron!
Show yourselves!
What have you done to Chentang Pass?
Didn't big brother tell us
to follow Master Shen's orders?
Shen Gongbao?!
Did you notice what's going on above us?
Maybe you should focus on the present.
My king,
we can't sit here and wait to die!
If I go into battle,
the Suppression Seal will...
Leave that to us.
Joining all our powers,
we can hold it for long enough.
Fine.
I've had enough!
You wretched demon!
This is a once-in-a-millennium chance for revenge.
Break out of purgatory!
Destroy the Dragon Palace!
Soul Blade!
Old fool!
Taste my sword!
Releasing demonic energy like this...
aren't you afraid of exposing your identity?
I told you,
if you dared to harm Chentang Pass,
I would smash your palace into PIECES!
Tell me!
Is Ao Bing dead?
Move! Out of my way!
Rise!
Do you have a death wish?
Let's see how long your body can take it.
I don't care if I live or die.
As long as you're dead!
Now is the time!
Look what you've done!
Is annihilation for all really what you want?
The chains.
Even the Eastern Sea Dragon King can't match your power.
I was right after all.
You're exactly what the Chan Sect needs.
Your parents spent their lives fighting evil.
From now on,
you must carry on their legacy
and eliminate all the demons.
Let me avenge your loss
by turning these evil dragons into pills.
Escort me!
Yes, master!
Nezha!
Dad!
Mom!
Nezha!
Son, are you alright?
Your body...
I... I...
They already know
about you and Ao Bing.
I... I...
I thought...
I'd never see you again.
Master is still casting the spell.
We need to buy as much time as we can.
Nezha,
it wasn't my father who slaughtered Chentang Pass.
The real culprit
is him, the Immortal Wuliang!
Shieldos!
Dragons?
Brother,
it's been a while.
Why are you here?
Shen Gongbao,
you collude with the dragons.
What are you up to?
I should be ask... asking you.
You captured my father.
What are you up to?
Who said I captured your father?
Only you know my family's situation.
If you didn't give the order,
why would Nezha and the Demon Hunters hunt my father down?
And my little brother's arrow wound...
He was obviously
shot by your disciple, Deero!
There's the talent I recruited myself.
Nothing slips past you.
Having done your dirty work for years
I can certainly guess your purpose here
putting up a show in Chentang Pass.
You are trying to fram... frame the dragons, aren't you?
Is this how you repay me, your brother and mentor?
You've always use... used me for your benefit.
Between you and me,
there's only grudge, not gratitude.
May I interest you in a deal,
Master Immortal?
As the overseer of Yu Xu Palace,
you must know the spell to break the Sea-Stabilizing Chains.
I do.
So what?
You... you are going to rebel?
A thousand years ago, the four of us fought in the celestial realm together.
Who has then betrayed us and
cast us into purgatory?
Now Wuliang is going after Ao Guang,
and that's exactly what we want.
I've long heard that Immortal Wuliang recruits talents without bias.
I trust you know well what we can do.
If you can free us from purgatory
and help us achieve immortality,
we are willing to offer our humble service.
Plus the secret of the Spirit Pearl and the Demon Orb.
The Spirit Pearl and the Demon Orb?
Pathetic!
Whe... where's your spine? Your will to fight back?
We were young and ignorant!
A thousand years of imprisonment
has taught us about the rules
and the rulers.
Smart.
But you're so unpredictable.
How can I trust you?
Unless you let me place on you...
We are willing.
The three dragons willingly agreed
to let Wuliang place a curse on them.
If they dared to disobey in the future,
Wuliang could take their lives at any time.
With the curse in place, Wuliang kept his promise,
freeing them from the Sea-Stabilizing Chains.
Whenever a powerful force is discovered,
Wuliang orchestrates massacres,
frames that power,
and sends troops to capture them.
Shen Gongbao will attest that
he has carried out many such tasks for Wuliang
in exchange for a chance to join the Chan Sect.
This time, Wuliang destroyed Chentang Pass
and framed the dragons of Eastern Sea.
As fate would have it,
he ended up recruiting the three dragon kings.
And from them,
he learned the secret of the Demon Orb and the Spirit Pearl.
After that,
they deliberately left two clueless survivors
to tell Yu Xu Palace what happened.
Seeing no hope of breaking through,
Shen Gongbao came up with a plan.
He had the Yaksha petrify us,
then hide us in the sewers.
Then Yaksha waited for the right time to revive us.
And you?
My families are gone.
I have nothing left to hold onto.
Over there!
The demons captured by the Demon Hunters
are not, as outsiders think,
being reformed in Yu Xu Palace.
Instead, they are thrown into the Tianyuan Cauldron by Wuliang,
refined into pills of immortality
to strengthen the Chan Sect's power.
Brother,
how could you commit such atrocities?
How...
How are you going to face our master
after betraying the teachings we received?
Now that you know what Wuliang did,
you should stop before it's too late.
Take him back to the palace
to face punishment from the Supreme Lord.
The Demon Hunters were personally trained by Master Wuliang.
Do you think a few words would turn us against him?
So,
I was wrong about the dragons.
Let them go!
Let me help.
You betrayed us?
We learned that from you, Big Brother.
Back then, in order to protect our kind,
I had no choice!
Well, in order to protect myself now,
Neither do I.
My King, wait for us!
Don't leave us behind!
My King, take us with you!
My King! My King!
You've all been sold out!
Dragon King of Southern Sea.
Dragon King of Northern Sea.
Queen of Western Sea.
[Ao Qin, Ao Run, Ao Shun]
Nephew,
it's playtime with your second uncle.
Take my spear!
Take my ax!
Take my wheel!
Take my wheel times a hundred!
Two hundred!
Three hundred!
Enough, huh?
No way!
There weren't that many.
Your body is still unstable.
Don't exhaust yourself.
For my mistakes,
I would give my life for freeing the dragons.
Young and vicious.
Let me have some fun with you, little one.
Bullying children,
shameless and vile!
Hey!
How dare you hit your master's brother!
Bullying an uncle,
eat a knuckle!
This won't do.
It's a mess.
Then let's make it messier.
How about some vapor?
Sure.
Take them down!
Watch out for sneak attacks.
There you are.
Careful, it's me!
Brother?
Sorry, sorry.
Nezha!
Ah!
Surprise!
Ha ha!
Transformation Spell?
Are you insane?
You can't fool me.
Huh?
Which one of you...
Code.
She sells seashells by the seashore.
What?
You dont know the code.
Impostor!
So you really are an impostor!
Unbelievable!
Serves you right.
Huh?
Code.
Eh... he sells bells in the big well?
Wrong!
It's "she sells seashells by the seashore
and the shells she sells all smell for sure.
I'm the real one!
How come I don't know this code?
We just made it up!
Can't you make it easier?
It's too hard!
You idiot!
Go away!
Impostor!
I'm the real Ao Shun!
Crap! You don't know the code!
Neither do you!
That's true.
Does it mean I'm an impostor, too?
My goodness.
Tai Chi flows in harmony divine.
Five elements perfectly align.
True fire of Samadhi ignites the gold.
A perfect pill, its power to unfold.
Swift and Uplift!
Why are you so scared?
We used to bathe in lava like it's nothing.
Hot! Hot!
Oh no!
It's the true fire of Samadhi.
What are you looking at?
If anyone should eat this, it's me!
Yum.
Let go of my father!
Hyah!
Freeze!
What a Spirit Pearl!
Perfect match for the Demon Orb.
Ao Bing!
Hyah!
Freeze!
Ah!
The Heart-Piercing Curse.
Since I already knew your true identities,
how could I not have a backup plan?
Impossible.
That curse is quite complex.
When did you cast it?
Oh...
That's why the Ascension Spell took so long.
You slipped in something.
You old fart!
Even the Demon Orb
won't soon be able to break the Heart-Piercing Curse.
A thousand spikes have pierced through your nerves and veins.
Any movement you attempt
will only result in your body
being torn apart.
No wonder I couldn't sense any living aura.
You were petrified.
But you being here alive again now
only harms Nezha.
The Spirit Pearl
and the Demon Orb
are precious treasures.
I wanted to treat you well,
but now you'll just serve as pills.
Ao Bing!
Father!
You...
you're still alive!
Ungh!
It's the Heart-Piercing Curse cast by Wuliang.
And he was the one that slaughtered Chentang Pass, framing the dragons.
Father,
Nezha was deceived.
Don't blame him.
Whatever you must do, do it to me.
Leave my parents out of this.
Killing you won't change anything.
We're all doomed to die here.
If anyone still holds grudges,
be my guest.
Brother,
the Chan Sect has a noble reputation.
How could you commit such a horrible offense?
Don't make more mistakes!
Why don't you go back and confess to Master?
I'll plead for mercy on your behalf.
You...
Indiscriminate fool!
If the immortals' place in the world were secured,
or if you ungrateful slackers were half as
diligent as the demons,
I wouldn't have wasted this much time and effort!
Even if it leads to my own doom
and infamy,
I did it for the eternal dominance of Chan Sect.
My conscience...
conscience...
My conscience is clear.
Another one is done.
I can't possibly eat any more.
You should try some.
Thanks.
When my fins are done, you should try some too.
The claws are ready as well.
We should swap and share.
What's going on?
My body...
He's become a pill!
I'm still so young.
don't want to die.
No, let me out.
Help!
Stay calm!
Focus all your energy!
Hold on for as long as you can.
Son!
Your power is greater than mine.
You can get through.
If you can hold out until the Heart-Piercing Curse fades,
you'll have a chance to escape.
The Heart-Piercing Curse takes at least six hours.
I'm afraid...
I won't be able to last that long.
My lady.
Mom!
Wake up, mom.
Nezha, Nezha?
Nezha.
I'm here, Mom.
You and Dad must not give up.
Don't worry about us.
Try to
stay focused.
I'm fine, Mom.
I don't feel the fire.
Nothing kills you, kiddo.
If I am correct,
flames of the Demon Orb and the true fire of Samadhi
share the same origin.
So the Tianyuan Cauldron can't harm you.
That's right.
My mistake.
Don't bother.
This is just my avatar.
As suspected, the Demon Orb
is indestructible.
No wonder the Supreme Lord had to destroy you with the Wrath of Heaven.
Nezha,
I see you're a good son.
How about I give you a chance to prove that?
The Oblivion Pill.
Swallow it
and I'll release your parents.
What do you say?
I may be ruthless,
but I always keep my promises.
Otherwise, all those elites of the demons
wouldn't swear loyalty to me.
As long as you swallow it,
I swear to Heaven,
I won't harm your parents.
What are you doing?
Using his parents' lives to threaten a kid?
And you call yourself a god?
You aren't even worthy to be a human.
Nezha,
leave us be.
You must live.
Hold on until the Heart-Piercing Curse is broken
or your two brothers find you.
You really think I can't kill the Demon Orb?
It's just a matter of time.
Once you're dead,
I have a hundred ways to destroy him.
I just wanted to have a meaningful death.
Why won't you let me die?
Why won't you?
If you trade your life for ours,
do you think we could live in peace?
Nezha.
No, mom.
It'll hurt you.
It's okay.
This is the end.
I just want to hug you one last time.
Mom.
I guess I won't get to see you grow up.
From now on,
you'll have to walk your own path.
I... I'm useless.
So useless.
I was born a demon,
and have always caused you pain.
I wanted so badly,
to make you proud.
This is all my fault.
I'm sorry.
Mom.
Every day I spent with you,
I was so happy.
I never cared
whether you were an immortal
or a demon.
All I know is
you are my son.
Mommy
will always
love...
Nezha, stay calm!
Stop!
Your body will be torn apart!
The True Fire of Samadhi has compensated for
the fire needed for the body restoration.
Nezha's physical form
is complete now!
Dad,
take care of Mom.
Help me break the cauldron!
Oh no!
They are absorbing the energy of the Tianyuan Cauldron!
Roota Maxima!
Demon Hunters, on my command,
march!
Father,
you need to save your energy for self-protection.
We've been backing down
for far too long.
We thought if we gave everything,
then Wuliang would let us live.
But in the end, they still want us dead.
If that's what they want,
then we'll fight them to the death!
Yes, let's fight!
Fight! Fight! Fight!
We can't let them out!
Do not give up!
Hang in there!
Make it...
break!
The cauldron!
My cauldron!
There goes the foundation of Chan Sect!
Kill all these monsters!
Attack!
You ungrateful traitors.
Can't tell right from wrong!
Roaring Dragon Waves!
So those two minions of his are monsters too.
Demons, immortals,
it's all part of your trickery!
You despicable lowlife.
How dare you oppose me!
Witness my true powers!
I'll give you two
one last chance because I value talent.
Surrender now
and I'll grant you immortality.
Who cares about immortality?
I'm all demon.
So what?
You claim to be a guiding light,
but all you do is bully the weak,
and bring chaos to the world.
You are the real evil!
Ignorant fools,
the immortals rule the world.
Siding with the powerful is the only way out.
Either accept that or
you'll have no place to hide.
If there is no way ahead,
then I will carve out a path!
If the world won't accommodate me,
I will turn the world upside down!
Master!
My face...
You...
You fools broke my Ageless Spell!
Old fart.
Ba... back to the palace.
Wait for me!
My father plans to lead the dragons
deep into the ocean to hide away.
Now that your identity is exposed,
why don't you come with us?
No.
I always used to hide
and run away,
until there was nowhere to left to go.
Now I finally know how to face this world.
Wuliang is one of the most powerful immortals
and is trusted by the Supreme Lord.
He may not fall so easily.
Plus, immortals and demons walk different paths,
like water and fire.
Immortals, demons...
Those are just excuses for controlling those who are different.
So what?
You think you can change things?
I want to try.
Perhaps I'm too old
to fight against the world.
Ao Bing.
I know that
once you've made up your mind,
you'll always follow through.
My son,
in the past,
I put too large a burden on you.
I never even
listened closely to you.
I apologize.
I only wanted to use my experience to give you a good life.
But now I see,
the experience of the older generation
is but the past,
and may not be right for you.
You must walk your own path.
From now on,
follow your heart.
I knew you'd come back.
How?
Because we are both too young.
Too naive to know the limits of the world.
Master.
Your face...
Don't worry.
Crana has helped apply some medicine.
With Tianyuan Cauldron destroyed,
Chan Sect is not the great power it once was.
We've committed a grave sin.
We must act before the Supreme Lord returns from seclusion.
Come,
let's go see him.
Is the holding cell concealed well?
Nobody else can come in here.
The cell inside is shielded with a spell.
The door can only be opened
by you and one other guard only.
Mmm.
Slacking off.
Snoozing on the job.
What is going on?
This door
uses facial recognition.
Your appearance has changed,
and your face will need to be re-entered.
Redo it.
You dare to laugh at me?
I curse you to sleep for ten years.
Are you suffering,
Brother?
Brother is the one who has suffered.
Who has... has beat you up like this?
Hmph.
Do you know why I originally recruited you?
I wanted your demon identity
so that in the Deification War,
I could entrust you with important tasks.
You're delusional!
[Shen Zhengdao]
Father
Don't worry.
He's still breathing.
If you will let me place a curse on you,
then your father can enjoy
a peaceful life at Yu Xu Palace.
The two people you've asked for are here.
Think carefully about it.
Hmm?
The medicine from earlier has taken effect.
Then what can we do?
Who else can open the door?
Ten years...
Jinzha of Five Dragon Mountain, Yunxiao Cave.
[Jinzha]
Muzha of Jiugong Mountain, White Egret Cave.
[Muzha]
Responding the summons to return to palace.
Master.
Brace yourself.
That should be enough.
I think
the left eye isn't swollen enough.
The right cheek needs adjustment.
Wait!
Were you two laughing just now?
I wouldn't dare!
Master is suffering
and my heart hurts a hundred times more.
Really?
Absolutely true.
Heaven and earth bears witness.
Okay, that's enough.
I think
we overdid it.
What?
It's alright.
Apply some medicine and we'll try again.
Master, you are one who accomplishes great things.
This is for the fate of the Chan Sect.
Let's try a few more times.
We will get it right eventually.
Catch him!
Don't let him run!
Hurry,
put on the medicine quickly!
Medicine!
Let me go!