First, it came to Momma
as a snake.
Then it took other forms
to torment her.
But Momma
was a good little girl.
She listened to her parents
and always stayed on the rope.
So, the Evil couldn't
touch her outside the house.
Because if the Evil touches you...
it makes you do bad things.
O blessed house
of ancient wood.
Shelter to the pure and good.
We'll keep you bright
and never roam.
Heaven is here, within our home.
Samuel, Nolan,
10-minute warning, boys.
Nine-minute warning, Nolan.
Momma says there's only love
inside of us.
That's why the Evil
wants us so badly.
He wants to destroy this love.
Make us turn
against each other.
Kill each other.
Like it made the people
in the world do.
All it needs is one touch,
without the rope on.
And then, not even the house
can save you.
Get it.
There you go.
Frogs sang loud last night.
Spring is coming.
We'll be ready.
It's a good day for a good day.
Don't feed the dog.
We're not
the only ones starving.
And I don't need to eat
as much as you.
Momma?
Momma, can we listen
to it tonight?
-It's not new moon.
- I'm asking Momma.
We should wait.
It won't be special if we don't.
Told ya.
You'll grow into 'em.
The Evil
can't touch me here,
dawn to night and year to year.
The forest
with its dangers abound,
wrapped up tight
and safe and sound.
Do you see it?
Go get 'em, Koda.
Bring us a big, fat rabbit.
Y'all ready?
Never let go.
Momma told us
that even before the Evil
possessed everyone,
the world was already bad.
And that's why it came.
The people opened
their door for it,
whether they knew it or not.
Let them go.
But Grandma knew it.
And Grandpa was the only one
to believe her.
He was a good man
and built this place for her.
A blessed house where the Evil
wouldn't be able to come in.
A place to raise a family,
far away from the darkness
of the world.
It was a good life.
But after a while, Grandma
started to feel a presence
lurking in the woods.
Something evil,
getting stronger.
She refused to leave
the house anymore.
So, Grandpa figured out
how to tie a rope
to the foundation of the house,
so she could finally
go outside.
Let them go, Junebug.
Whoo!
Whoo-hoo!
Nolan.
What are you doing?
Making some slack
so I can grab this egg.
Don't.
Could be a trick.
I could grab it.
It's right there.
Give me your machete.
No.
We'll let Momma decide.
She can tie the ropes together.
I wasn't gonna let go.
We didn't get this far
just to die of hunger.
How can you be so sure
of everything?
Because
I'm older than you.
Yeah. By three minutes.
She loves me more.
What?
What did you say?
I didn't say anything.
Sam!
Nolan!
Samuel!
Sam!
My rope.
Samuel!
Sam!
- Samuel!
- Sam! Sam.
Come on.
Nolan!
Run!
Get back on the rope!
No! No. No!
No! No! No!
Okay.
Did it touch you? Huh?
- Uh-uh.
- Did it touch you, Nolan?
I don't think so.
Hold on to the rope.
What do you see?
Momma, what is it?
Breathe. Just breathe.
Breathe. Breathe.
It's okay. It's okay.
Just breathe. Just breathe.
Just breathe.
On your knees.
I need to be sure.
Don't look at me.
Touch the wood!
Hands on the cellar.
Say it.
Say it!
O blessed house
of ancient wood.
Shelter to the pure and good.
We'll keep you bright
and never roam.
Heaven is here,
within our home.
Okay, get up.
- What happened?
-I didn't mean to.
I stepped on his rope...
Have you lost your mind?
It's all right, Momma.
He didn't...
Quiet! One more second
and it woulda all been over.
For all of us!
That rope is your lifeline.
-I'm sorry.
- I don't need you to be sorry!
I need you to use your head!
Can you move it?
I think it's broke.
Don't just stand there.
Get me a splint for his ankle.
I know. I know, I know.
Come on. It's okay.
What'd it look like this time?
Like my momma.
It's trying to scare me.
Like it tried to scare
my momma before.
That's all we got today.
Don't eat too fast.
Sure is good.
I used to be thankful
that the Evil
didn't show itself to you.
And then, I figured out
what it was doing.
I never told y'all this.
But one time,
it came to me as a little girl,
crying out for help.
She was just at my rope's limit.
She got her foot stuck
in a gopher hole.
She was howling, screaming.
I saw the bone
sticking out.
I had to keep telling myself
that it wasn't real.
But the screams
went on for days.
So, every morning,
I went out to check...
to see if the Evil had given up.
But she was still there.
Her skin turned blue and gray.
The smell...
I wondered
why she was still out there.
Why?
Because it wanted me
to go see about that girl.
It wanted me to doubt myself.
To lure me off the rope.
The Evil is clever...
and patient.
It's like the snake
you've seen in the woods.
Evil can wear many, many skins.
And the greatest trick of all,
it's playing on you boys.
And when enough time goes by,
you're gonna forget
it's even there.
You're gonna
let your guard down.
And it's gonna get you!
One touch
without a rope on
is all it takes
to possess one of us
and get inside the house.
Never
let go.
Never let go.
How long?
About an hour.
Felt longer tonight.
Did you imagine it?
Yes.
Tell us about it.
I imagined it was all gone.
You.
Sam.
Koda.
The house.
All I had left was the darkness.
And then what?
I thought about our birth
in the house,
and how safe
it keeps us every day.
And I felt
the darkness float away.
Look around.
Look how lucky you are.
All your dreams came true.
The Evil can't touch you here.
Samuel, your turn.
Time to clean your soul.
Remember, lose us completely
and then find us again.
Fill the cellar up
with all your love.
You remind the house
why we deserve its protection.
Can I move yet?
Nope.
Nolan, I got an itch.
I said, "Don't move."
It's just one itch.
Okay.
That should do it.
Wow.
Are those owl wings?
Uh-huh.
I can fly anywhere I want.
And eat whatever you want.
Once upon a time,
there was a boy who could fly
and catch all the squirrels
in the trees.
Hey, Sam.
After your rope broke,
did you notice anything?
Like what?
Anything strange.
That was the first time
we ever let go.
And nothing changed.
'Cause it didn't get us.
Yeah.
If it did,
do you think
Momma woulda killed us?
Like she killed Poppa?
Like she killed
Grandma and Grandpa?
The Evil touched them.
She was protecting us.
I know that.
What?
Nothing.
You ever wish
you could run free like Koda?
Without a rope
around your chest?
But Koda's a dog.
The Evil doesn't care
about animals.
You ever wish you could see
what she sees?
Just once?
I felt something
getting closer today.
You were just scared.
Why are you asking
all these questions?
Momma never lied to us.
"She loves me more."
That's what I heard you say
before I stepped on your rope.
I didn't say that.
I didn't mean for what happened.
I know.
O blessed house...
of ancient wood.
Home...
to my runaway wife.
Hey, Junebug.
What's wrong?
June!
June, it's me.
It's been a while.
God, have I missed you.
You think I can see 'em?
Oh, you ain't told 'em
the truth about their father.
I get it.
'Cause then you got to
tell 'em who you really are.
Ain't that right,
my little Junebug?
I'm not her no more.
You know you loved it.
What's your plan?
I know ya.
You ain't got no plan.
You might as well
give 'em to me.
Or would you rather
watch them starve?
I came so close today.
Sooner or later,
you're gonna let go.
And when you do...
I'm gonna
make you eat your babies.
June!
Careful now.
Don't break those roots.
You think it'll get better?
Hard to say.
The winter did a number on us.
All we can do now is hope.
What?
Nothing.
The snake on your back.
You said you got it
when you were in the city.
But you also said
the Evil was already there,
killing everybody.
I don't understand...
I got it before it all started.
When I met your Poppa.
I was a different person
back then.
Does it still scare you?
Not anymore.
I like it now.
Why?
Because
it's from your life before.
In the old world.
A world
full of pain and suffering?
What's to like about that?
Huh?
Don't know.
When I was your age,
asking questions like you do,
I didn't really believe
my momma, either.
- That's why you left?
- Mm-hmm.
Never thought
I'd come back here.
But it's the only place
I could keep y'all safe.
But what if the Evil did...
touch one of us
and come in the house?
What would happen?
It would make us
kill each other.
That's how the world ended.
But how do you know we're alone?
Maybe our house isn't
the only one that's protected.
Would that make you feel better?
We wouldn't be alone
for the rest of our lives.
We're not alone, Nolan.
We have each other.
And that's everything.
There's nobody else
out there, baby.
We're the world now.
"Once upon a time,
"there dwelt near a large wood
"a poor woodcutter,
"with his wife
and two children...
"a little boy called Hansel
"and a girl called Gretel.
"Once, when there was
a great famine in the land,
"he could not procure
even his daily bread."
"As he lay there thinking
in the bed one evening,
"rolling about for trouble,
"he sighed
and said to his wife,
"'What will become of us?
"'How will I feed my children
"'when we have no more
that we can eat ourselves?'
"'Know, then, my husband,'
answered she,
"'we will lead them away,
"'quite early in the morning,
"'into the thickest part
of the woods.
"'And there make them a fire
"'and give them each
a little piece of bread.'"
"'And then
we will go to our work
"'and leave them alone.'"
"'They will not find
a way home again.
"'And we shall be freed
from them.'"
It's new.
You sure?
You got eyes, don't you?
It's a new moon.
Right, Momma?
Can we listen to it tonight?
♪ One evening
as the sun went down ♪
♪ And the jungle fire
was burning ♪
♪ Down the track
came a hobo hikin'♪
♪ He said,
"Boys, I'm not turning ♪
♪ "I'm headed for a land ♪
♪ That's far away ♪
♪ "Beside
the crystal fountains ♪
♪ "So come with me ♪
- ♪ "We'll go and see" ♪
- Come on, Momma.
♪ "The Big Rock
Candy Mountains"♪
♪ In the Big Rock
Candy Mountains ♪
♪ There's a land
that's fair and bright ♪
♪ Where the handouts
grow on bushes ♪
♪ And you sleep out
every night ♪
♪ Where the boxcars
all are empty ♪
♪ And the sun shines
every day ♪
♪ On the birds and the bees
And the cigarette trees ♪
♪ And the lemonade springs
Where the bluebird sings ♪
♪ In the Big Rock
Candy Mountains ♪
♪ All the cops
have wooden legs ♪
♪ And the bulldogs
all have rubber teeth ♪
♪ And the hens
lay soft-boiled eggs ♪
♪ And the farmers' trees
are full of fruit ♪
♪ And the barns
are full of hay ♪
♪ Oh I'm bound to go
where there ain't no snow ♪
♪ Where the rain don't fall
And the wind don't blow ♪
♪ In the Big Rock
Candy Mountains ♪
Nolan?
Nolan.
Are you still asleep?
There you go.
You forgot
your bell again.
It's better with sap.
Yeah.
That'll make it taste
less like a tree.
We're doing
the best we can.
Eat.
Momma?
Sam?
No!
No! No!
Koda.
Touch the wood.
Say it!
O blessed house of ancient wood.
Shelter
to the pure and good.
We'll keep you bright
and never roam.
Heaven is here, within our home.
Say it again.
O blessed house of ancient wood.
Again!
O blessed house
- of ancient wood...
-Louder!
Shelter to the pure
and good!
Momma.
Momma!
I have to pee, Momma!
Did you feel
the darkness go away?
Sam.
You're awake?
No.
Sam.
Sam!
Yes.
We need to leave the house.
Goodnight, Nolan.
I'm serious.
- Sam!
- Shh.
How do you wanna leave?
The Evil will catch us as soon
as we take off the rope.
We know the forest.
If we look after each other,
we might have
a chance to outrun it.
What about Momma?
We'll come back for her
once we find something to eat.
Momma knows what's right for us.
I don't think she does anymore.
Did you see her?
She's starving, too.
She always
figures something out.
For once,
we have to help.
By disobeying her?
Will you really
let go of the rope?
I can let go of the rope,
but I can't let go
of my brother.
It's too dangerous.
I'm sorry.
This is a very special tool.
It's called a camera.
What does it do?
Takes pictures.
It captures what it sees,
with this little eye.
You aim it,
then you push this button
right here and...
A real-life picture comes out.
Like this one.
This was me...
from the old world.
Is that really you?
Hey, hey, careful.
I was a different person
back then.
Or this one.
I took it outside on the porch.
Sam.
- This is us?
-Mm-hmm.
And this is Koda.
Yep.
You can take a picture
of anything you want.
But a good picture
shows more than
what the camera's looking at.
It shows a special moment,
frozen in time.
They can even show a feeling.
Like love.
Where's Poppa?
He was holding the camera.
Do you have a picture of him?
Mm-mm.
These are the only two
I chose to keep.
And there's one more
in there, too.
I've been saving it.
For when?
Look for the right moment.
Maybe you'll find one
that reminds us
what we're living for.
Even if it's something small.
'Cause some moments in life
are hard.
But when we remember
why we're holding on,
we get strong again.
This right here
is about to be
one of those hard moments.
We've been through some brutal,
brutal winters, haven't we?
But nothing like this one.
Everything in the garden,
gone.
The roots are waterlogged.
The animals,
they ain't come back yet.
We got water.
But that'll last us maybe
a couple weeks.
Maybe a month.
But soon...
our bodies
are gonna start shutting down.
And we're gonna die.
So, we only got one option.
And that's Koda.
What?
We can salt the meat.
Maybe it'll last us
a month or so
- before it's spoiled.
- No!
I know you love him.
We all do.
But he nearing
the end of his life,
and he... he ain't caught us
nothing in months.
We can eat more frogs.
That's not gonna be enough.
I'll eat the bark, the bugs.
I don't mind it, Momma. I swear.
- Nolan.
- Maybe it's safe to leave.
I was out there
without a rope on.
The Evil coulda touched me,
but it didn't.
'Cause it chose not to.
It wants you to doubt me.
And look...
that's exactly
what you're doing.
What if you're wrong? What if
the world is still out there?
This is the world!
There's nothing out there!
It's either the house
or the Evil. That's it!
No. This is evil.
Eating family is evil!
If we can't feed ourselves,
how are we gonna feed the dog?
You wanna die?
I don't wanna die, but I don't
wanna see my friend die!
But this is not fair!
All he's done is protect us!
Let's ask Samuel.
Of course he'll do what you say.
He can talk for hisself.
Samuel?
We have to.
I hate you! I hate both of you.
I hate this house!
Come on, Koda.
Momma, I can do it if you want.
No.
No!
No. No!
No! No! No!
Koda! Koda!
No!
No! Momma, please!
Please, no!
Koda!
Please!
You're a good dog.
I thank you
for taking good care of us.
You're a good dog.
Momma.
Nolan.
It's not real.
Listen to me.
You need to see.
You need to see there's
nothing to be scared of!
That's what it wants you
to think, baby. Don't do it!
No! Don't do it.
No. No.
Nolan! Open this door.
Nolan!
Open the door.
Nolan, I... I lied.
I didn't tell you everything.
I brought the Evil here.
The Evil is real!
And if it touches me
and gets inside the house,
it's gonna make me kill you!
Open the door.
Please!
Open the fucking door!
Nolan!
Momma!
Bad little goat.
Bad little goat,
caught sitting in my chair.
Let's see that tushy,
and I'll make it
so you can't sit anywhere.
It's here!
Momma!
Damn it. What the hell?
Bad!
Bad little goat,
putting poison in my food.
Bad little goat.
Bad!
I told you,
I'm gonna make you
eat your babies.
You'll never get in.
No!
Momma!
Momma?
Wake up, Momma.
Momma, wake up!
It's okay, Momma.
I'm tying the ropes together.
It's okay, Momma. It's okay.
Momma, please.
O blessed house
of ancient wood.
Shelter to the pure and good.
We'll keep you bright
and never roam.
Heaven is here, within our home.
Momma, please.
The house has us now, Momma.
You can wake up.
Please, Momma, wake up.
I need you.
Please, Momma.
O blessed house of ancient wood.
Shelter to the pure and good.
We'll keep you bright
and never roam.
Heaven is here, within our home.
Momma, please.
Please, Momma.
♪ Our love ♪
♪ Is like a song ♪
♪ That lingers on ♪
♪ With it
light-hearted laughter ♪
♪ Leaving tears ever after ♪
♪ Fading away ♪
♪ The night
is like a symphony ♪
♪ But there's no melody ♪
♪ Without your love ♪
Koda!
Come back!
I made some pine needle tea.
It'll help with your hunger.
Was that you out there?
Out where?
I saw you,
in the woods,
laughing at me for not
being able to save her.
I think
you were dreaming.
Touch the wood.
Touch it.
O blessed house of ancient wood.
Shelter to the pure and good.
We'll keep you bright
and never roam.
Heaven is here, within our home.
Okay.
Now drink.
You need some air.
I won't let you die.
Help!
Hello!
Excuse me!
Hi, there.
Sorry to intrude. I just, uh...
I was hiking, and I...
I thought I heard someone
screaming for help.
That wasn't you,
by any chance, was it?
I...
I thought my ears
were playing tricks on me.
Wow, I didn't think
anyone was out here.
This is, uh...
Ah.
Are you okay?
What's your name, son?
Nolan.
I'm sorry, I didn't catch that.
- Nolan.
Hi, Nolan. I'm Cole.
It's nice to meet you.
So, uh...
Where your folks at?
They around?
My momma's dead.
Oh, I'm very sorry to hear that.
How did she pass?
My brother's sick.
He needs food.
Okay.
Well, I've got some food
in my pack.
You know,
Nolan, I've got a truck
about five miles from here,
- and I could take you
and your brother...
-Get back!
Whoa. Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Okay. Okay, okay.
Whoa.
Okay.
Uh...
Look, I don't mean
you boys any harm.
Nolan here says you're sick.
- We're not stupid.
- Sam.
I didn't say
you were stupid. I just...
I just thought someone
was in trouble. That's it.
You killed my momma.
No, son. I...
I don't know your momma. Okay?
Look, this was just...
this was a mistake.
I'm sorry. I'm gonna go.
I'm gonna leave now,
- all right?
- Don't move.
I ju... Okay. Just calm down.
What if he's a real person?
We were happy.
Listen to me, okay?
I'm just gonna turn,
I'm just gonna go back.
I'm gonna go back from where
I came from, all right?
- Just...
- I said, "Don't move!"
Look, everything's fine.
-Just let him go.
- Everything's okay.
Let him go, Sam.
Please.
It's over.
She's gone.
No!
Sam...
Help me!
Nolan, don't.
- He said he has food.
- It's a trick.
Help me!
911.
What's your emergency?
Sir?
Sir, can you hear me?
Can you tell me...
Sir...
Sir, tell me where you are.
Huh.
Mm.
It's from the man.
He's dead.
That wasn't a man.
Try it.
Did you let go?
No.
I touched him with the rope on.
He wouldn't have let me
if he was the Evil, right?
You still won't learn.
You're falling for it
all over again!
Just try it.
No.
Maybe there's no Evil.
Momma lied to us.
We're not the only ones left
in the world.
If we thought there was
nothing out there for us,
then we wouldn't
wanna leave her.
She killed herself
to keep us safe,
and you still won't believe it!
Just try it!
You'll see that it's real!
It'll make you feel better!
I promise.
Once upon a time,
there were two brothers
who trusted each other.
She loved you!
She loved you.
And I'm so sorry for what I did.
But we're not safe.
We're dying.
At least then we'll be
with Momma again.
Maybe that'll be enough
for you this time.
Hello?
Who's in there?
Koda?
Hello?
Momma?
I'm looking for my dad.
He asked me to wait by the car,
but he never came back.
Do you mind lowering that?
Thanks.
How did you get here?
I followed his footsteps
in the mud.
He's tall, black hair,
a bit of gray on the sides?
Have you seen him?
Why is that rope
around your waist?
To keep me safe.
From what?
Where did you get
that flashlight?
That's my dad's.
It was a mistake.
I didn't mean to.
What are you talking about?
Where is he?
What did you do?
What did you do to him?
I thought
he was the Evil.
No, wait!
I thought he was the Evil!
Come back!
The rope... Oh, no.
Please! Come back!
I know she's real.
Aah!
Sam!
Nolan!
Sam?
Sam!
Nolan!
Where are you?
No!
Sam?
Huh?
It's not real.
Sam.
Why did you cut my rope?
O blessed house of ancient wood.
Shelter to the pure and good.
We'll keep you bright
and never roam.
Heaven is here, within our home!
Stop it, Sam!
Sam! Sam!
Sam!
♪ One evening
as the sun went down ♪
♪ And the jungle fire
was burning ♪
♪ Down the track
came a hobo hikin' ♪
♪ He said,
"Boys, I'm not turning ♪
♪ "I'm headed for a land
that's far away ♪
♪ "Beside the crystal
fountains ♪
♪ "So come with me,
we'll go and see ♪
♪ "The Big Rock
Candy Mountains" ♪
♪ In the Big Rock
Candy Mountains ♪
♪ There's a land
that's fair and bright ♪
♪ Where the handouts
grow on bushes ♪
♪ And you sleep out
every night ♪
Sam! You don't wanna do this!
♪ You can walk
right out again ♪
♪ As soon as you are in
There ain't... ♪
The house won't protect you
anymore.
Nolan?
Come here, baby.
Come here.
I'm not mad at you, Nolan.
I was just like you
when I was your age.
I wanna hold you again, baby.
Come on.
My sweet boy.
I missed you so much.
You're not her.
I saw what you did to Sam.
You saw what he really was.
I just helped him see it.
Look at what you did.
You destroyed your whole family.
And I didn't even
have to touch you.
I didn't mean to.
It's okay.
You don't have
to be scared anymore.
You're not my momma!
I'm more her
than she ever was.
I'm the darkness
that was inside her.
that's inside you now.
I'm the darkness
that's in your blood.
All you got to do...
is let go.
I can't!
♪ In the Big Rock
Candy Mountains ♪
♪ You never change your socks ♪
♪ And the little streams
of alcohol ♪
♪ Come a-trickling
down the rocks ♪
♪ The brakemen
have to tip their hats ♪
♪ And the railroad bulls
are blind ♪
♪ There's a lake of stew... ♪
♪ You can paddle
all around 'em ♪
♪ In a big canoe ♪
♪ In the Big Rock
Candy Mountains ♪
♪ The jails are made of tin ♪
♪ And you can walk
right out again ♪
♪ As soon as you are in ♪
There's nothing for you
in that cellar.
Did you imagine it?
Yes.
Tell us about it.
I thought about
our birth in the house,
and how safe
it keeps us every day.
And I felt
the darkness float away.
When we remember
why we're holding on,
and who we holding on for...
...we get strong again.
The Evil
can't touch me here,
dawn to night and year to year.
O blessed house of ancient wood.
Shelter to the pure and good.
Never let go.
We'll keep you bright
and never roam.
Heaven is here, within our home.
I love you, Momma!
My brother.
I need to find my brother.
- You're safe now.
- My brother.
- But we can't leave him.
- You're safe now.
- Just breathe.
- No! Where is he?
- Just breathe now.
- Where is he?
Just breathe. It's okay.
He's right here.
Sam. Sam.
I'm here. Hey, Sam.
I'm here, Sam.
I'm here.
We're free.
She loves me more.
♪ Good night, Mother ♪
♪ Here's for bigger dreams ♪
♪ Sleep tight, Mother ♪
♪ Tell the morning days ♪
♪ America has answered ♪
♪ Every mother's prayer ♪
♪ You won't have
the heartaches ♪
♪ They have over there ♪
♪ Don't worry, Mother ♪
♪ You will not be blue ♪
♪ Your boy always ♪
♪ Will belong to you ♪
♪ He'll never be so far away ♪
♪ That he can't call
each night and say ♪
♪ Good night, Mother,
good night ♪
♪ Don't worry, Mother ♪
♪ You will not be blue ♪
♪ Your boy always ♪
♪ Will belong to you ♪
♪ He'll never be so far away ♪
♪ That he can't call
each night and say ♪
♪ Good night, Mother,
good night ♪