Lucas.
Fuck!
Bro!
I’m sorry,
that was kind of mean.
Why the fuck, dude?
What do you need?
I was lonely.
I need somebody to talk to.
What?
Yo, how much water
you gonna drink, bro?
Bro, I’ll be fine.
No, you won’t. You have
the world’s tiniest bladder.
I’m not stopping again.
Bro, I’m a camel. Chill.
What the fuck is wrong
with you? Chill the fuck out.
I’ve had this for four years.
Dry mouth?
Yes.
I told you.
It’s extremely rare.
I’m just saying that
I don’t think drinking water
is the solution.
Are you prediabetic?
You don’t think I’ve asked
myself these questions?
Gone to doctors
and tried to figure this out?
Well, you should probably
change primary care physicians.
Could you just drive?
I don’t have to pee.
Okay.
I fucking knew it! I knew it!
Don’t get mad at me.
What did I tell you?
Every time!
I have to pee.
Make it quick,
dude. Quick.
Bro, you got two minutes.
Fuck off!
Two minutes!
Oh, that’s so good.
"Bro, I’m a camel."
Camel my ass, dude.
Dude!
Oh, shit, shit, shit.
Give me one minute! Chill out!
It’s quite fucking annoying.
Want to go? Give me two
fucking minutes. Fuck!
Yo! Chill the fuck out!
What’s your deal, man?
Daniel?
What the...?
Help.
Daniel?
Daniel... Daniel...
Daniel.
Just, uh...
What the...?
Okay. Come on, come on.
What the fuck?
Come on. Come on, please.
He’s not real.
No way.
Stupid, stupid.
Thank you, guys.
Did you get
all the boxes?
Yeah, I did.
Hmm?
Not sure that horn’s gonna win
us any friends out there.
You don’t like it?
I don’t know.
People like it.
It’s like the road rage
diffuser, you know?
How we doing?
Good. Keys dropped,
apartment’s fully purged.
It’s like we never lived here.
Sure we don’t want
to put anything in storage?
No.
No? Okay.
No way. Feels good to make
a clean break.
Mmm.
Besides, everything we need’s
right here, right?
Home sweet home.
Mm-hmm.
Hmm.
Hey. Got you
a little something.
It’s like a housewarming gift.
Thank you.
Need some help with that?
No, that’s okay. Thank you.
I’m gonna help you with it,
because--
No, wait! Okay, okay, okay!
Let’s get this show
on the road.
All right!
Oh, my God.
It’s a little Bob Ross.
Do you like it?
It’s perfect, baby.
Thank you.
What does Bob always say?
"No mistakes,
just happy accidents."
No mistakes, but...
how about
no accidents either?
Amen.
You still
checking that thing?
Just making sure it still...
...works. Yay!
We’re not gonna
need it though.
I got us something better.
Mmm?
No?No.
Saint Christopher.
Patron saint of travelers.
My family always drove
with one of these.
This guy’s gonna keep us safe.
Yeah, I’ll just stick
with this.
Then I guess
you’re going to hell.
Oh!
All right.
Should we get out of the city?
Let’s go.
So,
I just have to run the car
for two hours,
and then my whole battery
system’s charged.
It’s Fuller time, baby!
Maddie?
Mads!
Okay.
Hey.
Hey. Ready to go?
Mm-hmm.
Good.
I was thinking...
maybe we could add
a brief pit stop.
How brief?
There is this local
barbeque spot
that’s supposed to be
unmissable.
All right.
Mm-hmm.
What do you say?
Game for Plan B... BQ?
You liked that one! Come on.
We got the reservation at six,
and it’s super tight.
You know?
Right.
But... beautiful romantic
hot springs?
Mmm.
Just us two?
I can’t wait.
But...
wouldn’t a little barbeque
on the way make it...
absolutely perfect?
Mm-hmm.
Yeah. Really?
You sure you can’t hold it
for another hour?
We’re thirty minutes away.
Forty-five, tops.
Yeah. Okay.
Got it, thank you.
This won’t be
the last hot spring.
Yeah... I know.
Sorry.
What do we do?
Everything else is booked.
I’ll have to find us a Plan C.
Yeah.
Oh, God.
What’s that for?
Six weeks on the road.
Wow.
I know, right?
Doesn’t feel that long.
Um, well, I was actually
gonna say it feels way longer.
Oh, really?
I’m kidding.
Cheers.
Wow.
Yeah.
Okay.
Ah! Whew!
All right.
Ty, what’s going on?
I got something to show you.
Oh! Wow.
Okay.
And, uh...
Wow.
This is amazing.
When did you do all this?
Wow.
It’s beautiful.
Tyler!
This was gonna be
way more romantic. I swear.
I had the whole thing planned
out at the hot springs.
But if we survive six weeks
on the road,
then we can survive
anything, baby.
So...
Maddie Brecker,
will you marry me?
Oh, shit!
Neighborhood Watch.
No camping
on residential streets.
Yeah. Oh, right.
You got sixty seconds
before I call the cops.
All right, we’re gone. Sorry.
Oh, my God.
I swear that isn’t a bad omen.
Yes.
Oh, yeah?
Yeah.
Yeah!
She said yes! Whoo, baby!
Thirty seconds!
All right, man!
All right, we’re moving!
Okay, we got to go.
Hey, you think
we should invite that guy
back there to the wedding?
I don’t think so. No.
You know what we should do?
Spring for a hotel.
Hmm.
A long hot bath
does sound amazing.
Fresh sheets.Yeah.
Maybe a massage.
There’s one about an hour
from here
that’s not too pricey.
Oh, yeah?
Yeah.
Book it.
Hey...
you must be beat.
Come on, just let me drive.
No, I’m good.
Come on.
I’m good. I’m good. No, no,
you be passenger princess.
Just let me drive, Ty.
Baby.
Come on.
I can drive for a bit.
Mads...
you’re looking
at the Road Warrior.
Shit!
Fuck.
All right.
Oh, fuck!
Come on, just go!
Come on!
What’s going on?
Uh...
What is wrong with this guy?
Slow down.
Let him go.
Your road rage woke me up.
Oh, my God.
Ty.
Oh, man.
Oh, shit.
There’s been a crash.
He’s hit a tree.
Well, straight off the road.
Uh, yeah.
Where are we?
Uh...
Forrester... I don’t know.
We’re on Forrester Road. Yeah.
You guys better hurry up, man.
It does not look good.
Ty, he needs help.
Yeah. Forrester Road.
Help.
Something pulled him back in.
Ty. Ty.
It’s just him.
What?
Hey, man... you okay?
Ambulance
is on its way, all right?
Don’t talk, don’t talk.
Just try to breathe.
What?
Oh, what the fuck?
Ty, are you okay?
Don’t come in here,
okay, Mads?
You do not want to see this.
I thought I just saw...
There’s nothing there, baby.
That’s so weird.
Hey, look. Cops are here.
I’ll talk to ’em, okay?
Yeah.
I just want to
get out of here.
Yeah, totally.
Go on.
Okay.
Hey. Uh... we, uh...Hey.
We were driving and this guy
just came out of nowhere...
Come on, come on, come on, Ty.
Hurry up.
Okay, let’s go.
So good
to have hot water, right?
Something’s wrong
with the dashcam.
Footage cuts out right before
the crash happens.
It’s so weird.
Come on.
That is weird.
What?
Come on!
Mads.
Why don’t we give it a rest
for tonight, huh?
Please?
Yeah.
Yeah? Good.
Yeah. Okay.
Can I have
your undivided attention?
Yes.
Good. Because I got an idea.
Tomorrow
there’s a van-life meetup.
How about you and me go?
Not be on the road?
Right.
Who are you?
I’m your fiancé.
Come on, you slowpoke!
Careful.
You can’t do that.
I’m coming.
I’m not gonna try.
What the fuck?
I... I saw these
on the car last night.
What?
What do you mean, like,
he crashed into us?
No.
I mean I saw the exact same
marks on his car.
Three scratches
just like that.
Yeah, well, his car
was all types of dinged up.
We’ll get someone at
the van meet to buff it out,
right?Yeah.
Yeah, good idea.
You excited?
Uh-huh.
Here you go.
Thanks.
I think we found your tribe.
I’m getting out there.
Go, go.
It’s Fuller time, baby!
Oh, my God. It’s him.
Yeah, absolutely.
Just respect, you know?
Hey. Hey!
Hi.
Hey, man.
You’re Brad Fuller, right?
From Vandalize Channel?
Yeah.
I’ve been a subscriber
of your channel forever.
I’ve seen all your videos
a hundred times!
What the fuck?
Oh, my God!
Ugh, gross!
So this is Pumpkin.
Uh, she’s nowhere near
as sleek and sexy as yours,
but we kind of based our build
off of yours.
Still working on it.
The van.
Not Maddie.
This is Maddie.
Hi.
She did the interior design.
Yeah.
Oh.
Last job before I retired.
Good for you.
But honestly,
nothing beats this.
Yeah.
I even feel like I breathe
different out here.
Ouch! That looks nasty.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Had a bit of a rough night.
Yeah, uh, we got kicked
out of the street
we were stealth camping,
and, um...
Oh, 24-hour gyms,
you park there.
They’re your friends
from now on.
They won’t give you the knock.
And they got hot showers.
Hmm.
How ’bout I tour the castle?
Yeah, of course, man!
Come on in.
I’m gonna go stretch my legs.
You want me to come with?
Uh, no.
No, it’s okay. Have fun.
It’s Brad fucking Fuller!
Prayer happening in ten,
hope you can make it.
Uh, no, thanks.
They’re great.
Betty, there you are.
How ya doin’, love?
Oh, hey.
Great to see you again.
Wow, these are new.
Yeah.
Nice.
A new design.
So much death.
Depressing, isn’t it?
Yeah. A little.
Let me guess.
What, two months out?
How can you tell?
Well, you don’t have that
obnoxious glow
of a first-weeker.
Um, how long
have you been out here?
Ah, I lost count
two decades ago.
Um, Maddie.
Diane. Good to meet you.
So, um, you’ve been
to a lot of these?
Not so much.
I just stopped in to see
how Betty was keeping.Mmm.
Yeah.
Um...
How long did it take you
to, you know, fully adjust?
Longer than two months, honey.
Well, took my boy,
uh, fiancé like two hours.
So...
Not what you expected?
We both
needed a change of pace.
And it’s been an adventure...
Mmm. ...for sure.
But...?
I don’t know, it’s, uh...
It doesn’t quite
feel like home yet.
But we’ll get there. I think.
You headed west?
Yeah.
Uh, you?
Flagstaff.
I got a friend has a little
seafood restaurant,
middle of the desert.
Go figure.
Great. Well, um...
Safe travels.
You, too.
The road can be a scary place.
We were driving and, uh,
this guy just
came out of nowhere
and crashed
right in front of us.
It was... awful.
Did you stop?
What...?
Look, you seem a lot brighter
than some of these yuppies.
Whatever you and your man
are looking for,
it’s not out here.
Oh, no, we’re okay.
No, I am serious.
You listen to me.
You stay off
the quieter roads,
don’t drive at night,
and if you do, don’t stop.
Don’t ever stop.
People don’t take trips.
Trips take people.
Maddie?
Hey.
You take care, Maddie.
Don’t want to see you up there
next time I’m back.
Hmm?
Making friends, huh?
Uh... yeah,
uh, I thought so.
Hey, I got something
to show you. Come on.
Uh... Yeah.
Yeah, come on.
Okay.
Hey, you want some popcorn?
Notice anything different?
You fixed it. Mm-hmm.
Yeah, I know a guy
who knows a guy
who knows a paint job guy.
Oh, wow.
How much did he charge you?
Well, he said he wanted
to reset his karmic balance,
so...
did it for free.
Wow.Mm-hmm.
Look at you networking!
Mmm.
Just like the old days.
Party’s heating up.
Mm-hmm.
Want to go for a ride?
Check out these guys.
You got to go dance.
Yeah? I might.
I mean,
I’ve had a couple IPAs,
so why not?
Tyler, come dance!
Oh, you got to go.
I hear the music,
I’ll go dance!
Hey, Mads!
Come on.
Yeah?
Yeah. All right.
All right,
we’ll go right here.
Here we go.
Which way we going?
Hey.
You done?
Yeah.
All right.
Movie’s nearly downloaded.
Cool. I’ll see you at the van.
Yeah, I’ll see you soon.
Jesus Christ.
Oh, shit.
All right.
Hmm.
Okay.
Oh!
What?
Oh, God.
All right, Ty.
Okay, come on. Please.
Come on!
Maddie, Maddie, hey!
What’s up?
Someone’s in the van.
Tyler, no, wait, baby!
It’s empty!
What?
It’s empty.
No. No, no, no.
I’m... I’m telling you, he...
He grabbed me and then--
Who did, baby?
No... What the fuck
is in the van? He’s--
He’s on... on the dashcam.
Let me show you, okay?
He’s on here.
Where do I go to the...?
No, it doesn’t record
when the van’s not moving.
It just...
What?
Just how it works, baby.
But he was in that guy’s car
the other night.
He was in his car.
Okay.
I saw it.
Look, he’s right there.
All right.
Let me see this.
Look, look!
If you just look really close,
he’s in...
There’s nobody there, baby.
All right,
what’d he look like?
Uh...
What’d he look like?
I’ll go find him.
Hey, hey, hey. No, no, no.
I... I don’t want
to sleep here. Please.
Hey...
I believe you.
Okay.
"Mistakes in life?
Just make them birds."
Bob really was
your happy place, huh?
No matter what home
I got moved to
or where I was,
watching this guy
do what he loved
was the one constant
I could count on.
I guess to me that meant
he was kind of home.
Having both your parents
under the same roof
don’t make it a home.
They look perfect, but...
behind closed doors...
people get trapped
in lives they don’t want.
But this van,
you...
was my way to escape
all of that.
Mm-hmm.
Hmm.
Oh, my God.
Mads, check it out.
No? It’s even got
your spelling.
It’s going in the bag.
It’s got to.
This place is like a goldmine
of, like,
the opposite of gold.
There’s nothing in here
of any value
and yet I want it all.
Oh, my God.
Hey.
Guilty.
In the bag?
Yeah.
In the bag.
I think we’re gonna need
a bigger van.
We’re gonna need a bigger bag,
that’s for sure.
That, too. Yeah.
So, uh, tonight,
at the campsite,
I was thinking
we’d cuddle or...
maybe just...
I can’t!
It’s this amazing spot
in the forest.
You’re gonna love it.
No. No, no, no!
Oh.
Hey.
Everything okay?
Yeah.
Good. I got something
to show you.
What?
Come on.
What is this?
Welcome to
Le Sprinter Cinema Paradiso.
Thank you.
Whatever happened back there
is way behind us,
it’s long gone.
It’s like a hundred miles
in the rearview.
I was thinking tonight we
could just be in the moment.
I mean,
it ain’t much, but it’s home.
From Roman Holiday.
Mm-hmm.Mmm.
Courtesy of the gym’s
free Wi-Fi.
Ah. Very good.
Yeah.
Well, here you go.
I love this movie.
Yes!
Ah!
My boy!
Even though we actually
get the better ending.
Oh, yeah? How’s that?
Uh, she goes home
by herself
without Joe at the end.
Hmm. Right.
But us... we get married.
Yeah.
We get to keep
doing this forever.
Forever?
I mean, eventually we’ll have
to go back to reality, right?
Well, actually, Gary,
my old boss, called me.
Oh, yeah?
He offered me my old job back.
Said I could do the thing
completely remotely,
and there’s even a pay bump.
Pretty good, right?
Yeah. Wow, um...
That’s, uh...
great.
You don’t exactly
sound thrilled.
Oh, uh...
I... I just... I don’t know
how long this is sustainable.
Do we really
want to try and find
somewhere safe
to sleep every night?
Hasn’t worked out lately.
What is going on
right now, Mads?
You haven’t even put
your ring on yet.
Suits you.
You should always
wear my clothes.
Seems I do.
It’s not
that I don’t love you.
I do. I love you.
I just...
I... I don’t love this life.
I mean...
you know I grew up
always being shuffled
from one foster home
to the next.
I never had a home home
like you did.
You know that’s not
all it’s cracked up to be.
You see?
The thing
you’re running away from
is the very thing I’ve been
searching for my entire life.
I thought
this was what you wanted.
You and me, together.
On the open road.
Unshackled from our desks.
I did. I did.
It was fun in the beginning,
but I...
All right. So, what, you...
You want to slow down?
I want to...
I want to stop.
You want to stop?
Yeah.
I’ll pack up the van.
Sell it.
No.
Head back to Brooklyn.
Maybe we can get
our lease back.
Hey, look at me.
I saw your face
at the van meet.
You love this.
Being free.
And I’d never ask you
to give up your dream.
I’m just worried...
That no matter
what direction we take...
one of us will end up--
Just glitched out.
But what were you saying?
One of us will end up what?
What just happened?
I’m not sure.
Ty.
What is that?
I don’t know, Ty.
Stay there.
Hey, man.
You saw that, right?
Yeah.
You see anything?
No.
Oh, hell no.
It stopped.
We got to move.
Yeah.
Come on. What?
The keys.
I don’t have the keys. Um...
Where...
Um...
They’re outside.
What?
They got to be.
Careful.
Come on. Come on!
Come on!
Come on, come on, go!
Go, go, go!
What the fuck is going on?
Is that what
you’ve been seeing?
Come on.
Hobo Code?
It’s the way drifters
communicated back in the day
when the roads
were first being built.
They used these symbols
to warn each other.
This is on our van.
And the car that crashed.
This thing...
it latches onto you
when you’re on the road.
Some waters for you?
Thank you.
I’ll give you two a moment.
Mm-hmm.
Some people call him...
the Passenger.
He made that guy crash.
And then we stopped.
And somehow
everywhere we’ve gone...
he’s there.
There’s got to be a way
we can shake him.
He marked the van.
Mads, look at me.
He marked the van, right?
Right?
So we just dump it, yeah?
No.
We burn the van.
No, no.
I don’t think
it works like that.
From what I read...
it’s not the van
he’s marked.
It’s us.
No.
No. No, we can shake him.
I’ll be right back.
Yeah.
Hey. Hey.
Uh...
We need to find Diane.
Who?
The nomad from the van meet.
She tried to warn me
about this.
What do you know about her?
She was headed to Flagstaff
to work
in a seafood restaurant.
There can’t be many of those.
Flagstaff is a straight shot
from here.
Let’s go.
No.
She said
not to drive at night.
We should wait.
We’re running out of daylight.
How much further?
We should be close.
Manager at the restaurant
said she was staying here.
Shit!
We can’t stop.
I know.
But we haven’t got a choice.
This thing only comes out
at dark, right?
So either we wait around...
or we get out there
and deal with this.
We’ll make it quick.
Oh, yes.
What the fuck?
Hey.
Baby!
Yeah.
Light.
Oh. Sorry.
The bolt things...
They were here, right?
Where’d they go?
They were just here.
Here, give me.
Give me the light.
Oh, you got to be kidding me.
Anything?
Careful.
Think I got them all.
Maddie?
Maddie!
Ah!
Okay, Maddie.
Maddie!
Come on.
Come on!
Ty?
Maddie! Oh, my God.
Oh. Oh, my...
Oh, my God.
I thought I lost you, baby.
It’s okay.
It’s over.
Mads! Mads! Mads!
You okay?
Oh...
Oh, God.
We have to go.
Yeah. Come on.
Yeah. Okay.
Well, the devil
Got a hold on me
She got me worried
Won’t let me be
’Cause she evil
Evil
Evil got a hold on me
Hey.
You guys know Diane Larson?
I don’t know her.
All right.
Okay.
Hi.
Hi, uh...
How’s it going?
Sorry to bother you,
but we’re looking for Diane.
Diane? Larson?
Don’t know her.
Can’t help you.
Diane. Her name is Diane.
We were told it was this camp.
We know it’s this camp.
Whatever you guys
got yourselves into,
we don’t want any part of it.
Just please point us
in the right direction.
Take your Airbnb on wheels
and get out of here.
What are you doing here?
Diane. Um...
Hi. Uh, is there some place
that we can talk
in private, please?
Why?
Something’s following us.
Oh, my God.
Get back in your van
and get the hell out of here.
What?
Now! Right away!
No, no, no, no.
No.
Let’s go, let’s go!
Come on,
everybody, pack up!
Get inside!
Lock your doors!
What are they doing?
They’re gonna lock up.
Lock themselves in.
These are good people
just trying to get by
and you chose to bring evil
into this camp?
We had
no choice, okay?
Uh, he’s been
following us everywhere.
And he’s gonna keep coming.
Well, what is it?
He’s a highwayman from hell.
An abomination.
I don’t know what it is,
but it’s unholy.
Something demonic.
It’ll have its fun by causing
wrecks on the highway.
Hungering for pain,
death, suffering.
When it marks you,
most people don’t last
more than a couple of days.
The fact
that it hasn’t killed you yet
means its enjoying the ride.
All right, so how come
you lived on the road
so long and not run into it?
Why’d it pick us?
Because you stopped.
We’re careful.
We see the warning signs
and, most importantly,
we follow the rules.
Don’t drive at night.
Whatever you do, don’t stop.
Don’t ever stop.
Hey, Diane.
What do you
want from me?
Please,
what do we do here?
There’s got to be
a way to beat it, right?
I hurt him.
You what?
The first time
he attacked me, um...
he let go when our
St. Christopher medallion
touched him.
Whoa.
There’s a story
from a long time ago.
There was this trucker
who got away.
He sought refuge in a church
outside of Grand Junction.
The St. Christopher Church.
So if you can get there,
that might be your best hope.
Okay, um...
What do we do
when we get there?
St. Christopher’s holy ground
just might weaken its powers.
Get it there,
maybe you can kill it.
If that doesn’t work,
you pray.
For salvation.
Diane, where do we find
this church?
It’s not on any map
you’ll find.
How do we get there? Come on!
It’s on a dead end road
in the middle of a desert.
And you need to know
how to read the signs.
How do we...
We don’t...
I’ll take you there.
Oh, my God, really?
Yeah.
Thank you.
We got to get
a move on though.
Get in your van. I’ll meet you
over on the other side, okay?
Run, guys!
We got to get out of here.
What is that?
Tyler, we’ve got to go.
He’s here!
Come on.
Hey, come on! Go, go!
I’m okay. Aw, shit.
Okay.
Come on, guys!
We got to drive.
No, no, no.
No! No, Diane!
Fuck. Oh, man.
Oh!
Oh, man. Oh, my God.
Oh, my God.
Oh, fuck.
I’m so scared, Ty.
It’s our fault she’s dead!
There’s no end to this.
Oh, my God.
Your hand. Uh...
Stay there.
Hey, here’s, uh...
Oh.
Hey. Hey.
Are you okay?
Yeah.
Watch your hand.
Mmm.
Sorry, I’m sorry.
That’s okay.
I’m a bit rusty.
Hey, that church!
That church.
We have to get to that church.
Right?
Yeah.
In Grand Junction.
Yeah. Yeah.
It’s not a lot to go on.
I know.
But I say we...
we drive in that direction
and try every back road
we can, right?
That’s better than waiting
around to die. Uh-huh.
I’ll gas up,
you go get us supplies.
Hey, hey.
Ty, we’re not splitting up,
okay? We’re not splitting up.
You got more
of these in the back?
Twenty-six miles from nowhere
I think I will stay
Find anything?
Just the usual
Saint Christopher stuff.
Here’s something.
"When he was younger
he wandered the roads
"with a nomadic monk.
"One morning,
"the monk suddenly
stopped in his tracks,
"terrified by a cross
on the side of the road.
"Christopher then realized
"he wasn’t traveling
with a man of God.
"This was a demon.
"The demon who takes
the form of a preacher
"as an act of blasphemy."
Diane said
he’s been around forever.
Christopher’s dark opposite.
For everything holy,
there’s something unholy.
We’re making good time.
How is it night?
I don’t know.
We got to get back to town.
Hey.
We’ll make it.
Why’d you stop?
"You have to know
how to read the signs."
Hold on.
Mads?
What are you doing?
It’ll be a one-way trip.
Just trust me.
That symbol.
It’s from the Hobo Code.
It means "this way."
But there’s no fucking
road there, baby.
Someone or something
put that symbol there
for us to see.
What if it was him?
Your sins have led you down
the path of condemnation!
And hell
is the wicked’s punishment.
Turn back, sinner, before...
What?
...before the sun rises.
Before Satan is upon you.
What the fuck? Shut up!
God!
There!
There’s something over there.
A sign. Look.
Yeah.
Go that way.
Look, look, look!
All right.
We’re on a road.
This has to be the road.
The church
has to be on this road.
Yeah.
All right.
How do we get through?
I’ll guide you.
Hey.
The church.
None of this is real.
He’s just trying to stop us.
Come on.
What is that?
No, no, no!
Keep going, baby.
Oh, shit.
Tyler!
Mads.
Get to the church.
Tyler!
Holy grounds.
Oh, fuck.
Shit.
Come on!
Oh, shit.
Happy accidents.
Maddie!
We lost everything.
Not everything.
I knew you’d save Bob.
That’s not Bob.
Ah.
What?
Oh, yeah.
I hit the S.O.S. button.
Yeah.
I’m thinking we buy a house
in a gated community.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah, sounds good.
Get a guard dog.
Yeah.
Order takeout every night.
And never fucking leave.
I am the passenger
And I ride and I ride
I ride through
the city’s backsides
I see the stars
come out of the sky
Yeah, the bright
and hollow sky
You know,
it looks so good tonight
I am the passenger
I stay under glass
I look through my window
so bright
I see the stars
come out tonight
I see the bright
and hollow sky
Over the city’s
ripped backsides
And everything
looks good tonight
Singing
La la la la, la-la-la-la
La la la la,
la-la-la-la-la-la-la
Singing
La la la la, la-la-la-la
La la la la,
la-la-la-la-la-la-la
Singing
La la la la
Well, the devil
Got a hold on me
She got me worried
Won’t let me be
’Cause she evil
Evil, evil
Evil got a hold on me
Well, them demons
Callin’ out to me
They got no mercy
For a soul in need
’Cause they evil
Evil
So damn evil
’Cause they evil
Evil
Evil got a hold on me
’Cause you’re evil
Evil
You’re so damn evil
And evil got a hold on me