(INSECTS TRILLING)
(OWL HOOTING)
(INSECTS CONTINUE TRILLING)
(RUMBLING)
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING)
RAYA:
I know what you're thinking.
A lone rider.
A dystopian world.
A land that's gone to waste.
How did this world
getso broken?
Well, that all began
500 years ago.
Kumandra.
(TRIBAL MUSIC PLAYING)
This is what we used to be.
When our land was whole,
and we lived harmoniously
alongside...
dragons.
Magical creatures
who brought us
waterand rain and peace.
It was paradise.
But then, the Druun came.
(RUMBLING)
A mindless plague
that spread like wildfire,
multiplying
as they consumed life
and turned everyone
they touched into stone.
The dragons fought for us
the best they could,
but it wasn't enough.
That's when
the Mighty Sisudatu,
the last dragon,
concentrated all her magic
into a gem and...
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC RISING)
...blasted the Druun away.
Everyone that was turned
to stone came back.
Except the dragons.
All that was left of Sisu
was her gem.
It should have been
this big inspirational moment,
where humanity united
over her sacrifice.
But instead,
people being people,
they all fought to possess
the last remnant
of dragon magic.
Borders were drawn,
Kumandra divided.
We all became enemies,
and the gem had to be hidden.
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING)
But that's not how
the world broke.
That didn't truly happen
until 500 years later,
when I came into the story.
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES)
(WHOOSHING)
(RINGS)
(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
(RAIN PATTERING)
(SOFT SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC
PLAYING)
Hmm.
(EXCLAIMS)
Huh.
Looks like someone's trying
to be clever.
(SQUEAKING)
All right, Tuk Tuk,
let's show 'em
what clever really looks like.
(TRILLING)
(WHOOSHING)
YOUNG RAYA: Tuk Tuk!
Come on!
Focus!
Thank you.
(SQUEAKS)
Hey, bud, that was awesome.
Give me some shell.
(LAUGHS) I got ya.
(WHOOSHING)
(GRUNTS)
(WHEELS CLICKING)
(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING)
(WATER TRICKLING)
(SOFT DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
(DRAMATIC MUSIC RISING)
Whoa.
Wait a second.
This feels too easy.
Chief Benja.
I know it's your job
to try and stop me,
but you won't.
BENJA: Don't mistake spirit
for skill, young one.
I promise
you will not set foot
on the Dragon Gem's
inner circle.
Not even a toe.
You might wanna take out
that blade.
You're gonna need it.
BENJA: Not today.
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING)
(WEAPONS WHOOSHING)
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC RISING)
(YOUNG RAYA GRUNTING)
(CONTINUES GRUNTING)
(PANTING)
(GRUNTS)
(GRUNTING)
(EXCLAIMS)
(PANTING)
BENJA: Boop.
Like I said, not one foot
on the inner circle.
You lost, Raya.
Did I?
Raya...
I probably should have said
two feet.
Hey, don't beat yourself up
too much, Chief Benja.
You gave it your best.
(CHUCKLES) I won't.
And it's either "Father"
or "Ba" to you.
You did good, dewdrop.
You passed the test.
-(ENCHANTING MUSIC PLAYING)
-(YOUNG RAYA GASPS)
Wow. (CHUCKLES)
The spirit of Sisu.
For generations, our family
has sworn to protect the gem.
Today, you will join
that legacy.
Raya, Princess of Heart,
my daughter,
you are now
a Guardian of the Dragon Gem.
(WATER TRICKLING)
(ENTHRALLING MUSIC PLAYING)
(BIRDS SQUAWKING)
(CHITTERING)
(SOFT UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING)
MAN: Whoa. Ah...
(BENJA LAUGHING)
Well, someone's excited.
YOUNG RAYA: Well, yeah!
I mean, anyone hoping
to steal the Dragon Gem
now has to face the fury
of the two baddest blades
in all the lands.
(LAUGHING) I'm glad
you feel prepared, dewdrop,
because I have something
important to tell you.
The other lands, they're on
their way here, as we speak.
-They are? Uh...
-(TUK TUK SQUEAKS)
Okay.
Okay, no, we can do this.
I'm ready.
I know exactly
how we'll stop them.
Really? Tell me what you know
about the other lands.
First... Tail.
A sweltering desert
with sneaky mercenaries
who fight dirty.
Second, Talon.
A floating market famous
for fast deals
and fighters
with even faster hands.
Third, Spine.
A frigid bamboo forest
guarded by
exceptionally large warriors,
and their giant axes.
(EXCLAIMS)
YOUNG RAYA: Fourth, Fang.
Our fiercest enemy.
A nation protected
by angry assassins,
and their even angrier cats.
-(HISSING)
-(TUK TUK EXCLAIMS)
Okay,
so we're gonna need some
crossbows and catapults and...
Ooh! What about
flaming catapults?
Or, how about
shrimp paste from Tail.
lemongrass from Talon,
bamboo shoots from Spine,
chilis from Fang
and palm sugar from Heart?
We'll poison them?
(LAUGHING) No, we're not going
to poison them
and we're not going
to fight them.
We're going to share a meal
with them.
-Wait, what?
-I invited them.
But they're our enemies.
They're only our enemies
because they think
the Dragon Gem
magically brings
us prosperity.
That's ridiculous.
It doesn't do that.
They assume it does,
just like we assume things
about them.
Raya, there's a reason why
each land
is named after
a part of the dragon.
We were once unified.
Harmoniously as one.
Kumandra.
That's ancient history, Ba.
But it doesn't have to be.
Listen, if we don't stop
and learn to trust
one another again,
it's only a matter of time
before we tear
each other apart.
This isn't the world
I want you to live in.
I believe that
we can be Kumandra again.
But someone has to take
the first step.
(SIGHS)
Trust me.
(DRUM ROLL PLAYING)
(WHISPERS) Things look
a little tense, Ba.
(WHISPERS) Don't worry,
I'm gonna open with a joke.
Please don't.
(LAUGHING)
I'm kidding, I'm kidding.
(IN NORMAL VOICE)
People of Tail, Talon,
Spine, and Fang,
welcome to Heart.
For far too long,
we have been enemies,
but today is a new day.
Today, we can be Kumandra
once more.
(CLAPPING)
(SARCASTICALLY)
Nice speech, Chief Benja.
But why'd you really
bring us here?
Are you gonna rob us?
Why would he need to rob us?
The land of Heart
already has everything.
Oh, it's easy to pontificate
on Kumandra
when you hold the mightiest
weapon in all the lands.
(CROWD MUTTERING)
BENJA: The gem's not a weapon.
It's a sacred relic.
SPINE CHIEF: Kumandra!
Kumandra's a joke!
TAIL CHIEF:
He brought us all this way
to talk about fairy tales.
SPINE CHIEF:
This is pointless!
(CROWD CONTINUES CHATTERING
INDISTINCTLY)
I have something to say.
Who's hungry?
(EXCLAIMS)
Oh.
(CHUCKLES)
Go ahead. It's all right.
I'm Namaari, of Fang.
Hi, Namaari. I'm Raya.
(GASPS)
Is that Sisu?
Sorry, um, yeah,
I might be a little bit
of a dragon nerd.
Hey, I'm the one wearing
the Sisu fan necklace.
Come on.
Have you eaten yet?
(SOFT UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING)
YOUNG RAYA:
(LAUGHING) Seriously?
Your mom actually said that?
Awkward.
Okay, next question.
Hand-to-hand or swords?
-Blades all day. (CHUCKLES)
-Right?
Okay, dressy or casual?
Only a monster would choose
to wear this outfit
on the regular.
(LAUGHING)
YOUNG RAYA: Uh, rice or stew?
I didn't think
that'd stump you.
Uh... This is actually
one of the first times
I've had rice in awhile.
Really?
Fang may look nice
on the outside,
but we have some pretty
big holes on the inside.
Oh.
Sorry. Didn't mean
to bring it down.
So, where were we?
We both have single parents
who are terrible
at telling jokes.
We're both warrior women
who despise uncomfortable
formal wear.
And we're both Sisu superfans.
(LAUGHS) Yeah.
You know, Fang legend says
she's still out there.
Sisu? You're kidding, right?
Wanna see something?
(GASPS AND WHISPERS)
Are you supposed to have that?
(SCOFFS) No.
According to this,
after the Mighty Sisu
blasted away all the Druun,
she fell into the water
and floated downstream.
Legends say she's now sleeping
at the river's end.
But which river?
There's, like, hundreds.
I don't know.
But if we could find it,
could you imagine?
A dragon back in the world.
Things could be
so much better.
YOUNG RAYA: Yeah.
Maybe we really could be
Kumandra again.
Here.
Whoa.
Really?
From one dragon nerd
to another.
(SOFT SENTIMENTAL MUSIC
PLAYING)
Hmm.
Hey.
Come with me, dep la.
I wanna show you something.
(RUMBLING)
(TUK TUK TRILLING)
(GASPS SOFTLY)
The spirit of Sisu.
I can feel it.
It's the last bit
of dragon magic
left in the whole world.
YOUNG NAMAARI: I see why
Heart guards it so closely.
Thank you, dep la.
You've been very helpful.
-(GRUNTS)
-(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
(YOUNG RAYA GASPING)
In a different world, maybe
we could have been friends,
but I have to do
what's right for Fang.
(GRUNTING)
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(TUK TUK SQUEAKING)
(GRUNTING)
(GROANS)
-(FIRES)
-(YOUNG RAYA EXCLAIMS)
Chief Virana, I'm so glad
Fang accepted our invitation.
(FLARE WHISTLING)
(OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING)
Huh?
There is no way
you're taking Sisu's gem.
Sorry. It's Fang's now.
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING)
(GASPS)
(GRUNTS)
(GRUNTING)
-(CONTINUES GRUNTING)
-(BLADES CLASHING)
(EXCLAIMING)
You will not set foot on
the Dragon Gem's inner circle.
FEMALE SPINE WARRIOR:
What's going on?
SPINE CHIEF: What is this?
FEMALE SPINE WARRIOR: Fang's
making a play for the gem!
No! Spine should have the gem!
TAIL CHIEF:
Not if we get to it first!
MAN: Our blades say different.
(CROWD CHATTERING
INDISTINCTLY)
Listen to me!
We have a choice.
We can tear each other apart,
or we can come together
and build a better world.
It's not too late.
I still believe
we can be Kumandra again.
(SENTIMENTAL MUSIC PLAYING)
(GRUNTS PAINFULLY)
Ba!
-TAIL CHIEF: Out of my way!
-(INDISTINCT EXCLAIMING)
SPINE CHIEF:
The gem belongs to Spine!
SPINE CHIEF: Give me the gem!
(SHATTERING)
(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
(BENJA GRUNTING AND PANTING)
No... No...
(BOTH GASPING)
-(RUMBLING)
-(CROWD EXCLAIMING INDISTINCTLY)
(CRASHING)
(SCREECHING)
Druun.
(MAN WHIMPERING)
(DRUUN SCREECHING)
(BENJA GRUNTING)
There's still magic in them!
-SPINE CHIEF: Get the pieces!
-No! (GRUNTS)
(INDISTINCT EXCLAIMING)
Ba! Come on, we have to go!
(BOTH GRUNTING)
They're repelled by water.
Hurry! Get to the river!
(BENJA GRUNTS)
YOUNG RAYA:
Ba, get up! Come on!
Please, we have
to keep moving.
Get up!
(BENJA BREATHING HEAVILY)
Ba! We don't have time!
(MAN WHIMPERING)
(WOMAN SCREAMS)
Stand up! I'll help...
Raya, you have to listen.
You are the Guardian
of the Dragon Gem.
Ba, why are you saying this?
-(CRASHES)
-(YOUNG RAYA GRUNTS)
There's still light in this.
There's still hope.
No! We can make it together.
(CRYING) You're okay.
BENJA: Raya.
Don't give up on them.
I love you, my dewdrop.
Ba?
-(BENJA GRUNTS)
-YOUNG RAYA: (EXCLAIMS) No!
(DRUUN SCREECHING
AND RUMBLING)
(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
(YOUNG RAYA GASPING)
Ba!
(GASPING AND WHIMPERING)
Ba.
(WIND WHISTLING)
(WIND BLOWING)
(SOFT SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC
PLAYING)
(KNOCKING)
(TUK TUK GRUNTS QUESTIONINGLY)
(SOFT TENSE MUSIC PLAYING)
(EXHALES)
Please let this be it.
-(TUK TUK GRUNTS)
-RAYA: Whoa!
What are you doing,
you big fur bug?
Hey, buddy, focus.
Eyes forward, Tuk Tuk.
Good boy.
You're so easily distracted.
-(DRUUN SCREECHING)
-(RAYA EXCLAIMS)
(GRUNTING)
(GRUNTING AND PANTING)
(GRUNTS)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(TUK TUK GRUMBLES)
-(RAYA GRUNTING)
-(TUK TUK GRUMBLING)
-(BOTH GRUNT)
-(THUDS)
RAYA: You're getting a little
too big for this, bud.
(GRUMBLES)
(EXHALES)
Six years of searching
and we end up
at a literal shipwreck.
(SIGHS)
That's not a bad sign, is it?
(TUK TUK GRUMBLES)
(SOFT SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC
PLAYING)
(GRUMBLES)
(SOFT SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC
CONTINUES)
(FLAME CRACKLING)
Sisudatu...
Um...
I don't know
if you're listening.
I've searched every river
to find you,
and now I'm here
at the very last one.
Look, there's not
a lot of us left,
and we really...
We really need your help.
If I can be honest,
I really need your help.
I made a mistake.
I trusted someone
I shouldn't have, and...
(SIGHS)
...now the world's broken.
(BREATHES DEEPLY)
Sisudatu...
(CRIES SOFTLY)
I just really, really
want my ba back.
(CRIES)
Please.
(EXHALES)
Okay...
(BREATHES DEEPLY)
Here goes everything.
(SOFT SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC
PLAYING)
(CHANTING) Suvaa de draa sim
Mandra de draa lim
Bavaa de draa
Tomben
(FLAME CRACKLING)
(SOFT SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC
CONTINUES)
(WATER TRICKLING)
(GRUNTS)
(TUK TUK EXCLAIMING)
I know, buddy,
I haven't forgot...
(GASPS)
(TRIUMPHANT MUSIC PLAYING)
(TUK TUK EXCLAIMING)
(TRIUMPHANT MUSIC RISING)
Oh, my... Where am I?
Pengu? Amba? Pranee?
Are you here?
Oh, Mighty Sisu.
Who said that?
-(WHOOSHES)
-(RAYA EXCLAIMS)
Hello?
-(MUFFLED GROANING)
-SISU: Oh!
Oh, I'm sorry.
I didn't see you there. (LAUGHS)
Not too bad.
Just a little dusty.
Let me get that for ya.
(LAUGHING)
RAYA: Sisu?
You are Sisu?
And you're people.
What's your name?
Raya. I'm Raya.
And you're not made of stone,
which means...
(EXCITEDLY) It worked!
We did it!
You hear that, Pengu?
It worked!
I didn't mess it up!
-Is that food?
-(RAYA GRUNTS)
I was so focused
on saving the world,
I forgot to have
breakfast today.
Today?
When exactly
do you think today is?
Tuesday.
(GURGLING)
I mean...
(FAKE EXCLAIMING) Mmm.
What is this delightful
culinary treat?
It's jackfruit jerky.
I dried it myself.
Well, compliments to the chef.
(LAUGHING)
Wanna finish this, Skippy?
(TUK TUK GRUMBLES)
RAYA: Uh...
Sisu, there are a few things
I need to catch you up on.
Oh, yeah?
(SHOUTING) You broke it?
(TUK TUK WHINES)
Oh, oh. Oh, my. This is bad.
This is bad.
I've been asleep
for 500 years,
you brought back
the Druun,
and none of my brothers
and sisters came back.
Why didn't they come back?
I don't know.
Also, you broke the gem!
But I still have
a big chunk of it, though.
Is that supposed
to make me feel better?
If you lost a puppy,
and I said...
(MOCKINGLY) "Well, we still
have a big chunk of it!"
Would that make you
feel better?
Can't you just make
another one?
No, I can't just
"make another one."
But you're a dragon.
I'm gonna be real
with you, all right?
I'm not, like,
the best dragon, ya know?
But you saved the world.
I did do that. That's true.
But have you ever done
like a group project,
but there's, like,
that one kid
who didn't pitch in as much,
but still ended up
with the same grade?
Yeah, I wasn't the one
who actually made the gem.
I just turned it in.
(ENCHANTING MUSIC PLAYING)
Whoa. Uh...
You're glowing.
Oh, thank you.
I use aloe and river slime
to maintain my...
RAYA: No, no. Look!
Oh! This is my little sister
Amba's magic.
I got the glow!
Your little sister's magic?
Yeah, every dragon
has a unique magic.
Okay, what's yours?
I'm a really strong swimmer.
Wait, wait, wait,
you touched this gem piece
and it gave you powers.
You know what
this means, right?
I no longer need
a night light?
What? No!
You're still connected to the gem's magic,
and that means
you can still use it
to save the world.
If we can get
all the other gem pieces...
-I can reassemble it...
-...you can reassemble it...
BOTH: ...and boom
the Druun away!
And bring my ba back?
And bring
all of Kumandra back.
(WIND BLOWING)
(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
(GROWLING)
(SOFT SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC
PLAYING)
Princess Namaari,
the Tail lands
are infested with Druun.
Benja's daughter is as good
as stone out here.
(SCOFFS) Retrieving
some useless dragon scroll
isn't worth the risk.
(EXCLAIMS)
Anyone else wanna question
why we're out here?
(CATS WHIMPERING)
-(CATS ROARING)
-(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
RAYA:
Okay, so here's the sitch.
After the gem broke,
each piece was taken
by one of the chiefs
of the five lands,
Fang, Heart, Spine, Talon,
and Tail.
Where we are now.
SISU: Wow. So many questions.
First one,
why am I wearing this?
Well, we don't want
to attract attention.
Oh, you definitely chose
the right hat for that.
So, what makes you think
the Tail chief's here?
(GASPS)
-(EXCLAIMS)
-(CRASHES)
Because this place
didn't just booby-trap itself.
SISU: This doesn't make sense.
None of this
would stop a Druun.
RAYA: It's not to stop Druun.
It's to stop people.
SISU: Hmm.
-(SOFT THUD)
-(GRUNTING)
What?
Why are you looking at me
like that?
(CHUCKLING NERVOUSLY)
Nothing.
I'm just not used to
seeing dragons.
Impressed, huh? Wait until
you see my backstroke.
I'm wicked
when I hit that liquid.
I got water skills that kill.
I slaughter
when I hit the water.
I'm, like, really good
at swimming, through rhyme.
I was trying to make that...
That I'm really good
at swim...
I'm a good swimmer,
is basically what I'm...
Okay, um,
we need to keep going.
-(GASPS) Oh, no!
-What? What is it?
We forgot to bring a gift
for the Tail chief.
I'm sorry. A gift?
Yeah. A gift says,
"You can trust me,
can I trust you?"
(GASPS)
Aw. Hey there,
little fella.
(LAUGHS)
This beetle's got a booty.
Uh... Careful.
It's a Toot N Boom.
-Why is it called a...
-(TOOTS)
-(EXPLODES)
-(BOTH GRUNT)
Got it. Noted. Makes sense.
(CHUCKLES SHEEPISHLY)
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING)
RAYA: Uh...
You have to admit though,
these bug booties
are kind of cute.
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES)
I'd say
we found the Tail chief.
SISU: What happened to her?
From the looks of it,
she was hoarding the gem
and became a victim
of her own traps.
Well, you gotta admire
her commitment.
(CLANGS)
Okay. Hold on.
(GRUNTS)
Oh, we were doing
a jumpy thing!
So sorry. My bad.
-(GRUNTING)
-I get it now. I'm with it.
(BOTH EXCLAIM)
(RAYA GRUNTS)
Sisu...
don't.
-(GRUNTS)
-(CRACKS)
(GASPS)
(TENSE MUSIC PLAYING)
(EXHALES IN RELIEF)
Two down, three to go.
(ENCHANTING MUSIC PLAYING)
(SISU EXCLAIMS)
I just shapechanged!
Into people!
Dragons can do that?
This was my sister
Pranee's thing.
Look at my people arms
and my people face.
Look how close my butt is
to my head.
Now that
you don't have to hide me,
getting the rest of the gems
is gonna be a breeze.
Yeah, well, this one was easy,
but the rest of them
are being held
by a bunch
of no-good binturis.
NAMAARI: Binturi?
That's not a very nice way
to describe an old friend.
(CAT GROWLING)
Namaari.
What's drippin', dep la?
Oh, I see you've finally
made a new friend.
And here I was worried
you were gonna end up
becoming a cat lady
like me.
(GROWLS)
Something tells me
you're not besties.
Stealing Dragon Gem pieces,
are we? Why?
What can I say?
Bling is my thing.
Hmm.
I gotta admit, Raya,
until a few months ago,
I thought you were stone.
But then, someone stole
Fang's dragon scroll.
Oh, is that why
you're chasing me?
And here I thought
it was because you missed me.
Are you really looking
for Sisu?
(LAUGHING)
What are you, 12?
Yeah, I actually was looking
for Sisu.
Oh, and guess what?
I found her.
Say hi, Sisu.
Hi!
It's very nice to meet you,
and I love your hair
and your cats' hair.
(CHUCKLES)
Take them.
(GRUNTS)
(EXCLAIMING)
(SISU EXCLAIMING)
RAYA: Run!
(SISU PANTING AND GRUNTING)
Not like that! Two legs!
SISU: Right!
-(PANTING)
-(GRUNTING)
(EXCLAIMS)
(CAT GROWLS)
(GRUNTS)
(NAMAARI GRUNTING)
(TENSE MUSIC PLAYING)
(SISU PANTING AND WHIMPERING)
RAYA: Tuk Tuk! Roll!
(GRUNTS)
SISU: Whoa!
(WHIMPERING AND EXCLAIMING)
-RAYA: Jump!
-(SISU EXCLAIMS)
(BOTH GRUNT)
Who was that girl?
That's Namaari.
She's the backstabbing binturi
that broke the world.
(TENSE MUSIC PLAYING)
Wow, those cats
are really fast, huh?
What do cats and Druun
have in common?
Um... They have no souls?
And they both hate water.
-Oh.
-Hold on!
(TUK TUK TRILLING)
(SPLASHES)
(GRUMBLES)
(GRUNTS ANNOYEDLY)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
Hello? Is anybody here?
(EXCLAIMS)
(WHIZZING)
Welcome to the world-famous
Shrimp-orium.
My name is Boun.
I'll be your server today.
Would you like to hear
our daily specials?
Yes, please!
We got shrimp, we got congee.
We got a shrimp congee
that won't quit.
The captain,
where is the captain?
Let me go get him.
What's up, my new customers?
I'm Captain Boun,
the owner, chef,
and chief financial officer
of the Shrimp-orium.
How can I help you?
Well, I'm Sisu and...
And we need
to get to Talon now.
I'm sorry. The Shrimp-orium
is not a water taxi.
-(COINS JINGLE)
-Toi, that's a lot of jade!
Half now, half when we arrive
in Talon. Deal?
Clasp onto your congee.
Today's special is
to go.
Uh, Captain Boun?
Does this thing go any faster?
(CATS SNARLING)
Whoa! You didn't tell me
Fang was after you!
This is gonna cost you extra!
Don't worry, I got it.
(SPLASHES)
What is she doing?
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING)
(BOTH EXCLAIMING)
(EXCLAIMS)
What is happening?
My friend's
a really strong swimmer.
(CATS SNARLING)
Bye-bye, binturi.
Princess Namaari,
if they're after gem pieces,
their next stop
would be Talon.
We're not following them
to Talon.
We're going back to Fang.
I need to speak
with Chief Virana.
(CAT GROWLS)
(SOFT MUSIC PLAYING)
(ENTHRALLING MUSIC PLAYING)
(IN HUSHED TONE) Sisu? Sisu?
SISU: (HAPPILY) Ah!
RAYA: Please get out of there.
I'm a water dragon.
This is water.
It's sort of my thing.
You wanna come in?
RAYA: Someone could see you.
Oh. Do you mean Captain Pop
and Lock over there?
What, are you scared
he's gonna challenge me
to a dance battle?
(RAYA GASPS)
(UTENSILS CLATTERING)
(LAUGHS)
(RAYA GRUNTS)
Sisu, I saw people
lose their minds
over a Dragon Gem.
Can you imagine what they'd do
over an actual dragon?
Look, we need you
to make this all work.
Until we have all the gems,
you have to stay human.
Please.
Wow, you really
got some trust issues.
Look, my father
blindly trusted people,
and now, he's stone.
Hey, we'll get your ba back.
I got you, girl.
Come on, who's your dragon?
I mean, human. Because
I'm gonna be a human until...
Yeah, you... You get it.
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
(BOUN GRUNTS)
Okay, who's hungry?
SISU: Oh, I am.
Two house specials.
How spicy would you like it?
Hot, hotter,
or Boun-goes-the-dynamite?
-Bring on the heat!
-Yeah, no.
No, I don't think so.
Uh, what are you doing?
(WHISPERING) We don't
know him. It could be poison.
(IN HUSHED TONE)
Why would he poison us?
Yeah, why would I poison you?
(IN NORMAL VOICE)
First, to get my jade purse,
second, to steal my sword,
and third, I don't know,
to kidnap my Tuk Tuk.
(TUK TUK STARTS)
All good points,
but if this is poison...
(SLURPING)
Mmm!
...you're gonna die happy.
Yeah, thanks,
but we got our own eats.
(GRUNTS)
(SLURPING)
This is delicious.
By the way, not poison.
But it's...
(GASPING)
It's hot. Ooh, it's hot!
-It's hot! It's really hot!
-(RAYA LAUGHING)
Oh, my! Oh! Water!
Boun? Captain Boun?
We need water on deck!
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING)
(SOFT DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
(EERIE MUSIC PLAYING)
(DRUUN SCREECHING)
(LOW GROWLING)
(TUK TUK WHIMPERS)
I know, buddy.
You know, during the day,
you can almost forget
they're here,
but at night...
(SCREECHING)
This is why
I never leave the boat.
You're a smart kid.
(SCREECHING CONTINUES
DISTANTLY)
What are Druun, anyways?
SISU: A plague.
Born from human discord.
They've always been here.
Waiting for a moment
of weakness to attack.
They're like
the opposite of dragons.
Instead of bringing water
and life to the world,
they're like a relentless fire
that consumes everything
in its wake
until there's nothing left
except ash and stone.
They took my family.
(SOFT SENTIMENTAL MUSIC
PLAYING)
They took mine, too.
(BREATHES DEEPLY)
(WATER RIPPLING GENTLY)
Looks like we're here.
So, where are you guys heading
after Talon?
I might be heading there, too.
I mean, for a fee, of course.
RAYA: (LAUGHS) Of course.
SISU: Wow! What a smart way
to Druun-proof your house.
Build right on the water.
People of Talon are geniuses.
Yeah. Talon may look nice,
but it's a hotspot for
pickpockets and con artists.
Lucky for me. Empty pockets!
Okay, so here's the good news.
I know where the gem piece is.
The bad news?
It's being held by
the notorious Chief of Talon,
Dang Hai.
What Dang Hai lacks in style,
he makes up in mean.
(SMIRKS) Hmm.
SISU: Gotcha.
Now, we're just gonna have to
turn up the charm.
Let's go get him a gift.
Sisu, I think maybe
it's safer for you
to stay here on the boat.
What?
Without you, we can't
put the gem back together.
But I wanna help.
I know, and you will.
By staying safe.
I'll be back
before you know it.
If you see any hungry faces,
send 'em my way.
You got it, Captain.
(UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING)
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
(CHITTERS)
All right,
there's Dang Hai's house.
No detours
till we score that Dragon Gem.
(BABY CRYING)
Whoa. What in the...
Uh... (CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY)
Okay.
-Hey, baby, toddler, thing...
-(COOING)
RAYA:
...whatever you're called.
It's really late.
What are you doing out here?
Where are your parents?
Hey, uh, whose baby...
-What? Ongis?
-(CHITTERS)
Drop 'em!
(CHITTERING)
-(EXCLAIMS)
-RAYA: Ow! (GRUNTS PAINFULLY)
-(EXCLAIMING)
-(GIGGLING)
Really? A con-baby?
(GRUNTS IN FRUSTRATION)
SISU: Ah, this is giving me
bad feels.
Chief Dang Hai
does not sound like
someone you could smooth talk.
And Raya
didn't even bring a gift.
That's it. I'm going shopping.
Oh, wait.
I don't have any money.
BOUN: You're an adult.
You could just put it
on credit.
Oh... Uh, what's credit?
It's kinda like a promise.
You take what you want now,
and you promise
you'll pay it back later.
Pay it back later? Huh!
What an amazing concept.
Thanks, Captain Boun.
-(LIGHTHEARTED MUSIC PLAYING)
-(INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
SISU: I'll be buying this
with credit.
Oh, Dang Hai's
gonna love this!
Credit, please.
Oh, I like that. Uh, yeah,
I'll be using credit, yes.
I love credit!
MALE MERCHANT: Hey, you!
Are you going
to pay for any of that?
Oh! (CHUCKLING)
Right, right.
No, this is on credit.
Yeah, I'm gonna pay it
back later.
Pay us back later?
We don't know you.
You have no credit here.
-Pay us right now.
-Now?
(NERVOUSLY)
I don't have anything,
but if I could just find
my girl Raya,
she has a sword, dried eats,
two Dragon Gem pieces.
No, we don't!
What? Who said that?
You better pay up, binturi.
This isn't a charity.
Who do you think
you're stealing from?
(EXCLAIMING)
Get away from her!
Can't you see
she's new in town?
(AFFECTIONATELY)
Come, dear. Don't be afraid.
WOMAN: It's okay.
(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
-(LAUGHING)
-(TUK TUK GRUNTS)
(EXCLAIMS)
MALE MERCHANT: Hey, watch out!
(GRUNTS)
-(GRUNTING)
-(WEAPON WHOOSHING)
(EXCLAIMS)
(EXCLAIMING IN SLOW MOTION)
(MOUTHING) Bye!
(GIGGLING)
(DRAMATIC MUSIC CONTINUES)
(EXCLAIMS) Diaper!
(BLOWS RASPBERRY)
(CRASHING)
(THUD)
(ONGI SQUEAKING)
(PUNCHES)
Thanks.
So, it's none of my business,
but using your baby charm
to rip people off...
(EXCLAIMS INDIGNANTLY)
-...is super sketchy.
-(HUFFS)
(GROWLS)
All right,
where is your family?
(BLOWS RASPBERRY)
(COMMANDS) Mm.
RAYA: Oh...
Right.
Hey.
How would you like to earn
some honest loot?
Gah?
(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYS)
(LAUGHING AND TAUNTING)
(CHITTERING AND SQUEAKING)
(EXCLAIMING)
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING)
All right, Dang Hai,
I'll take that
Dragon Gem piece.
Whoa! I'm not Dang Hai.
I'm Chai, the flower guy.
Where is Dang Hai?
(CHUCKLES)
He's right over there.
What? Who has his gem piece?
(CHUCKLES)
The most vicious chief
Talon has ever seen.
(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYS)
Those folks were,
like, crazy mad.
I just wanted
to bring some gifts
to the Talon chief Dang Hai.
Is that who
you're looking for, dear?
(GASPS EXCITEDLY)
I know exactly where he is.
You do?
Mm-hmm. I will take you there.
See? That's what I've been
trying to tell my girl Raya.
And she's all like,
"You can't trust people."
"Don't talk to anyone."
"I only eat terrible foods
I dried myself."
(LAUGHS) Come, dear.
Chief Dang Hai
is just outside the city,
beyond the gates.
SISU: Away from
the water, huh? Wow.
He really likes living
on the edge.
Hi there, Dang Hai.
Um, I'm Sisu,
and I've come here
to offer you some...
(EERIE MUSIC PLAYING)
Uh...
-(LOUD RUMBLING)
-(DRUUN SCREECHING)
Now, you're gonna tell me
where I can find
those other Dragon Gem pieces,
or I'll have to leave you
outside with that thing.
Take your pick.
But I... I trusted you.
Big mistake.
You better talk fast.
-It looks hungry.
-(DRUUN SCREECHING)
SISU: No. No, no. No, no, no!
Raya!
DANG HU: Stop her!
RAYA: Sisu, I told you
to stay on the boat.
SISU: Sorry!
Hold on to this for me,
will ya?
-(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
-(FOG HISSING)
(EXCLAIMING)
RAYA: Fog?
SISU: Yeah. That was
my brother Jagan's magic.
RAYA: Okay.
Three down, two to go.
All right, Captain Boun,
next stop, Spine...
(EXCLAIMS) Aah!
(UTENSILS CLATTERING)
Thanks for the new customers!
Yeah, I sort of promised
to buy them
all the congee they could eat.
Well, we're stuck with them
for a while
'cause ongis have
nine stomachs.
Oh, toi.
I can't believe it.
That old lady
was really gonna hurt me.
Well, I'm sorry, Sisu,
but that's what
the world is now.
You can't trust anyone.
-(SIGHS DEEPLY)
-(MUMBLING)
Does that include babies?
-Uh, well...
-She's so cute.
I mean, look at those cheeks.
-(GRUNTS)
-(MUMBLING)
(IN MUFFLED VOICE)
Hi, I'm Sisu.
(MUMBLING UNINTELLIGIBLY)
(LAUGHING)
She loves my face.
Yeah, watch out
she doesn't steal your teeth.
Here, let me help you.
-SISU: Oh, that's so sweet.
-(CON-BABY MUMBLING)
SISU: Okay, that's, uh...
That's too much sweet...
Too much sweetness.
It's too much!
(SCREECHING)
(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
GENERAL ATITAYA: Chief Virana,
we're running out of room.
We need to expand
to the mainland.
VIRANA: And how do you propose
we handle the Druun,
General Atitya?
Without proper protection,
it would be a death sentence
for our people.
I might have a solution
for that, Mother.
(GASPS SOFTLY)
My little morning mist...
Oh, it's good to see you home.
I located Raya.
She's out stealing gem pieces.
What?
I'd like to take
the royal army
and intercept her in Spine.
(SCOFFS) Well,
if she's going into Spine,
I doubt there'll be much left
of her to intercept.
She's more capable
than you realize.
We have to stop her.
(VIRANA SIGHS)
Walk with me.
(SOFT MUSIC PLAYING)
Look around.
We made all this
by making smart decisions,
not emotional ones.
We are safe.
Our canal protects us
from those monsters.
I don't think it's wise
to risk yourself
when you don't have to.
But you heard the general.
We're running out of space.
We need to expand.
If we had all the gem pieces,
we could do that safely.
You're right.
This isn't
an emotional decision.
It's the only decision
we can make
to secure Fang's future.
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
Namaari, you're truly growing
into the leader
I raised you to be.
General Atitya,
ready the royal army
-for my daughter's command.
-(THUMPS)
Thank you, Mother.
I won't let you down.
(OBJECTS SMASHING
AND CLATTERING)
(YELLING) Hey! Stop eating!
(ONGIS CHITTERING)
(STARTS)
RAYA: (EXCLAIMS) Whoa!
Sorry, buddy, I got this.
BOUN: Did you just throw
a shrimp at me?
That's not even edible!
-RAYA: Hey!
-BOUN: Don't look at me...
RAYA: Uh... Hey, guys?
BOUN: ...like that,
you fuzzy garbage can!
Do you wanna play
hide-and-seek?
All right. Ready?
One.
Two.
-Thanks.
-Two and a half.
Three.
Remind me to never have kids.
Being people is hard.
Yep.
Six.
Seven.
You have small heads.
No tails.
You lie to get what you want,
like the Talon chief
back there.
Yeah, well,
the world's broken.
You can't trust anyone.
Or maybe the world's broken
because you don't
trust anyone.
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
You sound just like my ba.
Well, he sounds like
a smart man.
Yeah, he was.
I really wanted
to believe him.
I really wanted to believe
that we could be
Kumandra again.
And we can.
Literally thousands of people
turned to stone
would argue otherwise.
That doesn't mean
you shouldn't try.
And I did.
And you know what happened?
I got kicked in the back
by someone who gave me a gift.
Look around.
We're a world
of orphans because
people couldn't stop fighting
over a gem.
Wanna know why other dragons
didn't come back?
It's because
people don't deserve them.
But you can change that.
No, Sisu, I am done trying.
Kumandra is a fairy tale.
The only thing
important to me now
is bringing my ba back.
Um... I think we're in Spine.
(SOFT DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
-Sisu!
-(SISU GRUNTS)
BOUN: Hey, my congee!
RAYA: Don't go anywhere.
I'll be right back.
(DRAMATIC MUSIC RISING)
Sisu! Come back! Please!
What... What are you doing?
SISU: I'm going to show you
that you're wrong!
How? By getting squashed by
a bunch of Spine rage-heads?
No.
By proving to you
that if you wanna get
someone's trust,
you have to give
a little trust first.
-Wait, Sisu, don't...
-(KNOCKER CLANGS)
(BOTH EXCLAIM)
SISU: In hindsight,
maybe I was a little hasty,
but, uh, who's hungry?
No? I'll leave you alone.
(RAYA GRUNTING)
Okay, where are we?
(FIRE CRACKLING)
(GASPS SOFTLY)
Interesting choice of digs.
-(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
-(BOTH GASP)
(DOOR CRASHES OPEN)
(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
You two must be
dung of brain
to think you could steal
Spine's Dragon Gem.
(CLANGS)
Gem? (SCOFFS)
Who said anything about gems?
We have no interest in gems.
(GEMS CLATTERING)
Okay, yeah, I can see how
that makes me look
like a liar.
Actually, I think
it was the lying
that made you look
like a liar.
(LAUGHING VILLAINOUSLY)
(BOTH LAUGHING)
I'm not sure what's funny.
Your fear
is like delectable nectar
feeding the tum-tum
of my soul.
It's good.
Tastes like... (SNIFFS) mango.
Oh. I love mango.
Of course you love mango!
Only a tongue-less
cretin wouldn't.
Oh, toi!
It's been such a long time
since I've last peered
into the eyes
of a trembling enemy.
Where has the time gone?
It's been so long.
(SENTIMENTAL MUSIC PLAYING)
He seems lonely.
No! I'm not lonely.
-I'm a Spine warrior.
-(THUMPS CHEST)
I was born and bred to do
only one thing.
To invoke fear
and to crush the skulls
of my enemies!
That's actually two things.
-(GROWLS AGGRESSIVELY)
-(SISU EXCLAIMING)
(LAUGHING)
Look at your face. (LAUGHING)
Hey. What do you plan on doing
with us?
Oh, it's gonna be bad.
Horrifying!
It'll take me two weeks
to clean up!
You have no idea, do you?
Yes, I do.
I'm formulating this
gruesome plan in my head...
Makes me sick
just thinking about it.
You... You just wait.
Until then, why don't you
just hang around?
Good one, huh?
(LAUGHING)
-(TUK TUK EXCLAIMING)
-(TONG GRUNTS)
(CON-BABY EXCLAIMS)
(ONGIS CHITTERING)
(TONG GRUNTS)
(TUK TUK GROWLING)
Huh?
(SNARLING IN BABY VOICE)
A little one?
All right!
Phew! Good work, Captain Boun!
-Fang's here!
-What?
NAMAARI: People of Spine,
we are hunting for Raya,
a fugitive from Heart!
Send her out,
or we're coming in!
You're the only one here?
My people battled the Druun
with much valor,
but lost.
Okay.
But the Fang gang's here
for me, not for you,
so, um,
if I can distract them,
then you guys
can get out of here.
You're gonna fight
an entire army?
No, I'm just gonna stall them.
Look, I know how to push
Namaari's buttons.
And once you guys are clear,
I'm out of there.
(SIGHS)
What's your name?
The moniker given to me
is Tong.
Okay, Tong, look,
you don't know me,
and I don't know you,
but I'm sure that
you know a back door
or a way outta here,
and it's really important that
my friends stay safe, okay?
So, I am sincerely asking you,
will you help us?
Please.
(GRUNTS IN AGREEMENT)
(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
RAYA: (BREATHES DEEPLY) Okay.
Note to self,
don't die.
Burn them out.
(GATE UNLOCKING)
(DRAMATIC MUSIC RISING)
Hey there, Princess Undercut.
Fancy meeting you here.
NAMAARI: You
and the Dragon Gem pieces
are coming with me.
Hmm.
My sword here says we're not.
(WEAPONS READYING)
Yeah, I knew you couldn't
handle rolling solo.
You're nothing
without your band.
Stand down.
This shouldn't take long.
(LAUGHS)
(WEAPON WHOOSHING)
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC RISING)
-(BOTH GRUNTING)
-(WEAPONS CLANGING)
(GRUNTING CONTINUES)
(EXCLAIMS)
Did you need that, dep la?
(GRUNTING)
Nah.
(GRUNTS) Looks like somebody's
been taking classes.
(GRUNTS)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(EXCLAIMING)
-(GRUNTING)
-(GRUNTS PAINFULLY)
-(EXCLAIMS)
-(GRUNTS)
(GASPS)
(GRUNTING)
(GRUNTS)
Why are you stealing
gem pieces?
(PANTING)
(SARCASTICALLY) Oh, I'm just
trying to get a matching set.
(GRUNTING)
-(GRUNTS LOUDLY)
-(GRUNTS PAINFULLY)
(THUDS)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(GRIMACING) You didn't happen
to bring Fang's gem, did you?
(BREATHES HEAVILY)
(GRUNTS)
-(GRUNTS LOUDLY)
-(EXCLAIMS PAINFULLY)
(TENSE MUSIC PLAYING)
(GRUNTS) No? Never mind.
I'll just swing by
and grab it later.
(CHUCKLES)
Oh, I'm gonna enjoy this.
-(LOUD RUMBLING)
-(WARRIORS EXCLAIMING)
(GASPS)
(ROARING)
(WARRIORS EXCLAIMING)
(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(ROARING)
(SOFT MUSIC PLAYING)
(GRUNTS PAINFULLY)
Yep, she's a dragon.
Let's go.
Come on!
(SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES)
(WATER RIPPLING)
(GRUNTS SOFTLY)
Did you just hit me
with a shrimp tail?
When were you gonna tell us
she was Sisu?
Well, technically,
you always knew she was Sisu.
Seriously?
Why are you here,
divine water dragon?
Isn't that obvious, big guy?
My girl Raya and I
are gonna fix the world.
Bring everyone back.
You're gonna
bring everyone back?
I wanna help.
(SIGHS) I'm sorry,
I can't let you do that.
It's too dangerous.
You're not the only one
who lost family to the Druun.
(SENTIMENTAL MUSIC PLAYING)
Please.
Let me help you.
(CON-BABY MUMBLING)
(GEM RINGING)
I too wish to join
this fellowship
of Druun butt-kickery!
(ENTHRALLING MUSIC PLAYING)
(RAIN PATTERING)
My big brother Pengu's magic.
(ENTHRALLING MUSIC CONTINUES)
(ENTHRALLING MUSIC RISING)
(LAUGHING)
(GIGGLING)
(ENTHRALLING MUSIC SWELLS)
(SPLASHES)
(LAUGHING)
RAYA: All right, Captain Boun.
To Fang.
BOUN: You got it!
(MUSIC CONTINUES SOFTLY)
(WATER RIPPLING)
All right, everyone,
here's the plan.
The last gem piece is in Fang,
the most heavily guarded
of the five lands.
Now, they're protected
by an artificial canal
that separates them
from the rest of the world.
The only way in or out
is by water.
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING)
(EXCLAIMING)
RAYA: Luckily for us,
we have a magic water dragon.
Now, the palace will be
swarmingwith Fang soldiers.
To sneak past them,
we'll need to...
I got this, guys.
I'll take care
of the first wave.
(GRUNTING)
BOUN: Tong will follow up
with hisgiant axe
of bad-axery.
(TONG EXCLAIMING)
BOUN: And then come the ongis
and that crazy con-baby...
(CON-BABY EXCLAIMING)
BOUN: ...who will toss the gem
to the Mighty Sisudatu.
(BOUN MIMICKING SISU GROWLING)
And then, bye-bye, binturis.
(BOUN MIMICKING EXPLOSIONS)
-Super flow plan, am I right?
-(CON-BABY CLAPPING)
Uh, no. Yeah, that's not flow.
That's a clog.
I agree.
Here's my plan.
We infiltrate Fang,
confront Namaari,
and offer her something nice
and go...
Hey! Wanna help us
save the world?
Because all it takes
is one gem piece.
(SISU SPEAKING AS NAMAARI)
Yes!
I've been waiting
for someone to ask me!
Here you go!
Best friends forever!
Yeah, I think I'd rather
go with Boun's plan.
What?
Yes!
What, why?
Because it's Fang.
Their blades
are specially designed
for the stabbing of backs.
If it weren't for them,
none of this
would have happened.
They're the worst.
(MUMBLES IN AGREEMENT)
If we're just honest with her,
deep down, I got a feeling
she wants to fix the world
as much as we do.
You weren't there
when Namaari betrayed me.
We're sticking with my plan.
(SISU GRUNTS ANNOYEDLY)
Whoa. Uh...
What's with the downpour?
SISU: Come on!
I need to show you something.
(RAYA EXCLAIMING FEARFULLY)
So, what do we do now?
I don't know.
RAYA: Where are you taking me?
(ENTHRALLING MUSIC PLAYING)
Sisu, why did you
bring me here?
This is where it all happened.
Yeah, I know.
-I was there.
-SISU: No.
This is where it all happened
500 years ago.
(GASPS SOFTLY)
SISU: I want you to meet
my brothers and sisters.
The real mighty ones.
I miss them.
RAYA: I never knew
they were here.
See that classy-looking one
over there?
That's Amba.
I get my glow from her.
And that's Pranee.
She's a shapeshifter.
Jagan, fog.
And Pengu.
He's our big brother.
He brings the rain.
We were the last dragons.
(THUNDERING)
SISU: All the other dragons
had been turned to stone.
We were drowning
in a sea of Druun.
(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
But my oldest brother Pengu
refused to accept defeat.
This is where
we'd make our last stand...
united.
So, one by one,
they combined all their magic,
creating the Dragon Gem.
I don't know why
they chose me.
It could have been any of us.
(DRAMATIC MUSIC CONTINUES)
All I know
is I trusted them...
(DRUUN RUMBLING)
...and they trusted me.
And so...
(GEM RINGING MYSTICALLY)
When they put their faith
in me,
it empowered me beyond
anything I could imagine.
The same can happen
with Namaari.
I really wish
I could believe that.
I once thought
that we could be friends.
After all this,
maybe you can be.
Even if she wanted to help us,
how could I possibly
trust her?
But if somehow you could,
you wouldn't just bring
your ba back.
You'd also bring back
his dream.
Kumandra.
(SOFT MUSIC PLAYING)
(EXHALES SOFTLY)
Do you think
he would even recognize me?
So much has changed.
Of course he will.
You remind me of him.
Oh, yeah? Strong?
Good-looking
with impeccable hair?
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
Hopeful.
How would I even
approach Namaari
after all that's happened?
It may feel impossible,
but sometimes,
you just have to take
the first step,
even before you're ready.
Trust me.
(SOFT SENTIMENTAL MUSIC
PLAYING)
Okay. We'll go with your plan.
What? My plan?
You're gonna go with my plan?
-Yeah.
-(LAUGHS) All right!
You're not gonna regret this.
But we're gonna need
a really good gift.
What do you think she's into?
Cats? Knives?
-Cats with knives?
-(LAUGHS)
SISU: Knives with little cats
on them?
Actually, I know exactly what
to give her.
And that is how
the land of Fang rose
in spite of all the monsters
that wanted to destroy us.
Because we're smart, resilient,
and we take care of one another.
Mother! We need to talk.
It's Princess Namaari!
(CHILDREN EXCLAIMING)
All right, all right,
now, run along, kittens.
-(CHILDREN MUMBLING DISAPPOINTEDLY)
-I have to speak with the princess.
Mother, you won't believe what I saw.
You saw a dragon.
General Atitya informed me
that you'd be returning home
without the gem pieces.
It was Sisu.
She can fix what we broke.
She can bring everyone back.
And that's what scares me.
When everyone comes back,
who do you think
they'll come for?
You forget.
The other lands blame us
for what's happened.
But we... We never meant
for anyone to get hurt.
Yes, but if we had the dragon
and the gem pieces,
we would be forgiven.
We could save the world.
But more importantly,
our people would remain safe.
But Raya isn't just gonna
give Sisu to us.
(SIGHS)
We're not going to give her
a choice.
What are you going to do?
That's no longer
your concern, my love.
You've done enough.
(SOFT TENSE MUSIC PLAYING)
If she refuses to help,
we've just flushed
our tactical advantage
-into the dung pot.
-I know.
Yeah. She really has no reason
to help us.
I know!
This jerky's terrible.
Are you sure
those four miniature menaces
will be successful?
I don't know.
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING)
-Huh? (GRUNTS AND GROANS)
-(BODY THUDS)
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES)
Hmm?
(GRUNTS)
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES)
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC RISING)
(CHITTERING)
Huh?
(SOFT MUSIC PLAYING)
(SIGHS DEEPLY)
TONG: There's too much spice.
Uh, no.
There's too much bamboo.
TONG: What do you know?
You have the taste buds
of a tall baby.
Well, you dress like
a tall baby.
Give me the spoon!
I'm taking over!
Back off, tidal wave.
I'm the professional here.
May I?
(SLURPS)
Whoa!
That's good.
RAYA: It's just a little
something my ba showed me.
Aw. Did he also show you
how to make
that delicious jerky?
(CHUCKLES)
No, that was all me.
It'll be nice to share a meal
with him again.
BOUN: I know what you mean.
I have this really
obnoxious sister
who always tousles my hair.
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
I can't wait to see her
the most.
After we win the day,
I look forward
to filling my eyeball
with the joytastic image
of my village full again.
(CON-BABY MUMBLING)
And you will be reunited
with your family, Noi.
Uh, what did you
just call her?
Noi. It's her name.
(BURPS)
It's written on her collar.
Have none of you ever checked?
And they think of me
as the ruffian.
(FLARE WHISTLING)
What's that mean?
It means we're on.
(TENSE MUSIC PLAYING)
Sisu,
until we get that gem
and confirm Namaari's actually
on our side,
promise me you'll stay hidden.
(TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES)
(SOFT MUSIC PLAYING)
I see you got my gift.
I never thought
I'd see this again.
Well, uh...
I tried to take
good care of it.
You're not the only
dragon nerd here.
(CHUCKLES)
(SOFT TRIUMPHANT MUSIC
PLAYING)
(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
(BREATHES NERVOUSLY)
The final piece.
Time to bring everyone back.
(WEAPON CREAKS)
(INTENSE MUSIC PLAYING)
Sisu and the gem pieces
are coming with me.
-Sisu!
-Stay back!
It was foolish
to trust someone from Fang!
Don't come any closer!
Namaari,
it doesn't have to be
like this.
I don't have any other choice.
Hey. I got this.
(SOFT MUSIC PLAYING)
(NAMAARI BREATHING HEAVILY)
I know you don't wanna
hurt anybody.
What are you doing?
You just want a better world.
Like we all do.
Sisu...
I trust you, Namaari.
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC RISING)
(RAYA GRUNTS)
(NAMAARI EXCLAIMS)
(EXCLAIMS) No!
(TENSE MUSIC PLAYING)
Sisu!
(SPLASHES)
No... (BREATHING HEAVILY)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(TENSE MUSIC RISING)
What's happening?
I don't know.
It appears that
with the last dragon gone,
so too goes the water.
Now there is nothing
to stop the Druun.
(OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING)
Nothing.
(DRUUN SCREECHING)
(VIRANA GASPS)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
Raya?
Where's Raya?
(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
(QUAKES)
(PEOPLE EXCLAIMING)
(LOUD RUMBLING)
(DRUUN SCREECHING)
(QUAKES)
Namaari!
Let's finish this, binturi.
(INTENSE MUSIC PLAYING)
(QUAKING)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(GRUNTING)
(BOTH GRUNT)
-(RUMBLING)
-(CROWD EXCLAIMING)
-(DRUUN SCREECHING)
-(GASPS)
(GRUNTS)
-(RAYA AND NAMAARI GRUNTING)
-BOUN: Raya!
(BOTH GRUNTING)
TONG: She cannot see us.
Raya's blinded
by her own rage.
(GASPS)
The gem's powers are fading!
(DRUUN SCREECHING)
All these people
are Druun food
if we don't get them out.
(TONG GRUNTS AFFIRMATIVELY)
Come on!
Trust me, it's gonna be okay.
Stupid Druun! Out of my way!
Go, go, go!
(WHIMPERING)
Up we go! Yep!
(DRUUN SCREECHING)
(ONGIS CHITTERING)
(EXCLAIMS)
(SPEAKING GIBBERISH)
MAN: Go, go! Hurry!
BOUN: Get to the water!
Keep going! Keep going!
(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
BOUN: Come on! Come on!
(CRASHING)
(RAYA AND NAMAARI GRUNTING)
-(WEAPONS CLASHING)
-(BOTH GRUNTING)
(EXCLAIMS)
(GRUNTING)
-(GRUNTS PAINFULLY)
-(GRUNTS)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(GRUNTS LOUDLY)
(COUGHING)
-(BOTH GRUNTING)
-(WEAPONS CLASHING)
(DRAMATIC MUSIC CONTINUES)
(BOTH CONTINUE GRUNTING)
(GRUNTS PAINFULLY)
(CLATTERS)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
I never meant
for any of this to happen.
(YELLS) Liar!
(CRYING)
I don't care
if you believe me.
Sisu did.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
NAMAARI:
But you didn't trust her.
That's why we're here.
Do whatever you want.
But you're as much to blame
for Sisu's death as I am.
(SOFT DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
BOUN: Tong, there's still
people back there!
Hurry!
We're running out of time!
TONG: Got it!
Everyone, out! Come with me!
(PEOPLE EXCLAIMING)
(CRYING)
-(DRUUN SCREECHING)
-(BOUN GRUNTING)
(RAYA GRUNTING)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(TONG EXCLAIMS)
(LITTLE NOI
SPEAKING GIBBERISH)
(EXCLAIMS)
(CHITTERING)
(TUK TUK EXCLAIMS)
(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
RAYA: Okay, Tuk,
these are the last of 'em.
Go! We're right behind you.
(DRUUN SCREECHING)
Tuk Tuk!
(TUK TUK EXCLAIMS)
-(NAMAARI GRUNTING)
-(DRUUN SCREECH)
What are you waiting for? Go!
(TUK TUK EXCLAIMS)
-(RUMBLING)
-(GRUNTS)
-(NAMAARI GRUNTS)
-BOUN: (YELLS) Raya!
It's the one who slayed Sisu!
(ALL EXCLAIMING)
(RAYA BREATHING HEAVILY)
BOUN: Raya! Raya!
The gem's magic,
it's almost gone!
TONG: They aren't backing off!
BOUN: They're everywhere!
(RAYA GRUNTS)
(DRUUN SCREECHING)
(GRUNTING)
(EXCLAIMS AND GRUNTS)
(CHITTERING)
(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
(GRUNTING)
(SENTIMENTAL MUSIC PLAYING)
SISU: I don't know why
they chose me.
It could have been any of us.
All I know is I trusted them,
and they trusted me.
And so...
Everyone, give me your gems.
We can still put it together.
It can still work.
Sisu's gone, Raya!
We don't have her magic!
It's not about her magic.
It's about trust.
What?
That's why it worked.
That's why we can do it, too.
By doing the one thing
Sisu wanted us to do.
What my ba wanted us to do.
To finally trust each other
and fix this.
But we have to come together.
Please.
After what she's done?
We'll never trust her!
(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
Then let me take
the first step.
Raya! No!
(DRUUN RUMBLING)
(CRACKLING)
(SPEAKING GIBBERISH)
(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
(RUMBLING)
-(DRUUN SCREECHING)
-(NAMAARI EXCLAIMS)
(GRUNTS)
(GRUNTS AND BREATHES HEAVILY)
(DRAMATIC MUSIC CONTINUES)
(GRUNTING)
(BREATHING RAPIDLY)
(CRACKLING)
(GEM HUMMING SOFTLY)
(WIND BLOWING SOFTLY)
(HUMS)
(FLARING)
(DRUUN SCREECHING)
(HOPEFUL MUSIC PLAYING)
(LOUD RUMBLING)
(WATER TRICKLING)
(RAIN PATTERING)
(HOPEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES)
(GASPS)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(SIGHS)
(SNIFFLES AND CRIES)
(CHUCKLES) It worked! It worked!
(EXCLAIMS)
(ALL LAUGHING)
(JOYFUL MUSIC PLAYING)
(WATER RUSHING)
-RAYA: Tuk Tuk!
-(EXCLAIMS)
Oh! (LAUGHING)
(TRIUMPHANT MUSIC RISING)
(MUSIC SWELLING)
(ENTHRALLING MUSIC PLAYING)
(GASPS SOFTLY)
(GASPS)
(TRIUMPHANT MUSIC PLAYING)
Pranee! Amba!
Jagan!
Pengu!
(LAUGHING) Yeah!
(LAUGHING)
(TRIUMPHANT MUSIC CONTINUES)
(MUSIC SWELLING)
-(SPLASHES)
-(LAUGHING)
Raya.
Sisu.
I am so hungry.
I got some jerky.
Not that hungry.
(LAUGHING)
(SOFT MUSIC PLAYING)
(EXCLAIMS) Sisu!
Aw, it's good to breathe in
your glorious dragon stench again.
Okay, I take that
as a compliment.
(COOING AND LAUGHING)
(BREATHES DEEPLY)
(CRYING)
(SOFT SENTIMENTAL MUSIC
PLAYING)
(SOFT UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING)
(BABY COOING)
(WOMAN EXCLAIMS)
(LITTLE NOI
SPEAKING GIBBERISH)
(GASPS)
Momma!
LITTLE NOI'S MOTHER: My baby!
(LAUGHING AND CRYING)
BOUN'S SISTER:
Mom, look, it's Boun!
(ALL EXCLAIMING)
BOUN'S BROTHER: It's Boun!
(SOFT MUSIC PLAYING)
(TUK TUK RATTLING SOFTLY)
(SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES)
RAYA: Ba?
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
Dewdrop?
(CLATTERS)
(CRIES) Ba!
(CRYING)
Is that really her?
Chief Benja,
your daughter did you proud.
Hope you don't mind,
she brought some friends.
(SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES)
(GIGGLING)
Ba? (CHUCKLES)
Welcome to Kumandra.
(MUSIC RISING)
(LAUGHS)
(LITTLE NOI LAUGHING
AND SPEAKING GIBBERISH)
(MUSIC CONTINUES RISING)
(MUSIC SWELLING)
(MUSIC FLOURISHES TO AN END)
(MUSIC PLAYING)
We have a choice
To build or destroy
To fight or to come together
Love is a bridge
And trust is a gift
We give it
And it gets better
There's an energy
in the water
There is magic
deep in our heart
There's a legacy
that we honor
When we bring
the light to the dark
Whatever brings us together
Can never tear us apart
We become stronger than ever
When we just trust
Trust and believe it
You'll see that
Well lead the way
When we just trust
Trust and believe it
You'll see that
Well lead the way
When we just trust
Trust and believe it
You'll see that
Well lead the way
When we just trust
Trust and believe it
You'll see that
Well lead the way
When you're broken
Open up your heart and feel
There's no difference
We're all family here
Despite all of our doubts
All our up and downs
There's never really
anything to fear
There's an energy
in the water
There is magic
deep in our heart
There's a legacy
that we honor
When we bring the light
to the dark
Whatever brings us together
Can never tear us apart
We become stronger than ever
When we just trust
Trust and believe it
You'll see that
Well lead the way
When we just trust
Trust and believe it
You'll see that
Well lead the way
When we just trust
Trust and believe it
You'll see that
Well lead the way
When we just trust
Trust and believe it
You'll see that
We'll lead the way
Takin' my first step
I see you as myself
Nothing we can't do
Put the past behind
Learn from life this time
We can start brand new
There's an energy
in the water
There is magic
deep in our heart
There's a legacy
that we honor
When we bring
the light to the dark
Whatever brings us together
Can never tear us apart
We become stronger than ever
When we just trust
Trust and believe it
You'll see that
Well lead the way
When we just trust
Trust and believe it
You'll see that
Well lead the way
When we just trust
Trust and believe it
You'll see that
Well lead the way
When we just trust
Trust and believe it
You'll see that
We'll lead the way
Kumandra, Kumandra