We're looking at a
very disturbing live shot here.
According to
police sources,
we're dealing with
aggressive infected individuals
within the airport premises.
Even after
two months,
the pandemic is unstoppable.
Despite the efforts,
new cases appear nationwide.
Symptoms can
show sometimes within days
or even minutes.
People become
uncontrollable raging beasts.
And they're
very, very dangerous.
Today, the
World Health Organization
officially announced that
this is a global pandemic.
We're all going to die!
These people are ill.
They have rights.
And how dare
you call them "ferals"?
I say one thing.
Fake news.
The airport
quarantine has been breached.
Authorities are asking
everyone to stay at home.
Do not go out at this point.
This is real.
This is happening now.
Gun them down, one by one.
We've seen
police fleeing the scene
and National Guard
soldiers are falling back.
Curfew has been
ordered with immediate effect.
Do not try to escape.
Stay where you are and hide.
Duck shot.
So tough.
Ooh.
Hmm.
Getting a little thin on top.
How about a little
soap to stimulate the scalp?
Mom?
The y don't
bel ieve that the authorities
are capable of
controlling the situation.
Shops are closed,
public services unavailable,
and panic reigns...
- in
so ciety
and now you want to matter
for your own unlawfully...
We can't just
shoot them, they're people.
People
protecting their fellow citizens
while you are preaching
about civil rights in both
Mom?
People, they're
not even humans.
Are you out of
your goddamn mind?
That is not
true and you know it.
We're watching
the death of the country
and the only thing that matters
to you is all this crap.
Gotcha.
Ha ha.
I can't leave without
you.
I know you're
strong enough darling.
I can't do this alone.
Let me talk to the kids.
Kids, come here.
Your dad wants to talk to you.
Hey, pumpkin.
When are you
coming home, Daddy?
I don't know, pumpkin.
You got to
help your mom
and get yourselves
over to Aunt Carrie's.
But I don't like Aunt
Carrie's.
I know.
I'll pick you up as soon
as I get out of here. Alright?
OK.
Don't you worry.
You see, I'm
wearing my lucky bracelet
and I can feel
its magic right now.
I promise, everything's
going to be just fine.
Bye.
Give me your bag.
Get this on.
Go, go, go, go, go!
Go, go, go!
Stay close to me.
Abby, Abby.
No!
Abby.
No.
All right.
It's OK.
You're safe now.
Come here.
Yeah.
It's OK.
OK.
You're safe now.
OK?
OK.
Close your eyes.
Go over your ears.
Good.
OK.
Get you out of here.
♪ Mary is floating on the
surface of the water ♪
♪ Of the shore in the salt
water winter ♪
♪ Take a stroke further out in
the harbor ♪
♪ Take a breath and it turns
diver down ♪
♪ Down, diver, down, diver ♪
♪ Keep swimming down, diver ♪
♪ Get it all out and go wash it
all away ♪
♪ Down, diver, down, diver.
Keep swimming down, diver ♪
♪ Get it all out and go wash it
all away. ♪
♪ Can you wash it away? ♪
♪ Help me wash it away ♪
You know the drill.
Align the sights.
Focus on the reticle.
Breathe.
Place the pad of your finger--
Remember this, old man.
Cocky.
Abigail, let's go.
Dinner time.
Finished?
One!
Only, one!
Well, we got 39 seeds that
are good for a tropical climate.
The rest we
can get in Garden City.
I know a place there.
It's hard to
picture us as farmers.
I bet we'll miss the adventure.
I'll miss them.
Nothing more.
Oh, and by the way,
I plan to spend most
of my time sitting on a beach
sipping orange juice.
I can't wait to see the ocean.
Two weeks.
You can cross it
off your bucket list.
A scout?
Yeah.
So the pack
must be nearby.
At least 30 ferals.
Get your gear.
We're moving.
Wakey, wakey.
Come on.
We're leaving.
Screw you.
We could...
we could go up north.
We could climb
up the old ferris wheel.
Nah, it's too big a detour.
Okay. Um...
We could fly to the island.
I hate flying.
Look, just
stick to the plan, okay?
But what if it wasn't a scout?
Just a lonely feral.
There's no one here except--
Okay, okay, okay.
Okay.
Ammo?
31 left of the 9mil
and 40 of the 5.56s.
I can get it.
Don't rush this time.
Wait for it.
No, no, no, no, no.
Fuck!
I told you not to rush.
It's the same pack.
We gotta be close.
Abigail, search the car.
Abigail, let's go.
Here.
I'm sorry, pal.
We can't waste any bullets.
Nice boots.
May I have 'em?
Ahh!
Trevor, where
are you, mate? Over.
Pack what's useful.
Let's go.
If we're fast enough,
we can make it to the ridge.
And the pack might not see us.
But they'll see them.
None of our business.
We gotta warn them.
Where are you,
man? Hey?
Hey, don't answer.
Think a little.
What'll be their first
question when they get here?
They'll ask, when
are the others coming?
Abigail!
Hey!
Hello!
What the hell happened here?
Your friends
have been attacked.
Drop your weapons
and get your hands up.
I said drop
your weapons
and get your fucking hands up.
All right, man.
Take it fucking easy, okay.
Check it.
It's okay.
We don't want to hurt you.
Shut up!
I've got a bad
feeling about this.
She's just a kid.
I don't like
the look of the big guy.
Yeah, you know who
we hate the most?
Looters.
We're gonna do
the same thing to you
that we do to
everyone of you scumbags.
We're gonna rip
you off, break your legs,
and leave you
here to fucking rot.
You misunderstand.
Oh, we do, you little bitch.
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
Don't do it. Put it down.
Put it down.
Don't do this.
Take it easy, man.
Put him down.
Take it easy.
Put your guns down.
We don't mean to hurt you.
Megan, get back in the car!
Look, we just
wanted to warn you.
Warn us about what?
The ferals.
We got to get out of here.
Back to the cars.
Let go.
Fuck!
Ammo.
Uh, 16 of the 9mil
and 37 of 5.56's.
Dammit, we
lost nearly everything.
What the
hell were you thinking,
traveling in that condition?
We ran out of
everything so we had to leave.
But where to?
Northeast, to a colony
on a riverside, a boat town.
How far along are you?
It's the 35th week.
What does that mean?
It means she's close.
What about you?
Where you going?
Definitely not Northeast.
Why not?
We've been
to several colonies
and we've seen
the same everywhere.
Same what?
Same chaos.
Dammit!
Pop the hood.
Maybe I can fix it.
Radiator's shot.
We have no spare parts.
The fuck are
you, the geek squad?
Yeah.
I'm David, by the way.
Abigail.
And the
grumpy guy is Cassius.
This is Megan.
Hi.
So, now what?
Get your stuff.
We're leaving.
Just leave it, not worth it.
We should contact the colony.
Let them know
that we're coming.
Looks fine.
Okay, five minutes.
We need to find
a shelter for the night.
A less exposed building.
She won't hold out for long.
That's the old elementary
school.
And the Jackson house is there.
That'll do
for the night.
Let's hit camp.
You sure you don't want any?
Thanks, but we
only eat meat that we hunted
because of the infection.
Um, we'd like to
thank you for helping us.
Can't imagine what would
have happened
if you hadn't come.
I can.
Tell me about
the place you lived.
What was it like?
It was just an ordinary farm.
Far from everything.
There were times when
it was 40 of us, but then...
But then
the Grim Reaper came.
And the colony?
What do you know about it?
We talked
to them on the radio
and they have
plenty of water and food
and they even have doctors.
They pulled a
couple of shipwrecks together.
Now over 100
people live on the water.
How far is it?
It's about a week's travel.
It's risky.
But we voted and
the majority decided to go.
Because we couldn't stay.
You know, the
ferals killed so many.
After the last
attack, we had to burn down
a whole wheat
field just to stop them.
We had almost nothing left.
The boat town
is the only safe place.
And you?
How did you survive?
Because we never
stopped.
And Cassius
taught me everything.
To hunt, to survive,
and even the most important
thing.
We're better off alone.
You can only count on yourself.
Tell me this is not your plan.
To just wander
around until the end of time.
No, we are
headed to the west coast.
Then to the islands by boat.
Okay. So...
This is where
your friends were killed.
And this is where we are now.
I wouldn't
recommend the old route 50.
But if you had North here,
you get out of the city.
And the 55 here,
takes you to the river.
Uhm...
We thought we'd go together?
That you'd come with us?
Yeah.
Nah.
That's not a good idea.
Well, why not?
Well...
Because we're the
only survivors in the area.
And when the pack finishes
the feast from your friends,
which can happen any
minute now, they'll remember us.
So, I wanna be as far away
as possible when that happens.
Got it?
I thought we were far enough.
Far enough?
Far enough
don't exist, sweetheart.
That's why we don't join.
That's the trick.
I suggest you do the same.
I'm sorry, it's just...
We have to
start the collection over.
It'll take
months before we can leave.
Why don't we
check out the colony?
We've seen enough.
Why would
this be any different?
We could use the company.
Maybe these
people are different.
People are the
same everywhere, Abigail.
No matter
whether it's North, South,
or some shitty boat town.
Still, we can't
just leave them alone.
You said back in the old days,
people would help each other.
You said that was a good thing.
And still, the
world is full of the bodies
of selfless people.
Whatever.
I'm giving them
my gun and some ammo
so at least I can sleep well.
Sleep well?
How the fuck
are you gonna sleep well
after the mess you made today?
Did you even
consider the fact
that we
nearly died at the mine?
But we didn't!
No thanks to you!
Fuck, Abigail. Get off
your high horse!
You'll get us into trouble
again next time, just think.
Fucking think before you act.
Thanks for today's lesson.
It was really useful.
I'll be on watch.
Blackbeard one, Blackbeard one.
This is Papa Hotel five, over.
Can't sleep, huh?
Me neither.
It's chilly.
That was really amazing back in
the valley.
I mean, those moves.
Really amazing.
It was luck.
Sheer luck.
Problem of luck is that
eventually you run out of it.
I don't know what I would
do if there was no way out.
It's easy.
It was a serious question.
So was the answer.
This,
this is my plan B.
Even has my name on it.
Really?
No.
Still, it's mine.
Well this is mine.
Hey, that's
not a bad plan either.
Hey man.
Oh yeah, it's nothing.
I just, I twisted my ankle.
And you know,
it's nothing compared
to what she's going through.
I know she blames
herself for what happened.
She was so
convinced we get to the colony.
She convinced everyone else.
I'm just glad
that today we survived.
We'll help
you get to the colony.
Time to move on.
Come on.
We must rest.
Look, if we stop, we die.
I remember this place.
We used to come
here a lot with my dad.
Yeah?
There's a civil
airport a couple of miles away.
My dad had a small plane there.
We used to fly it all the time.
Oh, you think that some
plane that's been lying around
for years is gonna fly?
There used to
be dozens of planes.
Lots of spare parts.
We could do it.
We don't have time for this.
Still, we
can't just walk for days.
Look, I know
a place in the town.
If the tools are still there,
we'll figure out
something.
Old cars,
bikes, whatever, we'll see.
At this pace, we
won't get there until sunset.
The airport is
only about an hour's walk.
All right.
Let's give it a try.
Give it a try?
Look, there's
one road to the airport.
If we get
surrounded there, it's over.
Then walking will be
the least of our problems.
Well, it's just your opinion.
Let's have a vote.
Who's for?
It's decided then.
Come on, darling.
They've been shot.
Not long ago.
Check inside.
We've got two minutes.
Take only what's useful.
We must eat something.
We haven't
stopped since this morning.
We'll eat the airport.
Why?
Because we're not alone.
Sorry.
Ah, might not kill us.
Oh, coffee.
We have to try it.
Bingo!
Not much use
to them, so...
Thanks.
I'm sorry you
were arguing because of us.
Oh, it wasn't because of you.
Do you have a
name for the baby?
Not yet.
But I'm not
afraid we won't find a name.
I fear that my child
will have to grow up alone.
Living in constant uncertainty.
I just want someone to
be with her, to look after her.
And I'd give my life for that.
You see?
Nothing.
That's unlucky.
We should turn back?
No, no we shouldn't.
That'd be a
fucking stupid idea.
We have to find a path.
Okay, asshole.
Fuck you.
That's enough.
David, relax.
What the hell are you doing?
Hey, that's where
my dad's hangar used to be.
How do we open it?
If we can fix it, we can
get there in a couple of hours.
Uh-huh.
And where do
we land the plane?
We'll cross that
bridge when we get there.
Uh-huh.
Just in case.
Okay.
We're gonna
look around. Ok?
You gonna be all right?
Yeah.
What do you say to
Belle or Benedict if it's a boy?
First of all,
it's definitely a boy.
And secondly, Benedict.
Sounds like some kind
of troubadour or something.
All right. Fine.
How about Sandra and Samuel?
Dammit.
Easy, David,
you can do it, it's okay.
I can't fucking--
Let me see.
It's okay, it's
okay, sit back down.
It's all right.
Let me see, come on.
My God, You hit it.
I'm gonna fix
this shitty airplane.
I'm gonna get us
to the boat town, okay?
Well, did you find anything?
Nope.
He can fix it, right?
Well, you're the
aviation expert, right?
How should I know?
Hate that I'm always right.
Come on, let's move.
Fucking hell.
Nearly there.
What is it now?
I don't
know and I don't care.
No, I know.
When can we take off?
Why isn't the plane ready?
It's a fucking airplane.
Are you okay?
No, we got three minutes.
Wait, what
happens in three minutes?
They're coming.
No, no, no, we won't be ready.
I don't wanna die here, honey.
Please hurry up.
Yeah, you probably
should have started with that.
Maybe, but it's
all the same now, isn't it?
60 seconds, be ready.
Go, go, go.
Can anybody pray?
Our Father who liveth
out there.
Those are the wrong words.
Just go!
It won't help!
Let's go, move it.
Come on!
It's too slow.
They're gonna catch this.
We gotta go faster,
- we're not gonna make it.
- I'm trying!
They're catching us.
Got 'em.
The carburetor.
The red button.
Do it!
Okay, that's it.
All right, all
right.
That was close.
I know.
Oh my God.
You got it, you got it.
Oh.
Well done, Abby.
Well done.
Hey, what's happening?
I can't hold it.
What?
What the fuck?!
I don't know what to do.
Abigail, you're
gonna land this thing,
or we're all gonna die.
What?
Over there, over there.
Okay, okay.
We're going down.
Brace for impact, okay?
Okay.
You alright?
Yeah.
Told you I needed more time.
Okay, I gotcha.
Okay.
Okay, let's just go.
No, let's find somewhere to
rest and eat, okay?
Okay, okay.
All right, all right, let's go.
Fucking hate flying.
All right, new plan.
We're here.
The riverbank and the colony
are on the
other side of these hills.
Now we can
get there in two days.
Ammo?
Um...
Seven and eight?
Okay, let's get some rest.
We're leaving first light.
Are you still mad at me?
How can I stay mad at you?
Sleep well, my love.
Chicken.
Yum.
Sorry, I got hungry.
Thank you.
So good.
Wait.
A little thank you.
You know, you
remind me of my wife.
Whenever she had something
to say, she could never hide it.
Those little wrinkles
dancing on the edge of her lips.
Busted.
I know what you're thinking.
But you know what's
right for us better than we do.
We rely on each other.
That won't
change, even if we help you.
She's stronger than you think.
Yeah.
It's not about that.
What then?
I killed her mom.
And her brother.
How else could
I make it up to her?
But to look after her.
I'm sorry.
I really am.
But you saved her as well.
And that's enough.
In this world it is.
You know, there was this kid,
three months
after the infection.
Jimmy.
Now his mom had gotten
so stoned
that she didn't
even wake up when a feral
was skinning her body.
We saved him.
He was a good kid.
A smart kid.
And a cheeky little
rascal at the same time.
He never listened to me.
Well, one day a feral bit
his finger clean off and
you know what
happens when a wound doesn't
hit an artery, right?
It takes days
until you totally transform.
He was the first.
And the last that I
ever watched go through that.
Never again did I
wait for the transformation.
And there was Patrick,
and Sarah.
Sometimes you just gotta run
and only worry about yourselves.
Joe.
Linda.
That was the first
time I watched someone die.
Rather than lose the other.
Jess.
She simply grabbed
a rope when she couldn't
take it any longer and...
Sometimes I feel that...
I don't have the space
for all the faces in my brain.
Dying.
Dying is nothing.
Losing someone
who is important to you.
That's different.
Yeah, you know sometimes
you just don't need more space.
Sometimes it's
just about letting them go.
You did everything you
could, Cassius, I can tell.
It's time to let her
stand on her own two feet.
Don't worry, you
trained her really well.
Just trust her.
She will always be there.
They always are.
Hey, um...
thanks for the gift.
Now, let's get some sleep, huh?
Got a tough day tomorrow.
Yeah.
This place has been farmed.
Must be people around.
Ahh!
What is it?
Are you okay?
Oh my God, you're burning up.
- Are you okay?
- I just need some rest.
Let me see.
Let me change
your bandage.
Stop, I'm alright.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Don't say a
fucking word, jackass.
When were you gonna tell?
Tell what?
I should kill you
right here, right now.
Give me one good reason
why I shouldn't shoot you right
this fucking second.
Cassius,
we found something.
Yeah, me too.
Coming.
Pull yourself together.
Think about
how you'd like to die.
You have that choice for now.
Who are you
and what do you want?
Abigail, stop.
We are peaceful travelers.
We just need some rest.
There's
nothing here to take.
Abigail, hey.
My name is Abigail.
We are travelers
with a pregnant woman.
We just need a little help.
All right, that's far enough.
We need medicine...
and something to eat.
We can even pay you if
you ask a reasonable price.
All right, put all
your weapons in the chest.
You too.
You two, come up here where
I can see you in the light.
Uh-uh, all of them.
That's better, thank you.
Well, come on inside then.
Well...
Um...
welcome to my uh, humble
abode.
Oh gosh, needless to say,
I rarely get
visitors these days.
When was the last time?
God only knows.
You have electricity.
I do, yes.
Not much, just
enough for my research.
You're some kind
of scientist?
I am, I...
graduated as an engineer.
Myself and my wife,
we did our research together.
Your wife?
Huh, where is she?
Fortunately, I
have plenty of books.
I've figured everything
out for inside the house.
I have geothermal electricity,
which provides hot water.
Hot water?
You have hot water?
Oh, I have
everything you need, my dear.
Except meat.
That I don't eat anymore,
but I have my own vegetables and
fruit.
I even have some bread.
It's a little bit
dry, but the old flavors, eh,
you can't beat them, can you?
Now don't get too used to it,
otherwise we won't be
able to get rid of you, will I?
Well, what are you waiting for?
Come on, take a seat.
Sorry about the wait,
here you go.
Yes, thank you.
Bon appetit.
Hey.
You okay?
Yeah.
And I just sometimes ask
myself how I'm gonna hold out.
Listen.
Everything's
gonna be just fine.
I'm scared.
Since we've been here,
I don't feel the baby moving.
Trust me...
Once we get there,
you won't keep that
big boy inside.
Or a big girl.
Cassius.
Promise me,
if anything happens to me,
you look after her, please.
I promise.
Thank you.
Cheers!
Well, non-alcoholic
for the mother to be.
Thank you.
And a little homemade
surprise for the rest of you.
Oh, it's an excellent year.
I'm very proud of it.
Cheers!
Mm.
- Mm.
- Cheers.
So, uh, how
long you been living here?
Me? Oh,
over 20 years. Yes.
First with my wife, and now, uh,
well,
now I'm on my own, yes.
And what about yourselves?
Where are you headed to?
To the colony.
Oh, brilliant
idea. Yes, I speak to
them from time to
time through my radio.
How come
you're not with them?
Surely your knowledge would
come in handy at the colony.
Oh, that's
very kind of you, dear.
But I think
I'm better off here.
I mean, even before
civilization, how shall I say,
disappeared into the abyss.
Now, I was never
impressed by crowded cities
and all that
kind of ostentation.
I mean, we used
to go there for work,
but real life is
here far away from all that.
Yeah. Yeah,
I hear you, buddy.
Yes, I mean,
don't misunderstand me.
I have no problem
with the people at the colony.
And I am sure it's a very nice,
cozy place these days.
I just don't understand
all that fitful adherence
to, you know, the old things.
I mean, there
was chaos even before.
Excuse me?
Oh, come on,
you know what I mean.
How we got here?
Over seven billion people,
all selfishly
trying to one-up each other
and not giving a
shit about the consequences.
I mean, Christ, there wasn't
even enough food and water.
But, oh, no, we all
had to have another one of this
and another one of that,
scrounging around
until the end of days.
I mean, what happened was
necessary
Yeah, but it was still awful.
Well, that's
besides the point, my darling.
It was heavenly for the virus.
And as for us
human beings, well,
it was just the
next stage in our evolution.
Next stage?
Don't you see?
The strong have survived.
And, my friends, only
the strong should survive.
That sounds cruel.
Oh, don't you worry about me.
It's just my opinion.
I mean, one violent
world replaced by another.
The Neanderthal was
overtaken by the homosapien.
Evolution didn't stop,
and it's not going to stop now.
How on earth can
you compare this to evolution?
Life doesn't care
about opinions, my dear.
Especially not ours.
I mean, come on,
we did deserve the punishment.
We thought we were
so superior,
but, I mean, a top predator
that uses up
all its own resources,
preys on those of others,
is destined for annihilation.
Evolution is
always a correction.
Homo sapiens cruentus.
Somehow I get the feeling
that you're on their side.
I am just a
realist, my friend.
I mean, all our
attempts have been in vain.
There is nothing we can do.
In a few generations, we won't
even be here to
remember all of this.
Back to the
instincts of the beasts,
from civilized
naivety in a matter of moments,
hours,
days.
I'd much rather
die than live like this.
Oh, no, you
wouldn't, my dear.
Living's always better than
dying.
What about a cure?
There could be one, right?
No, unfortunately, there is
none.
The moment that
virus enters your body,
it's over, finito.
Might as well
just shoot
yourself in the
head, but why would you?
Because that's no life.
And who decides?
Even human beings
only ever want to survive.
So simple.
Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm okay.
Oh, don't
you worry about him.
He just needs a little
rest and he'll be just fine.
You won't even
remember this little
inconvenience
that I can promise you.
I'd love to offer you all
another drink,
but unfortunately,
we haven't got much time left.
Ah, I thought so.
Do you know
what this is?
Well, let's just say it's a
special kind of dog whistle
that only
works on the infected.
So my question is--
What are you?
Hey.
Where are we?
What do you want with us?
Radio frequency.
Motivator test 18.
Participants four travelers
two male, two female.
One of them is pregnant.
Condition of the subjects.
Satisfactory.
Hey.
What's going on?
Drugged us.
Please don't hurt us.
We never cause you any harm.
It doesn't
matter now, my darling.
I've got plans for you.
What plans?
Even I can't skip the tests.
Now, who knows what this is?
This little wristlet
emits a sound
frequency that the infected
are unable to bear.
Or if I change
it, unable to resist.
I need no fence,
nor do I need weapons.
I need no other protection.
You could save others.
Why don't you help them?
Now, why would I want to do
that when I've got other plans?
You really are crazy!
I know what you think.
You think I'm the bad guy.
But I am merely the shepherd
of this brand new world.
The time of mankind has gone.
You bloody bastard.
Oh, by the
way, since you asked,
don't you want to meet my wife?
Anyway, I'm eager to
find out what you're capable of.
Particularly
because you've been bitten.
What?
No!
Would you call this?
Another fuck up.
Come on, let's go!
Abigail, get the car keys!
No!
You idiot!
Stop it!
Look, you knew damn
well he can't come with us!
Let me help, while I can.
Tell me why I
shouldn't fucking kill him!
Because it's not up to us.
Not yet.
We gotta go.
What happened?
My water just broke.
You broke my nose.
Boo
fucking hoo?
That's the least of your
problems, tough guy.
The baby's coming.
Hold on!
There.
Lights.
The colony.
Everybody out!
I'm out of ammo!
Go, I'll buy you some time.
No. No.
I'll always be with you.
Tell that big boy I love him.
Okay?
Come on!
Hey!
Go! Go!
Run!
Go!
Wake up.
Hey!
Hey, help!
We should help them.
Quiet.
Just wait.
Hey!
Hey, help!
Shh, you can do this.
You can do this.
Lie down.
Breathe! Breathe!
She needs to rest.
Leave her.
That was nice, man.
You didn't get bit, did you?
No.
All right.
We're still gonna check you.
Go ahead.
Shoot them all?
Sure did.
No worries, man.
You're safe.
Welcome to the King's Harbor.
The King's Harbor?
What a fucking shithole.
Keep an eye on them.
All right, boss.
I will do.
You see, my friend,
living is always better.
Stop!
Right there.
My name's
George, head of the colony.
I can't tell you how glad
we are that you guys are here.
We thought there was no
one else alive except for us
and that loony scientist.
Where are you from?
The woman.
Megan. She comes
from a distant colony.
And
we've--we've been traveling.
I see.
Don't worry about your past.
Some folks here might be worried
you brought some infection
or that you'd cut
their throats in their sleep.
But that's not true, right?
No.
Of course it's not.
Anyway, there's
nothing here to be taken.
And I hear
you guys are clean.
I am personally very happy for
all the
helping hands we can get.
Now go get some rest.
You've had a tough day.
Where are you going?
I need some time on my own.
Hey,
don't wander off.
We're moving on. First light.
What if I
don't want to move on?
It always
starts like this, Abigail.
First, everything is exciting.
Everyone is nice.
Then it turns out
that they're also just humans.
Listen, you saw the
way the men were looking at you.
Come on.
I can protect myself.
Still, we're
not staying.
That's it.
Discussion is over.
It's over?
You're not my dad!
Don't tell me what to do!
I'll stay if I want to.
Hey, hey, hey.
The past couple
of days, how many times
did we nearly
die because of you, huh?
Because you
didn't listen to me.
I told you.
We're better off alone.
You are better off alone.
You.
Not me anymore.
The baby's fine.
But the
woman's not gonna make it.
She's only got a
couple of hours left.
She wants to talk to you.
Hey!
Look at her.
She's beautiful.
Hello.
Hope.
Hope?
That's what she
brought to our life.
I'm going to see her grow
up and become a strong woman.
But if I don't,
I need you to look after her.
Just like you
looked after Abigail.
I--
Please.
I know you kept your promise.
And you brought her to safety.
I know you'll
do everything.
Just promise me.
You'll teach her
how to stand on her feet.
Please.
I promise.
I'm sorry for your loss.
Can-can I?
Um,
sure, sure.
I'll be back
with her in a short while.
Okay?
So what do you think
about a little old fashioned
revenge?
Fight!
You like it?
Well, then, what I'm going to
show you
will knock your socks off.
♪ Check it out,
check it out now ♪
♪ Gonna make all the men bow
Yeah, don't ya know it ♪
♪ Shake it up, shakeit up-- ♪
♪ We are the lucky ones ♪
♪ We have already won ♪
♪ Gonna paint our nails ♪
♪ Then we'll paint this town
We're up for gettin' down ♪
♪ Oh, can't ya hear us
shoutin'? ♪
♪ With our high-heeled shoes ♪
♪ And our skinny jeans
We are the dancing queens ♪
♪ Riding in limousines ♪
♪ Ain't nothing gonna stop us
now ♪
♪ We'll turn this world right
upside down ♪
♪ Ain't nothing gonna stop us
now ♪
♪ Come on ladies,
this is girls' night out ♪
Wouldn't be a good idea.
Why? What is it?
It's our little safeguard,
a plan B, if you will.
The entire boat
town is mined,
just in case,
the ferrals ever did enter.
But then you'd die as well?
Not necessarily.
What is it?
Back in the old days, a
huge dam was being built here,
so they
tunneled under the river.
The dam was never completed,
but the tunnel remained.
And we've
connected it to the boat town.
Connected?
Are there guards?
Is it safe?
Sure it is.
We've closed
down the other end.
If we're
attacked, we can escape.
Wow.
Wow it is.
What do you think?
Are you and your
dad going to stay with us?
Don't know.
And he's not my dad.
Really?
Seemed like he
deeply cared for you.
Quite an
unusual thing around here.
Good morning, my friend.
Happy hunger seek.
We've got to keep them back.
Wait.
It's too late.
Take the
people down to the tunnel.
Let's see how
your plan B works.
Go find a higher position.
You stay here and cover them.
And you?
I'm going to go find Cassius.
Move! Move!
Move!
Hey, hey, hey!
Have you seen
the girl who came with me?
No, no, give her to me.
Look, keep her safe.
I will, I promise.
Move, move, move, move!
I'm out.
Fuck, me too.
We can't hold them.
Everyone escape.
Use the tunnel.
Go to the bunker.
Where are you, old man?
Let's get out of here.
Thanks.
Go, move, move, move!
Look out!
Down!
We've got to go.
The whole shithole's
ready to blow.
What do you want from us?
You people just
can't accept your fate,
and the desperate are dangerous.
We'll soon be
together in a safer world.
No, no, no, no.
Ow.
Are you ready now?
No!
No! It can't be!
No! No!
Fuck your evolution.
Just do it, man.
Abigail. Come on!
Come on, let's go!
Go!
Come on, Abigail.
Move, move, move.
Go, go, go.
Not yet.
The girl hasn't come out yet.
There.
Five,
four.
Just do it, man.
Thank God.
What?
It's nothing.
OK.
Take it easy.
All right?
Don't move.
Don't even think about it?
- OK.
- Don't move.
All right.
OK?
Just lower your weapon, OK?
The sword.
- Lower your weapon.--
- I'm fine.
OK.
All right.
And what do we do now?
A new home is waiting for us.