NEXT ENTERTAINMENT WORLD presents
A M Pictures production
Executive producer
KIM WOO-TAEK
THIS MOVIE IS A FICTIONAL, CREATED STORY
WITH NO RELATION TO ACTUAL PERSONS OR EVENTS.
Baekgang Company!
Is Baekgang Company here?
JANG EUN-HA
This one isn’t worth taking at all.
- We’ll sell off the scrap metal.
EVIDENCE SALES – SCRAP CARS
PARK SO-DAM
SONG SAE-BYEOK
KIM EUI-SUNG
Okay!
JEONG HYUN-JUN
Written by PARK DAE-MIN
Directed by PARK DAE-MIN
SPECIAL DELIVERY
You should’ve called
a regular cab, not here.
Maybe you did call the right place.
What’s your destination?
Well, it’s a ‘special delivery’.
We transport anything
that regular post carriers can’t.
We’ll deliver anything
in anyway we can.
Holy cow!
A 940?
Fix it up.
Wow!
Did you catch a lot today?
- Not much today.
Surprise situations?
We only deliver.
You’re in charge of the rest.
But while on the job,
we’ll do what it takes to deliver.
Don’t worry.
Yes.
My beer!
Boss! Not again!
Shh!
Of course.
Stop drinking my beer!
- Send me the client’s picture.
Our driver will give more details.
Thanks for calling.
No drunk driving!
- I have a date tonight.
Can you drive for me, boss?
What date?
You don’t have any friends.
Chief Jang.
Do a special delivery later.
Only with 15% overtime pay.
- 5%.
15%.
Deal!
TOP HOTEL 9:00
TO DAESONG PORT 9:30
Let’s run!
6162.
- Boss! That’s it!
What?
- Open the door!
Why keep the door locked!
What? A girl?
A girl?
- What?
It’s a girl!
You idiot!
- Sorry, boss.
Think the chick can do the job?
If we don’t leave now,
you’ll miss the ship, boss.
Damn it!
Isn’t that Jong-tae’s men?
If you fail, you’re dead.
Seatbelts, please.
- I’m wearing it.
It’ll be $60 extra
for the no seatbelt fine.
Watch it!
Seatbelts!
Okay!
You’re good.
DAESONG PORT
Pull over now!
Shut up!
Stop the car now!
Floor it!
You can’t go in there!
No way! Stop!
It won’t fit!
Now what!
Perfect! Right on time.
Hey!
You’re damn good.
Send me your resumé.
What is this, my tip?
It’s not a tip.
It’s an offer.
Look.
How about working for me?
Apart from selling liquor,
I never asked a girl to work for me.
Think of it as an honor.
Here.
Thank you.
No offer needed.
Hey! Who’s your boss!
Asif?
Bring me some coffee!
Chief Jang.
I should raise your salary
from 60:40 someday.
How about 50:50 from tomorrow?
I wish I could,
but reality says I can’t.
Boss?
Don’t just wish, why not just do it?
Hey!
50:50 means we’re partners.
Then I can’t call you
Chief Jang anymore.
It’d be CEO Jang, ma’am!
And the 60% isn’t all for me.
I pay for rent and such
for the business.
If it’s not going to be 50:50,
don’t bring it up again.
I didn’t even take a puff!
- You never listen to the doctor.
Live long, boss.
You’re my meal ticket.
How about a barbecue instead?
Let’s have beef!
Short ribs? Sirloin?
Your call!
- Yay!
Sometimes they don’t eat beef
and sometimes it’s pork.
What do they eat?
Who said we don’t eat beef?
Indians don’t eat beef.
He’s Pakistani.
He’s Bangladeshi.
Muslims don’t eat pork.
Beef is not that expensive.
You boys always confuse me.
If you eat curry, you’re all Indian!
That’s Eun-ha’s!
Who? Chief Jang?
- Yup.
The high and mighty lady
who can drive?
Chief Jang who likes to eat alone?
Did she go home?
Why do you care so much?
You’re not family.
Don’t even think about dating!
Don’t eat it! I’ll eat it all!
As the Korean Baseball League
is on record to reach 8 million viewers,
a case casts a cloud over
the success.
Pitcher Lee Do- young
of the Dragons,
held a press conference today
to blow the whistle on match fixing.
Where is it?
The police is investigating
a broker
and an illegal sports gambling site
for match fixing.
Here is Lee Do- young’s
press conference.
A walk or 1 point loss per inning
are not difficult,
so I got $2000 to $5000 each.
If I gave up many points
and crucial plays to lose,
I got over $10.000
or luxury brand watches and clothes.
Dad! You’re on TV!
- What?
The former baseball player
who Lee pointed out as a broker,
is Kim Du-shik, who retired early
and appeared on various TV shows.
As the gambling site has been
successful despite Kim’s bold actions,
police suspect his close ties
with public officials.
Why’d they use
a picture like that?
There are lots of
good pictures of me, right?
Stop doing that!
Kim Seo-won! Done packing?
You didn’t pack at all!
Hurry up!
Family.
Lyric.
Ricotta.
Ta? Taboo.
Boohoo.
Hoo? Hoopy.
I don’t think that’s a word.
Why!
I enjoyed another meal today.
Like and subscribe! Come on!
See you all tomorrow! Bye!
Why don’t more bastards
subscribe to my damn channel?
Quiet down when I’m on live,
you damn pigs!
Nihao.
Here’s the money.
Here.
Okay!
By the way,
what about the ship?
9:00 p.m. tomorrow. Pyeongtaek Port.
- Pyeongtaek Port at 9:00 p.m.?
The deal is done.
Do you have a ride?
- My car is outside.
What? You’re driving there?
Then, take a taxi?
A taxi? Shit!
You’re unbelievable!
90% of those trying to smuggle out
get caught before they reach the ship.
Really? What do I do?
There’s a special way that guarantees
you reach your destination.
I recommend it.
- How much?
$10.000 each. No discounts.
$20.000.
Want me to set you up or not?
I’ll take it.
Awesome! Come on!
Bring me my phone.
Shit!
Who are you people?
I’m Jesus. He’s Moses.
Split apart.
Try it again.
What the?
Boss?
What brings you here?
It’s my first time
in this new office.
Yes.
- You went on vacation?
Everyone takes their kids abroad
on English camps these days, sir.
An English camp for kids in Macao?
I had to transfer there, sir.
It’s your gift, boss.
Thanks.
- Anytime, sir.
Suddenly came to collect, sir?
- Don’t you watch the news?
The news, sir?
Jeez.
If I gave up many points...
- It’s Lee Do- young.
and crucial plays to lose,
I got over $10.000.
A walk or 1 point loss per inning
are not difficult...
I know you or Du-shik did this.
Please, boss. It’s not me.
I swear.
I had nothing to do with that.
The bank security fob is gone.
Yesterday, you ordered Kim to...
I ordered Kim?
- To bring it, sir.
You idiot!
How much is in our account?
- About $30 million, sir.
Know why I made you co- CEOs?
Because Kim was able to
win over current players and...
No.
Because I have my MBA?
- Damn it!
Because I don’t trust you!
To hold each other in check!
But you thought I told Kim
to bring you the security fob?
Stupid!
Here. Scratch it.
If you win, I’ll believe you.
Then you can just disappear
and go into hiding.
If I don’t win?
If you don’t,
I’ll think of something.
Scratch it.
Yes, sir.
Boss!
I’ll take the fault, sir!
I’ll go in and be investigated.
I’ll do anything for you, boss!
Please forgive me just this once?
Is it no smoking in here?
No, sir.
That loser has no guts.
At least, Kim Du-shik
is gambling with his life.
BOSS CHO
Don’t answer it.
He’s calling again!
- Don’t answer it!
Kim Du-shik?
You answered your phone?
Sounds like you’re driving,
so I’ll be brief.
You know the $300.000 or so
you took?
Keep it.
It’s okay. It’s your severance pay.
But hand over the security fob.
Only I know the bank.
You can’t get the $30 million.
Answer me, Kim.
Fine.
I’ll give it back.
When I arrive safely
far away from you.
I’ll give it to you,
so don’t chase me, bastard!
Or else I’ll get rid of it for good!
Are you out of your mind?
I’ll come to you before you know it.
Just wait.
I’ll get you soon.
- Try it, you son of a bitch!
Let’s see if I lose my head
or you lose...
Slept well? Are you hungry?
Chubby!
My baby!
Watch the house
till Mommy comes back.
I work hard to provide
for you, baby.
Say, “Have a nice day, Mommy.”
Say, “Cheer up.
It’ll be another good day.”
You silly bastard.
See you later.
Drive safely.
The bottom is all scratched up.
Did you fall asleep at the wheel?
I should be the one on the road!
Watch it.
Check on the front camber.
The grip sucks when I turn.
Yes, sir!
Chief Jang!
- Yes.
It’s a job in Seoul.
Pyeongtaek Port, 9:00 p.m.
Pyeongtaek Port?
Is this job for Lim Ki-bang?
I told you not to take his gigs.
They’re messy.
It pays a lot.
If it’s messy, just dust it off.
You know the drill.
- Just call them a cab.
Come on!
Why do you think they called us?
They have their reasons.
I couldn’t care less.
But we make a living off
those reasons.
50:50.
All of a sudden?
- 50:50.
Deal.
I’m only going to deliver.
If it’s not packaged right,
I’m coming back.
Whatever you say, CEO Jang.
Uijeongbu Baseball Park.
Pick up at 8:00 p.m.
Drop off at Pyeongtaek Port.
Here’s the client plus one more.
There’ll be one backup car
at Pyeongtaek Port.
Get your own, if you need more.
- If things go wrong?
Take public transportation
and call with a 2G phone.
Here is the main entrance.
This is a side entrance.
There are two more here.
The client will be here.
This is you.
Where will you meet them?
I’ll go here. If I go on the roundabout,
it could be checkmate.
Right. And if flies tail you,
you can go here and lose them.
Then take the beltway.
- Okay.
What’s this blocking off
the intersection?
That’s just my lighter.
Stop!
Why do you always forget things?
Drive safely.
- Yes, sir.
Boss?
- She forgot this, too.
Jeez...
Just one more. The last strike!
What a naïve son of a bitch.
I’ll meet you there.
Seo-won.
I only won 8 games at most
in a season.
But you can win 20
and go to the Major Leagues!
You told me not to play baseball.
You hate it.
Who says I hate baseball?
Baseball hated me.
Our ride is here!
Shit!
Dang. That bastard can’t even run?
Dad...
BOSS CHO
Why is this on?
Go to the other side.
- Hey, Du-shik!
Why don’t you answer your phone?
Hey, Du-shik!
Seo-won. Look at me.
Make sure you don’t lose this.
Du-shik!
Memorize 6162.
Remember the fork by the entrance?
Find a car with plate 6162.
That’s our ride.
I’m starving.
Let’s get this over with!
Take my phone. If you forget,
turn it on to see then turn it off!
Take it.
- What about you?
I’ll be right behind you.
I’ll call you with this.
Okay?
Stop. Don’t cry.
A man’s gotta have guts!
Got it?
Now, go!
Chubby!
Where is he?
Did you eat?
Get lost, assholes!
Out of my way, bastards!
Cho Kyeong-pil!
Jesus!
I played baseball as a boy.
How’d it go?
Was it like this?
Shit!
Foul!
Look!
I gave you a chance!
To bleed bastards like you dry!
I let you be a CEO!
But you stabbed me in the back!
Stabbed? Do you even feel pain?
Look Du-shik.
I’ll ask you one last time.
Where’s the security fob?
Come on, man! Just tell me!
Sure.
Where is it?
I ate it.
What did you say?
Cut my gut and take it.
Fine, I will.
Hurry Dad...
Is it a no- show?
Find him.
Scatter out!
There he is!
Open up! Please!
Help me!
- Kid! Come here! Stop!
Help me, please!
Open the door!
Please!
Plate 6162!
Stop him!
Stop the car!
Stop! What the hell?
Stop!
Damn it!
The security fob isn’t here.
The kid must have it.
As I came,
Du-shik was happy to see my car.
He waved like this!
He was waiting for his ride.
Come out now.
The bitch who took him is good.
- What?
It was a girl!
Call Chief Woo.
Hello, sir.
I’m doing the laundry.
Yes, sir.
Wait for me!
Hey!
- I’m Kim Seo-won.
You left this.
Stop following me and go.
Take the subway over there.
I have nowhere to go.
- That’s not my business.
What if the gangsters come for me?
Call the cops.
- Dad said not to go to the cops!
Didn’t you come to rescue me?
Nope.
- But you saved me before.
I came to make money.
- I have money!
Forget it.
Dad said he’ll call.
Please stay with me until then.
Chief Jang! Explain yourself.
It’s a delivery glitch.
- Shit.
Are you with the client?
- Nope. Just his kid.
This is bad.
You can’t make a return, huh?
I told you not to take the gig!
Lim Ki-bang, that asshole!
Pull out.
I’ll cut lines with him.
Come back now.
Got the delivery fee?
- Not yet.
He left some money with the kid.
You gotta get paid.
Drop him off somewhere.
Hold on.
Kid!
I’m Kim Seo-won.
- Do you have a mom?
No grandma or grandpa?
Nope.
No aunts or uncles?
Got any friends?
- Do you, ma’am?
Lots.
He’s got no one.
Find a place for me, boss.
Make it quick.
Let’s do this.
I know a guy who deals with kids.
Leave the boy with him.
Then the delivery is done.
I have a dot here, too.
Wanna play word chain?
Word chain, please?
- Just sleep.
Nasty.
Nasty!
Typical games suck.
Suck? You’re good!
But sentences don’t count.
It has to be a word.
- Kid!
I’m Kim Seo-won.
Don’t call me ma’am.
Then what should I call you?
- Just don’t.
High shot!
Sent by Mr. Baek?
Are you Se-won?
I’m Seo-won.
Right Se-won. Come with me.
Want it?
Did you starve him?
Jeez.
Eat slowly.
How’s Mr. Baek doing?
I haven’t seen him in so long.
What do you do?
- Why?
Think I’ll make him sell gums?
That’s illegal now.
We do things legally to...
You’re done already?
Want another one?
Here.
Why you...
Let’s go.
Thank the lady.
Thank you.
Give my regards to Mr. Baek.
Come on.
Finished the delivery?
- Yes.
Okay. Well done.
Did you count the delivery fee?
- I’ll do it later.
You didn’t yet?
Must I do that now?
Just in case the kid paid wrong.
Count it!
It’s more than enough!
Don’t scream.
You always count the delivery fee!
What’s with you today?
Fine! I’ll count it!
What’s he doing with him?
What?
Where’s the kid?
He went into poo for so long.
Is he constipated?
Captain? Why the blood?
- What blood?
It’s nothing. Split apart.
Heard Kim Du-shik’s body was found
in the fire at the baseball park?
Yes, sir!
- Right after the fire,
a car was seen speeding out
of the park.
It’s an old BMW.
This is the car
we received a tip on.
This is from an intersection
near the ballpark before the fire.
The license plate
is from an expired vehicle.
It’s obviously a get- away car.
Kim Du-shik was murdered after this.
Next.
See? There’s a kid inside now.
That’s Kim Du-shik’s son,
Kim Seo-won.
An expired car,
then Kim Du-shik was murdered.
It means that driver with the cap
killed Kim and kidnapped his son.
It’s 10:10 P.M. now.
It’s been two hours!
The car could be anywhere.
- Find it.
Scan all nearby roads and highways.
Find the culprit now!
- Yes, sir!
Scatter out!
Sir?
- What?
Is it okay to investigate publicly?
Sang-hoon.
We’re not talking about $3000
but $30 million!
You can make $3000
if you work hard.
But $30 million?
You gotta put your life on the line.
RETURN KEYS HERE
Are you leaving me again?
No, I’m going to buy something.
Trust me now?
Ma’am?
Why is it so hard to live?
What do you mean?
I’m hungry.
Of course you are.
Express how it tastes. How is it?
It’s warm.
That’s not it, stupid!
You try it.
Excuse me.
May I ask
who is Mr. Lim Ki-bang?
What is it?
Who the hell are you?
That’s enough.
Stop it!
How can he talk
if you make him like this?
You’re extreme.
No going halfway.
Who are you?
He can talk, sir.
That son of a bitch.
Chief Jang? Call me.
You bitch! Are you nuts?
Why are you going AWOL?
Do you have flies on your tail?
If you come with luggage
and they find us, we’re dead!
Got it?
Chief Jang.
I’ll forgive you. Come back, please?
I’ll come after I give him this.
Let’s get to the point.
You’re the ones
who picked ‘em up, right?
No, sir.
I just got ‘em the passports
and the ship.
It’s called special delivery.
It’s a professional delivery service.
- Delivery service?
Yes.
- Where are they?
They just give me a number
for each pickup.
I called when they were late
for the ship, but no one answered.
You mean you have nothing much
to tell me?
Stop it! It hurts!
The car!
- What about it?
They carry many plates around
when they’re on the job.
When they get caught, they switch
the plates and take different cars.
That’s how they get away.
Stop everything and check on
car theft reports.
Then check footages of the culprit
where the cars were stolen.
Why’d you hit him so badly?
Go to the hospital now.
Don’t worry, bastards.
What did you say?
Go to the hospital.
Learn the definition of halfway.
Found her at a Mega Mart.
We’re combing through CCTV files.
Should we locate her and go?
Yes, of course.
But she’s a pro. Be careful.
The body was found
to be Kim Du-shik, who is wanted
for his role in match fixing.
Burned with signs of assault,
an autopsy is scheduled
for the exact cause of death.
Kim Du-shik, the suspect, has...
My dad is dead.
A woman who came with a boy.
Where are they?
Room 809.
Freeze!
Where are they?
They’re not here.
The bathroom’s empty.
They’re in another room!
Stop crying!
Kim Seo-won!
If you don’t wanna die, stop!
Okay?
Let’s go.
Police! Open up!
What the hell?
Almost missed it. Excuse me.
Let’s say you delivered this to me.
Go home.
Didn’t get paid? Then I’ll pay.
It’ll be hard on a cop’s salary.
Good eye.
Too good to just deliver.
His dad took something of mine.
The kid took it by mistake.
I just want what’s mine.
Then what?
I’m still working on that.
But still! He saw me kill his
dad and that means trouble.
Kid? Do you remember me?
Know how to shoot?
Shit.
Kid! I’ll come for you soon!
Wait for it!
Is this what he’s looking for?
If I give it do him,
will he stop coming?
Wow!
Okay, I hear you.
Calm down. Jeez.
Just a bit more...
Are you okay to talk?
Yes, go on.
What about the police?
They want info on a murder suspect
who is a North Korean defector.
The commissioner wants you
on the job, ma’am.
Damn it!
I should never drive!
What defector?
Got the fingerprint ID?
What took so long?
Her prints weren’t in
in the criminals’ databases.
She was never caught once?
Who is she?
- Name, Jang Eun-ha. Age 28.
No family. No criminal history.
- Born in...
South Pyongan Province?
She’s a North Korean defector.
That’s why she’s so feisty!
Current address?
- Residence unknown.
So, all we fished out
is that she’s a commie?
Maybe you were fishing
in the wrong place.
Hello.
Hi.
Who?
HAN MI-YOUNG
Not busy these days? No spies?
Why would NIS agents come here?
We’re busy.
But this case is a headache for us.
If people say
we didn’t manage defectors well,
then it’ll be a bigger headache.
If you filtered out commie offenders,
this wouldn’t have happened.
Right.
So we came to make right
and help you arrest the culprit.
Jang Eun-ha.
I’m the one who first reviewed her.
She’s something.
She’s the only one of her family
who survived escaping North Korea.
Let’s see.
Murder, kidnapping...
What a headache.
Get to the point, please?
You have no idea
how to find Jang Eun-ha, right?
We’ll light the way for you.
All you have to do
is follow it and catch her.
How will you help us?
The police?
If the boss finds out
they’re on your tail, you’re dead!
I don’t care if he does or not.
Asif. Memorize this number. 0118.
0118? What’s that?
My door code.
Aren’t we moving a bit too fast?
Chubby! Go and feed him for me.
Bye.
- Okay.
Not bad.
Who’s Chubby?
Is it your cat?
- Yup.
You live with a cat?
Isn’t it cute?
It looks mean.
No way! It’s pretty. Look closely!
I want to go to my mom.
Please take me to her.
You said you don’t have one.
Dad said I didn’t, but I do.
Do you know where she is?
So many...
How do you know
your mom’s number is here?
I called all of them.
Then someone said she’s your mom?
No.
One of them didn’t say anything.
She just cried.
Get all the phone numbers on
the mobile station around Mega Mart.
Okay.
- How can we check all that?
Why check it all? Only a few
of them would use 2G phones.
Hello? Is this Ms. Park Ji-sun?
This is Cupid Flower,
a 24- hour flower delivery service.
Found her.
She just left Seoul Toll Gate
and is headed south.
We can narrow it down
to a 500- meter radius.
We’ll send updates on her locations!
Captain Cho?
Yes?
Call me when you find her.
Yes, ma’am!
Found her. End it before
the NIS agents come.
You’ve arrived at your destination.
Are you okay?
I’ll bring your mom, so stay put.
- Wait.
You can have this.
With this on,
you won’t lose it again.
Don’t open the door.
Sorry.
While I lived with Du-shik,
I got pregnant.
But I had a miscarriage early on.
Last year,
a kid called from Du-shik’s number.
I suddenly got sentimental
and cried.
He got the wrong idea.
So, you’re really not
Seo-won’s mom?
No way!
How many times did I say it?
Poor Seo-won.
He has no one else to go to.
By the way, how could you
think of taking him to his mom?
Du-shik’s killers
are looking for him.
Then who would they seek out?
His mom, of course.
The kid must’ve grown a lot.
Is he a good boy?
Don’t be curious.
I told you to wait in the car!
I’m sorry.
It’s okay. Let’s go.
What about Mom?
She’s not your mom.
You were wrong.
You’re lying!
I’ll ask her myself.
Why’d you break it!
How can you break it!
You’re right. She’s your mom!
But she doesn’t want to see you!
She doesn’t want to be your mom!
I don’t need you anymore.
You came to get paid, right?
Take it all! I’m leaving!
Fine! Go and hear it from her...
- Ma’am!
Take him.
Go on.
Take ‘em!
Ma’am!
Stay still!
What the hell?
Are you okay?
Come to the front.
Seatbelt on!
What bitch drives like that?
Ma’am!
No!
You have the money, right?
Dear god!
Yes?
You finally answer.
Been busy?
What are you up to, Captain?
I’m out catching a criminal,
of course.
That’s good.
We gave you her locations,
but you didn’t catch her.
I was worried something was wrong.
Thanks for worrying,
but we lost her.
Things don’t always
work out as planned.
It doesn’t seem like
Jang Eun-ha is a kidnapper.
What do you mean?
We got a tip saying
the kid begged for people’s help
and stopped a car and went with her.
Are you sure she’s a kidnapper?
We’ll catch her and prove it to you.
If you just hand over the evidence...
Forget it.
Looks like the light is off.
Let’s investigate separately.
If you need anything else,
send me an official request.
Bye now.
That son of a bitch!
That bitch!
Stupid bastard.
Can you talk?
Hold on! We’re almost there.
You finally found going halfway.
You have a contact
in the police, right?
Yes.
Cross check the evidence
at Kim Du-shik’s murder scene.
I’ll go to Jang Eun-ha’s last location.
Okay driving that far?
- I have no choice!
The first car that the bitch drove,
where was it registered?
Gangneung, sir.
- And the other plates?
The car she drove to the motel
and Daejeon?
They’re all from different cities
like Incheon.
They were all abandoned
and expired cars, right?
Find out where the cars were expired.
- Yes, sir.
Why’d you buy a junk car
for that much?
You have way too much money, huh?
And if you bought it,
why lose the key?
You always lose yours, too.
Put it in deeper.
About a thumb’s length.
You got a long way to go.
Then why don’t you do it?
Stop.
Now, turn right.
Wow! It worked!
Wanna drive, too?
- Sure!
Your legs are too short. Sit here.
Where do we go now?
Ever been to Busan?
- No!
Let’s go.
The customer you have reached
is busy....
Hello?
Boss.
- Why you!
Where are you?
What in the world are you up to?
I can’t find a place
to watch the kid.
I think...
- What?
You’ll bring him here?
Hurry.
Pardon?
- No delivery destination.
No returns. It’s the worst ever.
He’s with you, right?
Send his picture.
- Why?
The bastards are cops!
This place won’t be safe either.
Let’s send the kid abroad.
I’ll prepare his passport.
Let’s wrap it up like a pro.
Let’s finish the delivery.
Are you listening?
Yes, of course.
Stand straight.
That’s dirty!
- You’re dirty! Stay still!
Ready?
Hey!
One, two, three!
Asif! Bring me some coffee!
Ms. Jang Eun-ha.
Do you have a boyfriend?
Why?
- Just wondering.
What’s your ideal man?
Don’t know. Never thought of it.
- Then think now.
Someone who doesn’t
pee his pants.
ask silly questions. Happy?
Guess not.
TO BUSAN
But...
- What now?
Why’d you take my picture?
It’s for going abroad.
Who’s going abroad?
You.
- Are you coming, too?
No.
Why?
Aren’t we going to your house?
We found it, boss.
All three cars were expired in Busan.
They were taken by Baekgang Company.
I think it’s a junkyard.
You bastard!
A cop shouldn’t chuck trash!
I’m gonna retire anyway.
Let’s go get our retirement money!
Eun-ha!
What’s with this junk?
Watch it. It costs $20.000.
20 grand? Why?
Don’t know. Ask him.
Why is this $20.000?
What special delivery
takes so long?
Right.
Maybe we should stop this gig.
Let’s see.
Baek-yeon.
Yeok-bong.
How do you read this?
Ji-ho.
Which one do you like?
For what?
- Choose a name for yourself.
I already have a name.
- I know, it’s Kim Seo-won.
But lots of people have two names.
You know EXO?
They all have two names.
And Girlfriend?
- I don’t have a girlfriend.
No, Girlfriend, the group.
They all have two names, too.
This way! Good!
You’ll go on that car later.
I’m going abroad on a car?
- Yup.
There’s a huge ship
that takes cars like that.
Never been on a ship?
Just hold the wheel tight.
After sleeping 5 nights,
you’ll arrive in my hometown.
My dad promised to take care of you.
Seo-won will have to eat
curry everyday.
Boss!
Okay. Ji- ho!
How’s that?
Like it?
After we send the kid,
I’ll make a deal with this.
Tell ‘em to take it and scram.
His dad probably brought this
to make the same deal.
I’ll finish things off.
- Don’t bother.
You have a long way to go and learn.
Goal!
He brings back old memories?
Sir! How’ve you been?
Look.
I have way too much money
coming to me when I retire soon.
I can split it with you boys.
How about it?
What can we do for you, sir?
Find someone.
No, no, no.
Find one bitch and a kid.
Will you visit me?
We’ll see.
If you don’t have a boyfriend then,
want me to be one?
What did you do?
- Nothing.
Comb the area thoroughly
and let me know if you find anything.
Yes, sir!
Over here, sir!
Du-shik!
I’ll ask you one last time.
Where’s the security fob?
Where the hell is it! Tell me!
I ate it.
Cut my gut and take it.
He’s not chasing a killer.
He is the killer!
That bastard.
Where’s Cho Kyeong-pil now?
We lost track of him
after Busan Toll Gate.
Okay. I’ll head to Busan.
Ramen!
Men? Mental!
Talent.
Ent? Ent?
That’s hard!
Okay. Be there in two hours
when the ship departs.
Okay. Please take care of him.
You must’ve driven.
Don’t drive drunk.
Know who I am?
A gangster?
If not, you must be a cop.
Or are you both with two jobs?
I don’t care who you are.
Let me close up and go.
Go home!
Hide in here. Don’t move, okay?
If you tell me just 3 things,
I’ll let you go home.
Where’s the kid?
Where’s Jang Eun-ha?
Wanna die?
Should’ve kept better employees.
Why use commies
and illegal immigrants?
Small business owners
need to save on labor.
That’s true.
Jang Eun-ha is damn good
at what she does.
I’ve hired many drivers
over the years.
But no one can work like her.
She’s better than me in my prime.
Student excels the master.
- Jeez.
When I first met Eun-ha,
I went to pick her up
as she crossed over.
The girl was covered in blood.
I’m just like her now.
Are you a commie, too?
Nope. I’m from Seoul.
It was a side gig
when I ran a business in Russia.
Taking runaway commies to Korea.
I had two jobs.
Wow!
What a businessman!
So, where is she?
Huh?
Who’s that? A new face!
Illegal alien.
You can tell me.
Where’s Jang Eun-ha and the kid?
Don’t speak Korean?
Where is Jang Eun-ha?
Talk to me.
Money!
I’ll pay you, so speak.
I’ll give you money.
Very big money!
Fuck you!
Fuck?
The bastard speaks Korean well.
Asif!
Stay put!
Stop it!
I’ll tell you! Stop it!
I don’t know where they are.
I told them I’d call when I’m done.
But I know
what you’re looking for.
What am I looking for?
The bank security fob, isn’t it?
I’ll give it to you if you let us go.
That’s my condition.
Where is it?
Ogwang, go.
- Yes, sir.
Sir! There’s a lock.
Fingerprint verification.
Take ‘em out!
Pull ‘em out at once,
so it’ll hurt less.
Pull ‘em all at once!
How much
are you getting paid for this?
Putting your life on the line,
will you get a few hundred thousand?
Think I’d do this
for a few hundred thousand?
Boss...
Asif, you idiot.
I told you to go home.
You never listen.
Shit.
Is this what you’re looking for?
Let’s find the kid and end this.
$100.000 bonus to the first one
who finds him! Go!
Find the kid!
What is it?
We received reports of gunfire
at a junkyard in Busan.
It’s Baekgang Company
run by Baek Gang-chul...
Baek Gang-chul?
That’s it!
He brought Jang Eun-ha to Korea!
Call Busan police for backup!
Found 100 grand!
Sir!
Told ya I’d find him!
Hello, kid.
I told you I’d get you soon.
What?
What the hell?
Damn it! Turn on the lights!
Jang Eun-ha!
Let’s go.
Run! Hurry!
Bitch! You’re dead!
Bro! Are you okay?
Kim Seo-won!
Bro...
Asif...
Asif is over there.
He’s hurt badly.
Wait. Hold on.
Let the kid go.
Let’s end this already!
Got a smoke on ‘ya?
Shit. I left ‘em somewhere.
Hey!
Why are you asking to die?
When people are dying to live?
Didn’t you come to Korea
for a better life?
Why pull all this damn shit
for this kid!
Are you okay, ma’am?
Do I look okay to you?
I do all the driving
and the fighting...
Some boyfriend, you are.
What’s she saying?
Don’t worry, Kim Seo-won.
Let’s go together.
So damn heartrending.
Jang Eun-ha!
Life is...
going on your own.
Split up!
I’ll be right there.
What?
Ma’am! Please save her for me!
Please save her!
Take him.
Please!
No!
Ms. Jang Eun-ha? How are you?
I’m doing fine.
We have a new student.
Seo-won, greet the class.
I moved to a new school.
It’s really far from my old one,
so it was hard to adjust at first.
But I have many friends now.
Goal!
I live with Seung-wan
and play with him all the time.
Try it! It’s yummy.
Hurry!
I live at Happy Home Orphanage.
The food is great
and the teachers are very nice.
But the school bus driver
drives really roughly.
But he drives less dangerously
than you, ma’am.
By the way,
Asif takes good care of Chubby.
Eat lots.
- So don’t worry.
And...
That’s it for now.
I’ll leave the rest for later.
Bye!
Mister!
Ma’am!
Why you!
Hop on. I’ll drive you home.
SPECIAL DELIVERY
PICK UP ONE AT 7:00 P.M.
DROP OFF AT INCHEON PORT 8:00 P.M.
Can we drop by somewhere first?