Since its formation, the Earth
has experienced five mass extinctions.
The sixth is just beginning.
CARIBBEAN SEA
off the coast of Puerto Rico
Eating that crap again?
Gimme a break. Give it back.
Eat some fruit.
Back off.
Tom!
Help!
How about I lock in the kids?
Silly.
- You made a wish?
- Sure, I did.
A good luck charm
to ward off evil spirits.
So soon?
- Ben, you good?
- Yeah.
- Okay, Cassie?
- Yes.
What was that?
Be careful.
Hold still.
If you keep moving, I can't do it.
Fucking hell!
Ben, seriously? We're in deep shit here!
Beat it.
Get off my bed. Move!
Fucking move!
It's gross.
You got crumbs everywhere.
Shit!
Watch out!
Mom...
Kids?
What?
Honey...
We don't know for sure.
Don't go imagining the worst.
Come on.
Go away.
Go away, will you!
We gotta go. Pack up your stuff.
Come on, let's go.
Come with me.
Stop it! Stop!
Cassie!
Mom!
What's going on?
Hide back there!
Mom?
There! Move it!
Get in.
Fast! Come on!
If it's not me, the flare's loaded.
Shoot!
Get it? Shoot if it's not me.
Shoot.
Shoot!
Get out!
Get out.
Mom, what the hell are you doing?
Forget the supplies!
Hurry!
Forget the bags!
Let's go!
Drink. A few sips.
You think he saw the balloons?
What?
The psycho.
You think he saw the balloons?
Stop.
Don't say that.
Don't blame yourself.
There was no way of knowing.
Don't blame yourself, okay?
It's not your fault. Got it?
It's not your fault.
I'll do all I can to protect you.
I won't let anyone hurt you.
No one.
What?
Come on!
Go!
Keep going!
What's wrong?
Dehydration. You need fluids.
Hold on.
Who the hell did this?
Drink what's left.
I think I left it unscrewed.
Shit, Cassie, it's empty!
It wasn't on purpose.
How do we survive without water?
Don't yell at me. Back off.
It's not like we won't die anyway.
- Don't say that!
- Why? We're gonna croak.
It's the truth!
You think you can save us
but you can't!
Nobody can save us.
We're gonna croak here.
Dad got slaughtered by a freak.
and you're obsessed about a bottle.
A fucking bottle!
Enough!
Shut up, that's enough!
Shut up!
Go right.
Thanks.
Try to get some sleep.
I can't believe he's gone forever.
I feel like...
I've fallen off a cliff.
I know.
Tell me the story of how you met again.
The first time I saw him,
I was 22.
I was training
at the hospital in Nice.
And one morning...
a German was brought in
after a diving accident.
What was he doing?
Research for his thesis
on red gorgonians dying out
in the Mediterranean.
On what?
They look like coral.
Anyway, he'd had a...
decompression issue on a dive.
He spent three days
in a hyperbaric chamber.
There are better first meetings.
As soon as he got out,
he started hitting on me.
It worked?
Not right away.
I set him straight.
As his doctor.
As if that would stop him.
Two days later,
outside the hospital,
he was waiting with flowers.
Old school.
We spent a whole week together.
It was...
He had to go back to Germany.
I thought...
I'd never see him again.
And then?
Six months later, he...
He was there,
outside the hospital.
And...
he declared his undying love.
With a poem by Victor Hugo.
"It's enough for you to fly away.
"For me to fly too."
Then,
he explained
he'd got his degree
and been offered a job in Miami.
And he'd only accept it
if I agreed to go with him.
Not an easy decision.
To practice in the USA,
I had to requalify.
You know what he said?
Every problem has a solution.
What could have done this?
Whatever it was, it's not human.
So there's something out there
even nastier than this wacko.
Come on.
Let's go.
Wait!
Where you going?
Wait for us.
Get out of there right now!
Don't!
Are you nuts? You'll get sick!
Kids!
We can't stay here.
What's going on?
Move it!
Look!
People.
Let's go.
There's a woman and children!
Forget about it.
Look, behind them!
Help!
There's more of them. Get inside!
Help us!
Go on, Cassie, climb up.
Keep going!
C'mon, kids.
Back up.
Mom!
We went for help. There's no one!
Where's Ben?
Where'd you learn to do that?
Cassie, keep watch.
Shit, a radio!
Grab that gun!
Work, dammit.
Channel 16.
Work.
Nao?
Look, over there.
Shit...
That rift.
Let's go.
What's with "save my children" earlier?
Ben, c'mon!
Mom, all good?
Keep going.
Watch out!
Hurry!
Here we go again.
Shit!
Watch out!
Mom?
Climb over!
Hold on, listen to me.
Keep going!
- What?
- Just go!
No!
Keep going, I said!
No, climb over it!
Just go!
Climb over it!
Hurry!
Climb!
Mom, we're not going anywhere.
Come with us, for fuck's sake!
Not without you!
Take Ben and go!
You hear me? Just go!
I'll find you.
I'll find you. Now go!
We're going. Come on!
Careful.
There!
Nao!
Wait!
Come on.
Grab my hand.
There's room for you.
Climb up, come on.
Give me that.
Inside!
Go on, get in.
C'mon, now!
- Fast!
- Get inside!
Hurry up, Ben!
How does this shut?
Turn it.
We're good.
Push it.
Sit down. Get in your seats!
Fast!
Strap in!
- Fuck it!
- Look...
Cross them in front.
SURVIVE