Downloaded from
YTS.MX
Official YIFY movies site:
Your breakfast, Mr. Soliman.
I don't care about cantaloupe!
Tastes like melon! -It will
never happen again, I promise.
- Yalla, habibi, come back!
- Just going to clean up.
- I'll be very fast.
- I'm not done yelling at you!
Unit two, I've lost camera four.
We need eyes
on the rooftop terrace.
I'm in.
Okay, Mr. Shark, you're up.
SHARK
Nice work, rookie.
- I'm on my way.
- Yasmin told me
- I need to be more attentive.
- What?
You are very attentive.
I know. That's what I told her.
Yalla, did you get a haircut?
I did.
- Thank you for noticing.
- It's very nice.
All clear on the roof.
GUARD 2
Copy that.
Uh, that was me.
- It-It's still Shark.
- Yeah, no.
I got that. Thank you.
All right,
Mr. Piranha, go crazy.
Mr. Snake, that's your cue.
Hope your timing's right, kid.
Snake, be nice to the rookie.
It's her first heist.
I was being nice.
It's just how I sound.
Welcome to the team.
See?
All right.
We finished, uh,
with the banter?
Let's do this.
Come on. Five.
- Four.
- Three.
- Two.
- One.
It's showtime.
Hello, Mr. Soliman.
The Bad Guys!
Remind me again:
Why didn't you just
come through the front door?
- Where's the fun in that?
- He loves an entrance.
Stay back, you... you monsters!
Monsters?
Wow.
- Did he just say "monsters"?
- He did.
I wouldn't have done that.
You like monsters?
I'll show you a monster, pal.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
P-Please.
- Whoa.
- Okay, I see you.
Check this out. -No, no.
No, no, please. Mr. Wolf.
Oh, baby, where have you been
all my life?
No! No!
- No, no.
- Not bad. Not bad.
This is... this is
a one-of-a-kind prototype.
Shiny!
Wait. We did all this
for a car? -
Listen, kid, the heist is never
really about the loot, okay?
- It's a power move, baby.
- -Let's go.
I-I have to say--
No, no. No, this--
It's never been driven!
Don't worry.
We brought you
a little parting gift.
We're classy like that.
For me?
Nice.
Ooh, you say
the naughtiest things.
No! No!
You Bad Guys will never
get away with this!
Go bad...
Or go home.
♪ You see, steel sharpen steel
when it's time for the go... ♪
After them!
♪ Stare every challenge
in the eye ♪
♪ We don't play with the soul,
no matter what you was told ♪
♪ Every rat find a hole ♪
♪ See, it don't matter
what you thought ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ We taking
everything you want ♪
- ♪ Whoa, whoa, whoa ♪
- ♪ Now don't forget it ♪
♪ Better know we come to get it
and we with it ♪
♪ And there's nothing better ♪
♪ I hope you know
to play it smart ♪
Get out of the way!
Hey, guys, watch this.
Step on it!
Do you always drive like this?
Only when
it's strictly necessary.
And it's always necessary.
♪ And there's nothing better ♪
♪ I hope you know
to play it smart ♪
♪ No matter what you thought,
you better believe we coming ♪
♪ And if you thought
that we was playing ♪
♪ Let me show you something,
so then we jump ♪
♪ And we swoop
and we dodge every bullet ♪
♪ It don't matter
when they pull up ♪
♪ And they try to pull it ♪
There! The bridge!
That's our exit!
I gotcha.
- Piranha, check our six.
- I got it.
All clear, papo.
It's the Bad Guys!
♪ Better know we on the clock
and it's time to go ♪
♪ Everything is tactical,
now enjoy the show ♪
♪ Then we skip and we bounce
and we hop ♪
♪ Out of every situation... ♪
Whoa.
♪ See, it don't matter
what you thought ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah... ♪
Uh-oh.
♪ Better know we come to get it
and we with it ♪
♪ And there's
nothing better... ♪
Wolf, you got a secret plan,
or are we just dead?
- I'll let you know in a minute.
- The ramp!
- Yes?
- Punch it. I have an idea.
Okay. New kid,
let's see what you got.
♪ Better wear your seat belt
and strap up... ♪
♪ I know the way you see us
doing it to 'em ♪
♪ I think you really, really
need to shack up ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
- ♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
- ♪ It don't matter ♪
♪ Every single time
they really try to trap us ♪
♪ And they come from every
corner and they really try... ♪
- Rookie...
- Wha-bam!
♪ Better get up out of the way ♪
♪ Because we come
and then we pack up ♪
♪ And we taking
everything you want ♪
♪ You know you better back up ♪
♪ Let's go ♪
♪ Let's go. ♪
Yeah, baby!
Welcome to the crew, kid.
- Call me Webs.
- Ooh, punchy.
Okay, okay.
I am never driving another car
ever agai--
Nice carbon footprint, jackass!
Classy.
Come on. Easy, now. Easy, easy.
Come on, girl. You got this.
Ugh.
Oh, hey. Look who it is.
Get over here.
Where you been
keeping yourselves?
Me?
Oh, terrific.
Fantastic.
I mean,
not everyone believes it,
but, uh, the Bad Guys went good.
I'll spare you the details,
but in a nutshell,
we felt the wag of doing good.
Made a couple of new friends...
Diane?
You're the Crimson Paw?
We took down Marmalade,
a real bad guy.
The Crimson Paw!
Me? No, no, no.
She's the Crimson Paw.
And surprised everyone
by turning ourselves in.
Yeah, we had a pretty good run
as bad guys,
but sometimes you got
to give up the thing you know
in order to find
something better.
So here we are,
law-abiding citizens
starting over
with a clean slate,
and we cannot wait for society
to welcome us with open arms.
And-and now you want to work,
uh, at-at a bank?
Why not? Some of
my best memories are at banks.
Uh, you robbed us three times.
That was this bank?
It says here that you saved the
city from an evil guinea pig,
but aren't you
a notorious criminal?
Yes. No.
M-Maybe?
Sor... Sorry, nerves.
I-I mean, I-I can also do
a great tuna impression.
It's like you're talking
to a tuna, right?
Well, I'm proficient
in Unix, Linux, Windows, Mac
and fluent
in 87 coding languages,
so, yeah, I'm qualified.
I see.
And, um, how do you explain
this gap
in your employment history?
Uh...
My salary expectations?
Wow. That's a good question.
No one's ever given me money
on purpose before.
"Great at Secret Santa"?
Yeah. How does that...
W-W-Wait. Don't tell me.
Bath bomb. Lavender.
And how would you react if you
saw a coworker doing something
that violates company policy?
Snitches get stitches
and sleep with the fishes.
You know what? Can I act--
Can I get another chance
at that one?
I think we got
everything we need.
- So great to meet you.
- Thanks for coming in.
Uh, we're gonna...
we're gonna pass.
Uh, look, Craig,
anyone who wants to change
needs to start somewhere, right?
So I'm just asking for a chance.
Just a chance.
Please?
You know what, Mr. Wolf?
I might-- you know, I might,
I might have
something here for you.
I'm gonna give you a call.
Gee. R-Really?
Craig, that's great!
Number's on my résumé there.
- Okay. Uh...
- And this has been just great.
- You can let go now.
- Sorry.
I didn't mean to...
I got a job!
This is fantastic, man.
Oh, by the way, Craig,
uh, you know...
Ah.
Yeah. Got it.
...to a better future.
In three weeks, my next-gen
MoonX rocket will blast off
and deploy the Power Cell X3.
That's right.
Free wireless charging
from outer space
directly to your phone.
- You're welcome, world.
- Hey, guys. -Hey! -Wolfie.
Wolf! So you got the job?
Well, I mean,
it's not a hundred percent,
but he said,
he said he'd call me.
Well, you did better
than Piranha.
I thought I was supposed
to project confidence.
Yeah, but why a tuna?
What? Tunas are confident.
What tuna do you know
that's not confident?
All of them.
- Tunas are confident.
- Right?
Guys, come on.
Life's like a car chase.
You know what I mean?
There's-there's gonna be
bumps in the road, but
when has that ever stopped us?
Never.
It's just gonna take
a little time,
but I promise you,
people will come around.
Even if we get framed for the
Phantom Bandit's crime spree?
That's awfully specific.
Who's the Phantom, uh-- Who?
You haven't heard?
It's all over the news.
There's a battle
of survival for the bil--
The Phantom Bandit hit
three locations yesterday,
stealing several
priceless artifacts.
The Phantom is known
for being impossible to trace,
but this time,
he left a calling card.
Wait, hey, hey!
That's our move.
Exactly.
Commissioner, are the Bad Guys
back to a life of crime,
or are they being framed?
Just like your face
with those fabulous bangs!
Thank you. I cut them myself.
Look, I cannot comment
on an ongoing investigation,
but let's just say:
once a con, always a con.
- So it's the Bad Guys?
- I said no comment!
- Come on.
- What?
How are we supposed
to get a fresh start
when we get blamed for
every bad thing that happens?
Hey, guys.
Isn't the sun
particularly radiant today?
- What are you wearing?
- What are you drinking?
Wheatgrass kombucha
with extra moss
and two shots
of cold-pressed dandelion.
Uh, I don't think you're
supposed to eat those things.
Aw, you guys.
I wish I could trade
lighthearted japes
with you all night,
but I'm late for vinyasa.
- Vinyasa?
- W-W-Wait. You're going out?
But y-you just got back.
You know how it is.
You think I got this body
by sitting around, watching TV?
- Okay, ew.
- Oh, and don't wait up for me.
It's lucha night.
Well, bye...!
Guys, I think
the kombucha ate his brain.
Hey, you know what?
As long as he's happy, right?
- And you're not?
- I'd be happier
if I could land
one of these jobs.
- First impressions
are hard to shake.
Ooh, that was quick.
I mean, when I first met you,
I thought you were arrogant,
self-satisfied,
dishonest...
...greedy, for sure.
Oh, yeah?
What changed your mind?
What do you mean?
Ha ha ha. Very funny.
Seriously, it's hard
to stay positive
when we keep getting rejected.
It makes you feel--
I don't know-- hopeless.
Mm.
I mean, going good was the
hardest thing that I ever did.
And compared to you guys,
I had it easy.
No one ever knew
I was the Crimson Paw.
I'm sorry,
did you say you were the
Crimson Paw?!
Sorry.
I didn't quite catch that.
Okay, you asked for it.
You're about to discover
why they call me
the Big Bad Wo--
I think I got carried away.
I don't think this is gonna
help my-- with my interviews.
I don't know. I think it's cute.
- Gives you character.
- Oh.
Do I have a concussion, or is
the governor flirting with me?
- Can't it be both?
- Hmm.
- Uh, uh...
- Oh, uh...
- Sorry, I shouldn't have...
- Oh, no, no, no.
I-I didn't really, um...
Uh, yeah, 'cause
you're the governor,
- and I'm, you know.
- An-an ex-con.
- Yeah.
- I know.
It's optics.
- Totally.
- Let's just...
- Yeah, let's keep it friendly.
- ...keep it friendly.
- Medium friendly?
- Yeah.
- Madam Governor.
- Oops.
Madam Governor.
Sorry to interrupt
you and your acquaintance...
Finally, she remembers my name.
...but you've got the
children's hospital fundraiser
in 20 minutes.
- I'll be right there, Maureen.
- Oh, good. Thank you.
Another fundraiser?
Oof, look at you.
Same time next week?
My calendar's wide open.
Hey.
I know it's tough,
but you can't lose hope, okay?
People do want to trust you.
You just have to give them
a reason.
Promise?
Governor's word.
But until then, I would work
on that right hook.
It feels a little like I'm
getting kissed by a butterfly.
Catch you later, tough guy.
I was holding back.
Huh.
"Give them a reason."
No!
I said no comment!
I want answers.
Get me security footage,
scour the phone logs,
and where's my coffee?!
- Uh, Commissioner?
- Not now!
- But you have a visitor.
- They can wait.
Uh, but he's, uh...
Hey-hey, Chief!
Can I just say:
love the bangs.
First off,
it's "Commissioner" now.
And second...
Ooh, nice.
What's the difference?
Well, the chief is the top
uniformed officer, whereas--
Why am I explaining this
to you?!
Did you touch my board?
- My board. My beautiful board.
- Oh, I'm sorry.
I thought I heard it say,
"Solve me."
- Wolf.
- Listen.
I think we're both having
an optics problem.
You need to show the world
you've got this investigation
under control,
and we need
to show the world we're good.
If I help you catch the Bandit,
it's a win-win.
I'm calling the governor.
Go ahead.
It was basically her idea.
Look at this.
Each of the robberies occurred
within a three-minute window.
- So?
- Three minutes is the loop rate
of most standard
security consoles,
which means whoever did this...
Patched into security
from the inside.
Bingo.
Fine.
Let's say they did.
How would we even trace that?
We'd need some kind of
high-tech computer expert.
They'd have had to clone the IP
address and redirect the feed
to a four gigahertz
dummy console, duh.
Huh?
Your Bandit is clever
but not as clever
as he thinks he is.
However, he'd still need
an inside man.
Hmm.
Hey.
Hold this.
Hmm.
There!
But that's just the janitor.
Perhaps to the untrained eye,
but if he's really
just the janitor,
why is he pushing around
an empty bucket?
Hmm?
So the real question is:
How did he get in?
I'd come this way, jam the fan,
pop the grate,
and bam, you're in.
Ooh, ugh.
Why is there pickles in this?
Because that's my lunch.
Who said you could eat my lunch?
Well, he said there was lunch.
Chief, come on. Let's focus.
So we know when and we know how.
The real question is why.
Well, why don't you call
some more people
to barge in and help?
Ooh!
SNAKE
Welcome, friend,
to Mr. Snake's voicemail.
Today's advice for the soul:
We must stop concentrating
on our differences
and look for
what we have in common.
- Namaste.
- Ugh.
Bye...!
Is he possessed?
Ugh, don't even get me started.
I mean, one day he's going
to yoga, he's doing pottery.
I mean, who does pottery,
the cast of Ghost?
Guys, guys, guys, guys. Hold on.
- Huh?
- What'd he say again?
"Look for what we have
in common."
Look. It's not about
the artifacts.
It's about
what they have in common.
They're all made from a rare
metal called MacGuffinite.
Of course.
Uh, MacGuff-a-what, now?
Um, sounds kind of made-up.
So does the word "gold"
if you didn't know it was real.
Say "gold."
- Gold. Gold. -Gold. Gold.
- Gold.
- Gold. -Gold.
That does sound made-up.
Oh, now I can't stop thinking
how it sounds weird. Gold.
So now that we know
what the Bandit is after...
We can figure out
where he's gonna strike next!
There you go.
That's the chief I know.
Mmm. You grinding
your own beans these days?
It's "Commissioner."
Now get out of my office.
Yeah!
♪ Shake your groove thing ♪
♪ Shake your groove thing,
yeah, yeah... ♪
Next thing you know,
we're on TV getting medals.
Naming streets after us.
Piranha Street, baby.
Hey, listen to this.
Translated into English,
the word "MacGuffinite" means
"a small MacGuffin." Cute.
Okay. Not super helpful,
but, uh, what else you got?
The most famous
MacGuffinite object is
the Belt of Guatelamango.
Did you say
the Belt of Guatelamango?
- You heard of that?
- Heard of it?
It's the championship trophy
for the Lords of Lucha
tournament.
Uh-oh.
Wait, isn't that
where Snake is going tonight?
That's right.
Can you imagine him
at a wrestling match?
- He hates crowds.
- And loud music.
And flamboyant costumes.
And things
that make life worthwhile.
Oh, no.
Ow!
It's Snake!
It's all right here.
Happy hour. Pottery. Yoga.
All the same times
as the Bandit's robberies.
He's been lying to us
this whole time.
Ooh, he's such a little snake.
- That's why he's so happy.
- Oh.
Vinyasa, my butt.
If he gets caught,
he's going back to prison.
We got to find him before
Police Chief cracks the case.
Uh-oh.
Hello?
Guess who has two thumbs, bangs
and cracked the case?
- This gal!
- Oh, really?
It's going down tonight
at the Lords of Lucha
tournament. -
I am gonna catch
that Bandit red-handed.
I got to say, well done, Wolf.
Well done.
You have exceeded my...
- Bro, that was our only phone!
- What the thorax?
I don't know. I panicked!
Guys, there's only
one play here:
find our friend and...
Tear him apart limb by limb
until all he can remember
is pain!
Wow, okay.
I was gonna say save him,
but, sure, if there's time,
we can do the limb thing.
Ladies and gentlemen,
put your hands together
for the current
reigning world champion,
Handsome Jorge!
Ha ha! Yes!
Face of an angel.
Punch of el diablo.
Ha! Ha!
Snake!
I'm gonna kill you!
Wow.
And Mama said
I'd never get to heaven.
Look at me now, Mama!
I'm gonna need
a lot of mustard.
Piranha, check it out.
One in your size
and one in my size!
Guys, we can shop later.
Right now, we need to find
Snake. Let's go. Come on.
Ooh. Right, right, right,
right, right.
- It's just so much!
- Now, listen.
He could be anywhere.
Webs, search the upper deck.
I'll look ringside.
- You two...
- Guys!
I can't believe
you came all this way
just to see me arrest the Band--
- What? What was that?
- I don't know.
I panicked, okay?
I'm a panicker.
Okay, no more panicking.
Webs, search the upper deck.
You two, backstage.
Remember, we're dealing
with a master of deception
who can move like water
and vanish like smoke.
- He could be anywhere...
- There he is.
- Snake!
- Huh?
We know everything!
What? How did you find out?
Ow!
Snakey Cakes?
Huh?
Uh...
If I knew you were
expecting friends,
I would've gotten more nachos.
Because, well, I know
you don't like to share.
That's true.
- Unless it's kisses.
- Mmm.
Then he likes to share,
- don't you, Snakey Wakey?
- Oh, yeah.
Guys, this is Susan.
Hey.
Is she your hostage?
No!
She's my girlfriend.
She called him Snakey Cakes!
Huh. So these are the roommates.
Roommates?
Did you say "roommates"?
Hey, I'm pulling
your whiskers, Whiskers.
Snakey here told me
all about you guys.
Wait, wait. I'm-I'm just
trying to do the math here.
You're with Snake on purpose?
Well, you talk pretty tough
for a mango with teeth.
What? Is that what I look like?
Ooh, she is spicy. I like it.
Insult me next.
Are you ready to dance?
Another victory
for Handsome Jorge!
CROWD
Jorge! Jorge!
No one can defeat
my handsomeness.
And now bring down
the Belt of Guatelamango!
Oh, my gosh! It's the belt!
Give me the belt!
Give me that belt! I love it!
Wait a minute. Fans...
Can it be?
Yes! It looks like
we have a new challenger!
Someone has
a death wish big enough
to take on Handsome Jorge!
CROWD
Jorge! Jorge!
Jorge! Jorge! Jorge!
Of course.
What better way to steal
the belt than to win it?
That's the Phantom Bandit!
Ha ha.
So, you want that belt, huh?
We got to expose him.
How are we supposed to do that?
We improvise.
Well, come and get it, pig--
Wow!
He means business!
Yeah!
C-C-Can we talk about this?
This is wrestling at its best!
Not the face.
I didn't really think
that through.
Uh-oh.
Huh?
Whoo.
You ever been deboned
by a chicken?
Who's ready for some violence?!
" playing) -Violence!
Violence! Yes!
Guys, go for the mask.
♪ I said I like it like ♪
♪ Now, I like dollars,
I like diamonds... ♪
♪ I like million-dollar deals ♪
♪ Where's my pen?
... I'm signing ♪
♪ I like those Balenciagas... ♪
Spider!
Now the mask. Go for the mask!
♪ I like textses from my exes ♪
♪ When they want
a second chance ♪
♪ I like proving ... wrong,
I do what they say I can't ♪
♪ They call me Cardi Bardi,
banging body ♪
♪ Spicy mami, hot tamale... ♪
♪ Hop out the stu,
jump in the coupe ♪
♪ Big Dipper
on top of the roof ♪
♪ Flexing on ...
as hard as I can... ♪
♪ Told that ...
I'm sorry, though ♪
♪ 'Bout my coins
like Mario... ♪
Snake attack!
Whoa, wait! Whoa, whoa! Ow!
♪ I said I like it like... ♪
Great.
All together now!
Ladies and gentlemen,
this is no luchador.
It's the Phantom Bandit.
She came here to steal
the... the...
belt?
Good luck getting
out of this one, Bad Guys.
Huh?
- What?
- Huh?
Uh-oh.
- It's the Bad Guys!
- They're stealing the belt!
Let's get them!
Run!
Piranha, will you take off
the belt? -I can't get it off!
- Take off the belt!
- I can't get it off!
My belt! My belt! Get 'em!
Chief.
Chief, it's not
what it looks like!
I... I trusted you.
People! We've got a code 12!
Bad Guys are the bandits!
Mobilize!
OFFICER
Yes, ma'am.
Uh-oh.
- What do we do now?
- Wolf!
Get in!
You heard the bird. Get in!
Go, go!
Wow, that was close.
Stop this truck now!
Hold on, folks!
Wolf!
Sorry.
Isn't she great?
Bad Guys.
I'm getting too old for this.
All units. All units.
Suspects are headed east
in a hot dog truck.
OFFICER 2
Can you be more specific?
Um, it looks to be all beef,
possibly chorizo.
I need birds in the sky,
roadblocks every five miles.
I want eyes on every motel,
greasy spoon,
gas station, bus station,
cattle station, mole hole,
vole hole and watering hole
within 80 miles.
Let's go!
Now it's personal.
They fell for it.
Just like you planned, boss.
FEMALE VOICE
Good. Let's go.
Well, that went sideways.
Susan, you were amazing.
Where'd you learn
to drive like that? -
I used to deliver pizzas.
Got canned for being too fast.
Cool.
- Your breath stinks.
- What?
What do you brush
your teeth with, sardines?
That's a burn.
I don't brush my teeth
with anything.
Shocking. Uh...
That's kind of bad.
I'm surprised
you hang out with me.
- How about a mint?
- Ooh. That's clutch.
- Yes, please.
- I'll take two.
Uh, what about you, Wolf? Mint?
I'm good. Thanks.
So, how'd you guys meet anyway?
Spill it. Spill it.
- Okay, well, uh...
- Well...
You tell it. -No, no, no,
you tell it better.
Yeah, but you do all the voices.
And, like, you're so good at it.
Can somebody tell it?!
Okay, okay.
It's a funny story.
Hey, kid.
SNAKE and SUSAN:
Are you gonna eat that?
What?
♪ I think I could... ♪
Hey.
Um...
Mix-up.
♪ Crimson and clover. ♪
Why is she in his mouth?
Anyway, that's how we met.
But-but that's nothing
compared to our first date
- when we were...
- Ew, no! -Stop!
All right, all right, all right.
Got it.
Love triumphs over all,
and that's great.
But right now,
we need to focus on the fact
that every cop in the state
thinks we're the Phantom Bandit.
Hmm.
Not much of a romantic, are you?
Don't mind him, Sugar Beak.
He's a little touchy.
Uh, he's been friend-zoned
by the governor.
I have not been
friend-zoned by the...
I need a phone.
Madam Governor. Madam Governor.
How soon are the Bad Guys
going back to prison?
Please, let's not jump
to conclusions
before we have all the facts.
Thank you. That's all quest--
That's all the questions
for now.
All right, Diane.
It's time to implement
damage control.
I'm gonna tell the press
there's no more questions
- for now, and if they have...
- Hang on, Maureen.
Aunt Linda!
What a pleasant surprise.
Wolf, what were you thinking?
WOLF
Diane, listen.
We hit a little bit of trouble.
Oh. Which part?
Assaulting
the police commissioner
or stealing a priceless belt
in front of thousands of people?
It's-it's not
what it looks like.
Someone's setting us up.
You got to believe me.
Of course I believe you.
Well, you might be
the only one.
Listen, we could really use
your help right now.
Wolf, I can't
call off the cops.
There's too much heat on you.
I know. I know. I know. I know.
If you could just give me
something to work with,
a-a clue, a starting place, something.
All I know is,
it-it's got something to do
with that MacGuffinite thing.
- MacGuffinite? Really?
- Yeah.
It's what the Bandit's
been after the whole time.
I hate to drag you into this,
but it's our only lead.
Can you look into it?
Yeah, I know exactly who to ask.
- You do?
- Listen to me.
I need you to lay low until
I get to the bottom of this.
In the meantime,
don't trust anyone.
- And, Wolf...
- Yeah?
We'll get through this, okay?
I hope so.
Hey. I owe you one.
What are medium friends
for, huh?
Yeah.
Maureen?
- Yes, ma'am?
- Cancel my appointments.
You got it, ma'am.
I've got to catch up
with an old friend.
Good news, gang.
Diane's gonna help us
clear our names.
All we got to do is
lay low and...
You.
You should've taken
the mint, Whiskers.
Hey! Hey.
Hiya, boss.
Yeah, the chickens
are in the broiler.
Repeat, the chickens
What? Where... where are we?
What's happening?
Once upon a time,
there was a big, bad wolf.
Ooh, love that guy.
What a character.
He's the one
who challenges the status quo,
who takes the big chance.
Without him, shoot, I don't
even think we have a story.
And they call him the villain.
Hmm. Kind of backwards,
don't you think?
Do I know you?
They call me
the Phantom Bandit.
Nice ring to it, I guess.
But you can call me Kitty Kat.
I think you met my girls.
- Hello!
- Holy shrimp.
I'm Pigtail.
It was great honor
to kick the butts of my heroes.
The butts were even greater
than my dreams.
She's a huge fan.
Big crime nerd.
Thanks.
I think.
Oh, hey, Susan!
Actually...
Hey!
- It's Doom.
- Uh...
Susan is an alias.
- You lied to me.
- That's all right, papito.
- Played me.
- Not cool, man.
- Betrayed me.
- Hey. Hey, listen.
- It's just business.
- You're...
- Shady.
Shady.
Let it out, buddy.
You're the perfect woman!
She out-snaked a snake!
If that's not true love, well...
well, then I don't know
what true love is.
Snake...
Okay. Kitty, y-you mind telling
us what we're doing here?
Cutting to the chase. I like it.
We're planning something big.
Only problem: It's too big
for the three of us.
You need work.
We need extra hands.
Professionals, you know?
With a specific set of skills.
One last job.
Whatcha say?
What do we say?
No, uh, is the short answer.
But, well, we're flattered.
But, uh, the thing is,
you know...
- We're good now.
- Yeah.
We don't steal stuff anymore.
Yeah, so if you can just,
you know, untie us,
and, uh,
we'll let ourselves out.
And we can just call it
a noche, okay?
You know what?
I love the red ones.
Is it cherry?
Is it strawberry?
I'm not really sure.
I can never tell.
It's kind of like people,
you know?
You think they're one thing,
but it turns out
they're something else entirely.
Diane.
She knows.
Can you imagine if this got out?
The governor's secret past
as the Crimson Paw?
Whew. Talk about a scandal.
She will be
in the hot bubble water.
So...
Let me rephrase the question.
Play along,
and Diane's secret is safe.
Or don't, and you, Diane,
the good life,
it all comes crashing down.
What'll it be?
All right, hot sauce.
What's the job?
That's the job.
Whoa.
Wow.
That's the MoonX rocket.
Seriously?
You better believe it, girl.
Why steal a car when you can
steal a big, jumbo rocket ship?
I think she's serious.
Why would you want
to steal a rocket?
A heist is never
just about the loot.
Isn't that right, Wolf?
- It's a power move.
- Exactly.
You get it.
He gets it.
All right, now, come on.
We got work to do.
And after that,
we're square, right?
You're gonna give us the video?
Thieves' honor.
This is gonna be gnarly.
In the good way.
Come on, y'all.
We're going on a heist.
So, are we bad again, or...?
You got to hand it to them.
They thought of
almost everything.
Almost? Oh, you got an angle.
I've always got an angle.
One last job, and after that,
Little Miss Lollipop's
gonna regret she ever met us.
Madam Governor?
Take me to his cell.
Well, well, well.
Hello, Diane.
Marmalade.
Of all the super maximum prisons
in all the world,
you had to walk into mine.
Oh, my.
You look like a balloon animal.
I know, right?
Today was arm day.
That's why I'm looking
extra swole.
So, to what do I owe the visit?
I wonder if it has
anything to do with
your mangy protégés fleeing
the scene of a crime.
How do you know about that?
It's my job to know.
I'm the editor in chief
of the Crazy Max Chronicle.
I also do yearbook, and I'm
captain of the pickleball team.
To be honest, I'm kind of
crushing it in here.
All right, well, good for you.
But what do you know
about MacGuffinite?
Oh.
MacGuffinium Fictitium.
Fascinating metal.
With one extremely
unique property.
And that is?
Well, I'm not
just gonna tell you, am I?
Did you forget?
I'm sitting in prison
for your crimes.
So what's in it for me?
I am not giving you a pardon.
A pardon?
In the middle
of pickleball season?
No. I have a better idea.
How would you like
to play a game?
What sort of sick game
do you want me to...
Backstabbing governors first.
Oh, goody.
All right, everyone, listen up.
Each of you has
a specific part to play.
Safecracking gear!
Disguises!
Welcome, Ms. Tarantula.
Whoa, that is some serious tech.
Uh, I think
I got the wrong bag.
Yeah, this doesn't seem like
proper attire
to infiltrate a launch site.
Oh, no.
We're not going
to the launch site.
We found a way to circumvent
every level of security
leading to the rocket,
and it's right there
on Mr. Moon's wrist.
Watch controls everything,
from front gate
to mission control
to blastoff.
Steal the watch,
steal the rocket.
Only problem?
He never takes it off.
Lucky we have
world-famous pickpocket.
And we think
there's a window.
"Jeremiah Moon invites you
to his exclusive,
state-of-the-art wedding."
Are you serious?
We're gonna crash the wedding?
Oh, I love weddings!
I mean, you know--
I li--
I mean, I like them.
They're fine. I don't care.
Whatever. No one cares.
Um... here's how it's gonna go.
This is a highly
exclusive event,
and it's got protection
to match.
So, we'll have to get creative.
I'm a little rusty,
but I promise
to play you respectfully.
Mamma mia!
Where's-a my flowers?
Prego! Cappuccino! Extra grande!
Tutti frutti! Limoncello!
Oh, the veil? It's vintage.
A princess wore it.
Yoo-hoo!
Jeremiah! Oh, there you are.
Moon wears a pair of
AR-enhancement glasses
that identify
the people worth talking to.
And the people who aren't.
But-but I'm his aunt!
Those who make the grade earn
a 60-second one-on-one
with Mr. Moon. -Jeremiah.
That's our window.
Our only window.
Once the ceremony begins,
it's over.
All right, everyone. I got eyes.
Piranha, you're a go.
- Hey, Clarence.
- Huh?
Something doesn't look right
in this trunk.
Oh? What is it?
L-L-Let's see here.
Oh, it's there.
It's there. Way in the back.
Uh, I don't see
anything. -Yeah. No, no, no.
I think if you put
your head in there.
Oh, Clarence.
All clear here.
Titanium triple spring release.
I've missed you, my old friend.
You're sure you still got this,
Snakey Cakes?
SNAKE
Please.
Lock picking is like a romance.
You got to start
gentle, playful,
work your way into
its little cold heart,
until all those defenses
melt away.
Oh. Sounds kind of fun.
Are we still talking
about the lock?
Huh?
A power outage?
Hello.
Extremely quick electrician.
Did someone call
for an electrician?
Yes, sir. That was me.
- She's all clear.
- Oops.
Don't worry. I fix and be out
of your lip hair in no time.
KITTY
All right, girls. Have fun.
Name's Webs.
I'll be your hacker today.
Mr. Wolf, that's your cue.
Don't spend
it all in one place, you hear?
That's my job.
Hey. Afternoon. Howdy, ma'am.
Eyes up, cowboy.
Your target's at twelve o'clock.
WOLF
That's our man.
What are you doing? Get in line.
Buck Wolford doesn't do lines.
Webs, how's my cover ID?
Hang tight, Wolfie. Just a
couple more firewalls. -Great.
Relax, Kitty, I got this.
- Wolf?
- Hey, excuse me.
- Mr. Moon, sir.
- Hey.
Come on. Come on. Come on.
- Wolf!
- Bypass and boom!
Careful, careful.
Let's show our wealthy
and influential friend
- a little respect.
- I thank you kindly.
You still got it.
Now this is it.
Swap the watch for the dummy.
Well, at least somebody's
civilized around here.
My name's Buck Wolford.
Big Bad Oil.
But I'm sure you heard of me.
I am just so...
Need a hand?
Last I checked,
you didn't have any.
You never minded before.
Ow!
- Is she okay?
- Whoops.
Oh, boy.
Unless I'm mistaken,
rockets do need oil.
How'd you feel about
a strategic partnership,
Mr. Moon?
You're coming to me
with a business proposal
right before my wedding?
You're a real operator,
Mr. Wolford.
You don't know the half of it.
Who authorized you
to make eye contact?
Oh, no, no, no, no, no.
Mr. Wolford?
- Uh...
- Get the watch!
- Moon!
- Ah!
There's my Soli-wolly.
You're looking extra bald.
And you're looking short.
Wolf.
Have we met before?
Uh, no, no. I guess I just have
one of those faces.
Hey, anyway, Mr. Moon, uh...
Did you take
a pottery class in Sydney?
- Uh...
- Sir, it's time.
Ah, yes. Showtime.
Wait a minute.
Excuse me, Mr.--
Can I just, uh-- Mr. Moon...
No, habibi, listen.
I never forget a face.
I-- Naked high diving!
Was it that?
Oh, hi, yes.
Can I borrow him for
just a moment? -
- No. Okay.
- Thank you kindly.
You blew the heist!
That guy, I-I-I knew him,
and he was, he was gonna
recognize me.
Bellissima. Bellissima?
Uh, we got a slight problem.
Someone needs to tell Marco
that a shark ate him.
Are you guys trying
to sabotage this?
Who's ready to get married?
- Shark!
- I'm a panicker.
This is all too much. You happy?
I like this one.
This whole thing's a bust!
You lost your edge.
And now the governor's
gonna pay for it.
Hey, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Hey, let's not do
anything crazy, okay?
We'll get you the watch.
Oh, yeah?
How?
It's like a freakin' fairy tale.
Honey, you look so beautiful
in this dress.
Hmm.
"Big Bad Wolf"?
Hmm. Hmm.
Shark, you're up.
Welcome!
Welcome to this most
beautifious, majestacular,
incredimonious occasion.
Whoo! Whoo!
Could he be a little more
subtle? -(over comm): Whoo!
- For Shark, this is subtle.
- Whoo!
Give it to me real good.
We stand here today
to marry this man--
this manly, masculine,
manleously maleful man--
and this totally normal woman
- in the sacra-nimonius bonds...
- What? Wait a minute.
...of holy matriminimamony.
Whoo!
Now, would you please
join hands.
Hmm. Uh...
That's him!
Yep. Just-just join those hands.
- Look. Look.
- No need to look at them.
- Come on. Come on. Come on.
- Just blindly join
- those hands together.
- I object!
- What?!
Honey-bunny.
Soliman, who do you think
you are?
Moon, look what
you are marrying!
It's none other than
the Big Bad Wolf!
Here comes the bride.
- Boop.
- How could this be?
- He was here!
- Soli-wolly, this is a disgrace.
- There were claws! I saw claws!
- Get him out of here now!
Where are you taking me?!
There are witnesses!
- We all saw it! You!
- Huh?
- Don't just stand there!
- Hey, where's the officiant?
Ooh, who cares?
Definitely top five
Bad Guys heist ever!
When big man say, "I object,"
I almost make pee-pee accident!
Right.
Almost.
Wolf, I-I got to ask.
How'd you know
that was gonna work?
You see, Kitty, there's
three parts to every con.
First, bait the hook.
Look.
Then comes the turn.
Something weird is going on.
- Someone should object.
- I object!
But none of it works
without the payoff. -What?!
'Cause it's one thing
to steal the watch...
Soliman, who do you
think you are? -
Hold on tight, bellissima.
...and another
to get away with it.
The Big Bad Wolf!
The art of misdirection.
It's not the action,
it's the distraction. Got it.
Yes, ma'am.
Hey!
All right, I see you.
Oh, I love weddings!
All right!
Hmm.
No. Not there.
No. Maybe...
- Oh, so many options.
- Oh, my goodness.
Can we move this along?
Patience, Diane.
This is a game
of subtle strategy
and psychological endurance
mastered only by
the most cunning
and sophisticated minds.
"Ages six and up."
Besides, it's not
every day that the governor
drops by to chat about
quantum ferromagnetism.
Quantu-- Wait, are you saying
MacGuffinite is magnetic?
Not just a magnet.
MacGuffinite is
the atomic inverse of gold.
Exposed to extreme voltage...
It will cause gold electrons
to decouple
and attract
with spectacular force.
It's a gold magnet.
Oh, she's catching on.
Very good.
Why rob a bank when you can
make the gold come to you?
All the crime,
none of the exercise.
- Uh, thanks, Professor.
- Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
You can't go.
We haven't finished our...
What? No! But how?!
It's literally tic-tac-toe.
Send me your yearbook?
You know, it's funny.
You're the second person
to come all the way here
to ask me about MacGuffinite.
What are the odds?
You had a visitor?
I didn't get her name,
but apparently we have
a friend in common.
Or should I say... five?
Madam Governor.
I need footage of Marmalade's
last visitor. Now.
Found ya.
- But can I drive?
- No. -
This was
new best day of my life.
- Why must you leave forever?
- Aw.
- Cheer up, Buttersnout.
- Buttersnout?
- I always wanted a nickname.
- Oh.
Uh, great.
Hey, listen, uh, no hard
feelings about the whole,
you know, pretend relationship
to entrap you
and your buddies, okay?
Oh.
Come on, now. Of course not.
I mean, to be honest,
I-I wasn't, uh,
really that into you.
Oh, weird.
'Cause you, uh,
you seemed pretty into me.
Well, that's...
Yeah?
That-- You know, I didn't
want to hurt your feelings,
so, uh, yeah,
sorry if you're disappointed.
Oh, no, no, no, no, not me.
You see, uh, I'd only be
disappointed if I was into you,
which, uh, as previously
established, I was not, okay?
Of course.
Otherwise,
this marshmallow toast
would be
full of romantic tension.
Hmm.
Yeah. Of course I did.
WOLF
Oh, really?
So impersonating the bride
was your idea?
- Absolutely.
- Yeah. Okay.
I hired you.
Therefore, your ideas
are my ideas.
Classy.
What's going on
with the MacGuffinite?
Oh, just a little
science project.
Ah. So you framed us
for science?
Come on, I had to frame you.
It was the only way
to draw you out of retirement.
Anyway, you got
what you wanted, so, uh...
Oh. Oh!
Right. You want the video.
There we go.
- Ooh.
- Oh, man.
Did... did I ever tell you
about my first heist?
Uh, no.
Um, was it a bank?
Jewelry store?
Lollipop.
Back in school, we had a teacher
who used to give
the good kids a lollipop.
And maybe it was
my claws or my teeth,
but she never, ever
looked my way.
It was hurtful.
So one day, when the old fart
wasn't looking,
I snuck into the drawer
and swiped the whole bag.
After that,
when the kids wanted lollipops,
they came to me.
Dude, it was amazing, man.
For the first time in my life,
I felt powerful.
I must've pulled off
a hundred jobs since then.
And the more you steal,
the more they respect you.
Hmm.
Why would you give that up?
You think if you play nice
and follow their rules,
they'll just see you
for who you truly are.
But let me tell you, they won't.
What if the bad life
was your best life?
My advice:
Stop hoping
and enjoy the lollipop.
- Did you get it?
- Oh, we got it.
Come on, I had to frame you.
It was the only way
to draw you out--
Full confession.
I can't believe
she didn't notice the camera.
All we need to do is get this
to the chief and clear
our names. -All right.
- We did it. We did it.
- Whoo! Yeah!
Woo-hoo! -Touchdown dance!
Hey, buddy.
You okay?
Huh?
Oh. Uh, nothing.
Just, uh,
imagining my next round
of thrilling job interviews.
Wolfie, this is the plan.
Yeah. No, I know.
I'm just saying...
What am I saying?
I'm just saying, wh--
what if we took a wrong turn
with the whole going good thing?
You know what I mean?
Yeah, but it's gonna be
different this time.
"Captured the Phantom Bandit."
That'll look great
on your résumé.
We're gonna be heroes.
Piranha Street.
Yeah, no, yeah. Totally.
What am I talking about?
You're right.
Come on, let's find the chief.
- Let's go.
- That's my Wolf.
Uh-oh.
Did you really think
it was gonna be that easy?
Shoot.
Hey! -Watch it!
Naughty, naughty.
Are these gold?
Kitty, can we talk about this
for a second? Uh...
Nope.
Is that MacGuffinite?
What's going on?
How about I show you?
Ooh, shiny.
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
A gold magnet?
You bet your scaly butt it is.
And this is just a prototype.
Wait till you see
what it can do in zero gravity.
- You're taking it to space?
- Obviously.
What do you think
giant rocket is for?
Is not for science fair.
You can't expect us to steal
all the world's gold
from down here.
The biggest heist in history.
Courtesy of us.
All the world's gold?
Oh. Oh.
And the cherry on top!
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa. What are you doing?
The video?
You don't need to ruin Diane.
Let's-- Let's-- Come on.
- Let's talk about this.
- Hmm, see, thing is,
I promised this rodent
that I would.
Kind of a quid pro quo
type thing.
- Marmalade.
- I know.
What a goofball.
But a real wiz
with the science stuff.
I-I'll tell you what.
'Cause we're friends,
I'm gonna give you a choice.
No, no, no, no, no! Stop it.
You can stop it with this.
What the...
The upload is paired
to the magnet.
The moment you turn it off,
the video goes viral.
Or leave it on, protect Diane,
but y'all keep dangling
until the police arrive.
Oh, such a dilemma.
The police?
LUGGINS
Hello. Commissioner speaking.
Yes, ma'am. I got a hot tip.
The Bad Guys are holed up
in a hangar
two klicks north
of the MoonX launch site.
What? W-Wait. Wh-Who is...
Sorry, doll.
Look, it's nothing personal.
You are so hot right now.
- Snake!
- Yeah?
Come on, man.
You are one twisted reptile.
I wish I could stick around
to see how it ends,
but we've got a rocket to steal.
Ciao.
Kitty. Kitty, wait.
Hold on a second, please.
See? This is why
I'm not a cat person.
How are we supposed to choose?
We're not.
I don't give up that easy.
- Piranha.
- Yeah?
I need you to pull out the USB.
Follow my lead.
You got it, papito.
One, two, three.
♪ Whole crowd ♪
♪ Hold on, Boosie,
wipe me down... ♪
I got it!
And it's going faster.
- Not good.
- New plan. Regroup!
♪ On the corner posted up,
smoking loud ♪
♪ Ay, tell 'em they can't
break me, break me down ♪
♪ Ay, come on, baby,
shut it down ♪
♪ Black king, black rose,
black hoodie ♪
♪ Black ..., black cars,
got my Black chin up ♪
♪ Tell 'em they can never
bring us down ♪
♪ Yeah, jumped off the porch
since a child ♪
♪ Uh ♪
♪ Why they wanna push me... ♪
Webs, you got enough wiggle
in those legs to hack in?
Three legs is all I need.
I think.
All right, let's go.
♪ All black on,
got my ski mask ♪
♪ All black on ♪
♪ Got my ski mask... ♪
Wolf, Wolf, I can't get in.
Fall back! Fall back!
♪ Whew, girl, look at you ♪
♪ Hop up in that coupe,
check the temperature ♪
♪ Hop up in that, hey, hey ♪
♪ Star ..., mosh pit,
they can never stop ... ♪
♪ Got it from the mud,
I ain't have no other option ♪
♪ Watch out for the cops,
here they come ♪
♪ Gotta go ♪
♪ Chain swang, Levi's,
pain behind these eyes ♪
♪ They don't want the...
♪ And I see why... ♪
Now, think, think,
think, think, think, think.
You got this. You got this.
What are we doing?
♪ Now listen... ♪
- The forge!
- The what?
We're gonna throw
the whole thing into the fire.
- It's our last chance.
- You got this, buddy.
Here...
we...
go!
♪ All black on,
got my ski mask ♪
♪ Hundred million ...,
don't they see that? ♪
♪ This not time
for your feedback, ah ♪
♪ All black on,
got my ski mask ♪
♪ All black on ♪
♪ Got my ski mask ♪
♪ Hundred million ...,
don't they see that? ♪
Huh?
Well, well, well.
Not so tough without your
hot dog truck, are you, Wolf?
- Ooh.
- Wow. -Wow.
This is getting real.
Morning, ladies.
Madam Governor.
Oh, yeah. Foxenstein, right?
Close enough.
What are you doing here?
You know, I'm very hands-on.
Especially when someone tries
to frame my friends.
I know everything.
The MacGuffinite. The magnet.
Hmm.
You talked to Marmalade.
Actually, he did
most of the talking.
I'm more of an action girl.
Step aside before anger
becomes punch.
You're all under arrest.
Governor's orders.
Ooh, feisty.
You don't know, do you?
You're not governor anymore.
You might want to check
your phone.
Crimson Paw.
Crimson... What?
No. No, no, no, no, no. But...
How-- H-How?
They never expect the dart.
Shall we?
Kitty!
Kitty.
A viral video has revealed
that the notorious thief
known as the Crimson Paw was
none other than Governor
Diane Foxington! -
While police search
for the rogue politician,
they have wasted no time
in ordering the speedy release
of sweet, adorable
Professor Marmalade,
unlike the Bad Guys,
whose claim to have "changed"
fooled absolutely no one.
Chief, we were set up
by a gang of supercriminals.
They turned the MacGuffinite
into a gold magnet.
- Back in line.
- And they're stealing
that rocket to take it to space.
Yeah, that's what they all say.
Ch-Chief, I know it looks bad,
but if we did this,
why would we help you
solve the case?
Why would we tell you
about the MacGuffinite?
And where's the loot?
You know it doesn't add up.
Look, we don't have proof,
but I know, somewhere in that
big, booming heart of yours,
you know we didn't do this.
Chief, please.
How many times
do I have to tell you, Wolf?
It's "Commissioner."
Ready to fly this thing?
With watch, rocket flies itself.
Hey, Jenny. You seeing this?
Uh...
So much for Piranha Street.
Ow.
Chief?
Okay, let's say,
hypothetically, I believe you--
Which I don't.
But if I did... if I did
and some supercriminal
has a gold magnet,
how would we stop them?
You... you believe us?
No! No, no, no!
No! No!
I want to give her a hug.
Ooh, I like Chief.
Ooh, wow, Chief,
is that a new shampoo?
Okay, okay.
Please stop with the touching.
I don't get you guys.
You're good, then you're bad,
then you're sort of good,
then really bad.
Ugh, it's hard to keep up!
Yep, yep. That's fair.
I get it.
We're all over the place.
But you need to get us to that
rocket before it takes off.
Rocket? What-what are you
talking about?
Initiating backwards counting.
Countdown initiated.
Countdown initiated?
Whoa. What's going on?
- I don't know.
- Well, shut it down, Jenny!
- Shut it down!
- I'm trying, Jim!
Uh, Mr. Moon?
Uh, we've got
a slight situation.
The launch isn't
until next wee--
Well, butter my crumpets.
Five, four...
Evacuate!
...three, two, one.
Woo-hoo!
The twists just keep coming.
The MoonX rocket seems to have
taken off three days early--
Huh?
What the hairbrush?
Yeah!
Uh-oh.
Bring it on!
Whoa!
Holy moly.
Are you sure about this?!
Not particularly. No.
Remember, when you come back,
you're under arrest!
You got it... Commissioner.
Go get 'em, guys.
All right, here we go.
First time
for everything, right?
- Run, run, run! Let's go!
- Come on!
Go! Go! Go!
- Let's go, go, go, go, go!
- Guys, come on!
Move, move, move!
We did it. We did it.
We did it. -PIRANHA: Yeah!
- Woo-hoo!
- We did it!
We didn't do it.
Jump!
Pull us up, Snake!
Vinyasa, baby!
Up there! The cargo bay!
Pull!
Come on! Pull! Pull!
Are you kidding me?!
Lefty-loosey, righty-tighty.
Oh, right.
What is it?
Ah, never mind. Just glitch.
Whoa.
Now, that is a view.
What is happening?!
Sir, they're heading to the
Multinational Space Station.
I think they're docking.
Doom, you're with me.
Pigtail, get the MacGuffinite
in place.
You got it, Kitty.
Yoo-hoo. Anybody home?
Ooh, nice decor.
Very, uh, space-y.
In hindsight,
that was a little reckless.
Did everybody make it?
Hey, wh-where's Piranha?
Whee!
I can fly!
I just needed to believe
in myself. Ha!
Whoa. Whoa, whoa, whoa. Whoa.
Oh, you...
you guys can fly, too?
All right, watch the legs.
Whoa. Guys, check this out.
What is she doing?
They're using
the MoonX Power Cell
to activate the MacGuffinite.
Kind of genius.
Yeah, they're smart,
but there's something
they didn't count on.
I got a plan.
Mm-hmm. Installation complete.
Confirming coordinates.
Shouldn't we, uh, get
some special training for this?
Just don't-don't look down.
Uh, follow-up question:
Which way is down?
Listen up.
This is all about timing.
Webs, Shark, I need you
to hack the external console
while Snake and Piranha pop
the control panel to engage
- the manual override switch.
- You got it.
- And what about Kitty?
- Leave her to me.
We got one shot
to save the world.
Let's make it count.
Okay, buddy. You can do this.
- First, clear the root folder.
- Mm-hmm.
Then in system directory, type
"ENC underscore word equals
word dot encode." -Mm-hmm.
Now "import hashlib."
- Mm-hmm.
- Hit enter.
Then "input underscore path
equals input."
Okay. Cool, cool. Got it.
Okay, so, clear
the root folder, you say.
Okay, come on.
Come on, Piranha.
You're not nervous, right?
'Cause we know what happens
when you're nervous.
Wh-What would I be
nervous about?
Oh. Piranha!
- Dude!
- Sorry.
I can taste it.
We're in position.
I think it's time
we introduced ourselves.
♪ People, people,
dancing on the people... ♪
♪ People, people... ♪
♪ Everybody... ♪
Huh.
♪ Apart from you ♪
♪ Now that we're dancing ♪
♪ People ♪
♪ Dancing people ♪
♪ Dancing people... ♪
Oh. Thank you.
What's going on?
Why am I flying?
Holy potatoes.
It's actually working.
Ooh, yeah!
Oh, boy.
- How we doing, Snake?
- Hang on.
Got it!
Like stealing candy and a baby.
Don't you mean
"candy from a baby"?
I know what I said.
How about the air lock?
All right, Webs.
I like your style.
Oh, that one was all Shark.
I panicked.
But it worked out.
I'm a programmer now.
I'm going in.
- What was that?
- Huh?
Oh, that's not good.
Uh...
Snake, buddy, I'm sorry.
What? No, no, no...
I hate you.
Get to the air lock!
Go, go, go!
Girls, nothing gonna
stop us now.
Snakey Cakes?
Help... me.
Stop farting, you maniac!
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa. Come on.
Turn it off, all right?
You're gonna kill them.
I'm sorry.
Whose side are you on?
Kitty, stop! It's just a heist.
It's never just a heist!
Secure the air lock. Now.
Whatever you say, boss.
"Turn it off."
Ha! I'm just getting started.
It is total mayhem!
A cataclysmic gold storm is
literally destroying the city!
Oh, yeah.
The gold.
Come to mama.
You know,
I've been thinking. -
Wolf?
Doesn't that word sound
kind of made-up?
"Gold."
It's kind of weird, right?
- It's weird.
It's weird-- It's a weird word.
Go ahead. S-Say, say, "Gold."
Gold. Gold. Gold.
Anyway, it doesn't matter.
I'm gonna need you
to turn off the magnet.
Or I'll just do it for you.
Is that supposed to be funny?
Stay with me, papo.
Stay with me!
I-I don't want
to die like this.
Oof.
Okay, okay.
Come on, Piranha, your friend
is spinning out in space.
You should know what to do.
That's it! The pen!
The pen? Wha...
Grab the pen! The pen!
Grab the... -
Oh, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no!
Okay, I can do stuff.
I can do stuff.
Why would you risk your life
to save people who wouldn't even
give you a chance?
At least when you were the Big
Bad Wolf, they respected you.
Oh, that was respect, huh?
That wasn't respect.
That was fear.
Oh, whatever, man.
What's the difference?
Trust me, there's a difference.
Respect is earned.
One day, you'll learn that.
Honestly, Wolf, what made
you think this would work?
Who says it didn't?
Like you said,
it's not about the action.
It's about the distraction.
Hey, genius, the watch controls
the shuttle, not the magnet.
You get it.
She gets it.
Got it!
You sure about this?
Trust me, chico.
Tuna power!
I got it!
Well done, boys.
Webs, tell me you're ready.
Lining it up, Wolfie.
Nice work, kid.
No.
You want to see
a power move, Kitty?
This is a power move.
It's fine.
- -Huh?
- Hello!
- Need a hand?
- I got you, Snakey Cakes.
Oh, Sugar Beak.
And you said
you weren't into me.
Why would you believe
anything I say?
No!
How do you expect to get back
to Earth without a shuttle?!
At least there's an Earth
to go back...
You destroyed my beautiful plan!
What did I tell you about
messing with my friends?
- Wha-- How did you...
- Wolf, we got-- Oh.
We tried to stop her
from posting...
Ah, wow. What happened
to medium friendly?
Well, good thing I'm
not the governor anymore, huh?
Ugh, gross.
- 'Bout time.
- Guys!
Whoa! Diane.
What are you doing here?
Just happened to be
orbiting the Earth.
Thought I'd drop by.
Woo-hoo! -Yeah!
We did it, baby.
I feel the love.
Like, I feel it.
I hear about the famous
Bad Guys all my life.
But now I get it.
Alert.
- It is a massive system failure.
- Alert.
We're falling out of orbit.
I think this is it, Wolfie.
We're doomed!
One last hug, everybody?
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Hang on.
Don't talk like that.
Sure, it's-- it looks--
yeah, it's bad.
Yeah, okay. It's bad.
Sure, we're hurtling
towards Earth in a tin can,
staring squarely
into the face of death.
Sure, our blood may boil,
our bones may liquefy,
but if there's one thing
that I know about this crew,
it's that we never,
ever give up.
Because we have something
that's stronger than fear,
stronger than even gravity.
And that's hope.
Yeah, hope.
That's hope.
We're gonna land this thing...
...or we're gonna die tryi--
What those guys,
those brave, beautiful guys
did up there,
saving the world from
a 24-karat catastrophe.
And despite all the rejection
and suspicion,
all the tiny humiliations,
they did it for us.
They didn't do it
for the fame or for the glory.
They did it for us.
They weren't just good guys.
They were my best friends.
And I would give anything
to arrest them
just one more time.
This one's for you, Wolfie!
I, for one, am outraged that
it took an evil space magnet
for people to realize
that the Bad Guys
were worthy of our love
all along.
But it's too late,
because now they're dead.
Ironically, the only survivors
were the perpetrators
of the heist,
including the supercriminal
known as the Phantom Bandit,
while a second escape pod
was, tragically, empty.
Did I sell it or did I sell it?
Are you gonna tell us
what this is all about?
Yeah, 'cause I don't feel dead.
And who are the suits?
And why are they wearing
sunglasses inside?
Hmm?
I know. I know it seems
elaborate, but trust me,
it's the best way if you want
to do some serious good.
Gentlemen. Ladies.
You have been identified
as ideal candidates
for a brand-new, ultra-elite
unit of secret operatives
that we're calling
the International
Super-Galactic League
of Protectors:
ISGLOP.
- Huh?
- Sounds kind of made-up.
I-I don't understand.
What-What's happening?
We're offering you a job, son.
You're gonna be secret agents!
Huh?
- Is he serious?
- That can't be right.
Secret agents? Get out of here.
- They're serious? Really?
- That's what I'm talking about!
- Woo-hoo! -Nice.
- All right.
Hey. Almost forgot
you were there.
As you might have noticed,
change isn't easy.
Some days, it's gonna feel
downright hopeless.
But with the right attitude
and the right friends,
the good life
has a way of finding you.
Ready to get to work,
Agent Wolf?
Not bad.
Not bad at all.
Woo-hoo!
♪ I feel lucky,
and I feel blessed ♪
♪ The sun is shining,
so take a breath ♪
♪ Of the good life, good life ♪
♪ We heading for the good life ♪
♪ Good li-i-i-ife ♪
♪ Cool breeze blowing away
my cares ♪
♪ 'Cause where we're going,
it's in the air ♪
♪ It's the good life,
good life ♪
♪ We heading for the good life ♪
♪ Good li-i-i-ife ♪
♪ Oh, so good,
just the way it should be ♪
♪ Told you that it could be,
told you that we would be ♪
♪ Heading for some new heights ♪
♪ Heading for the high life ♪
♪ Feels like
we just took flight ♪
♪ We on a joyride ♪
♪ Never doubted
we were born for greatness ♪
♪ A life so animated
that nothing can contain it ♪
♪ Leveled up like we knew
all the levels from the start ♪
♪ I hope you feeling
like a star ♪
♪ We're gonna show
the whole world who we are ♪
♪ All those days
we were searching for ♪
♪ Something meaningful,
something more ♪
♪ Like the good life,
good life ♪
♪ We were longing for
the good life ♪
♪ Good li-i-i-ife ♪
♪ I knew we'd get here, never
doubted, never doubted it ♪
♪ If we are in a dream,
then I ain't coming out of it ♪
♪ Speeding through the clouds ♪
♪ So you better hold on,
grip tight ♪
♪ Ready for the spotlight,
we heading for the good life ♪
♪ I feel lucky ♪
♪ And I feel blessed ♪
♪ The sun is shining ♪
♪ So take a breath of ♪
♪ The good life, good life ♪
♪ We heading for the good life ♪
♪ Good li-i-i-ife ♪
♪ The sun is out, so am I ♪
♪ Let's get our wings
on to fly ♪
♪ I feel the magic around ♪
♪ Nobody stopping us now ♪
♪ With you here by my side ♪
♪ I can feel
where we can glide ♪
♪ So much higher than the sky ♪
♪ Oh, oh ♪
♪ We heading for ♪
♪ The good life, yeah ♪
♪ The good life ♪
♪ Uh-uh ♪
♪ We heading for ♪
♪ The good life ♪
♪ Good life, good life ♪
♪ Get ready for the good life ♪
♪ Good life ♪
♪ We heading for the good life ♪
♪ Uh-uh, we heading
for the good life ♪
♪ It's the good, it's the good ♪
♪ It's the good life ♪
♪ Good life, good life ♪
♪ Get ready for the good life,
good life ♪
♪ We heading for the good life,
♪ Get ready for the good life ♪
♪ Good li-i-i-ife ♪
♪ Good life ♪
♪ Good life, good life... ♪
Ah.
I love it
when a plan comes together.
And now time to go home.
♪ You ain't courageous enough ♪
- ♪ Most of you probably fold ♪
- ♪ Yeah ♪
♪ You ain't willing
to the face the challenge ♪
- ♪ Acquire the gold ♪
- ♪ Yeah ♪
♪ We only here to just retrieve
what you probably stole ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ You see, steel sharpen steel ♪
- ♪ When it's time for the go ♪
- ♪ Yeah ♪
♪ We here to create
such a ruckus ♪
- ♪ We all on a roll ♪
- ♪ Yeah ♪
♪ Stare every challenge
in the eye ♪
♪ We don't play with the soul ♪
♪ No matter what you was told,
every rat find a hole ♪
♪ See, it don't matter
what you thought ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ We taking everything
you want ♪
♪ Whoa, whoa, whoa ♪
♪ Now don't forget it,
better know we come to get it ♪
♪ And we with it
and there's nothing better ♪
♪ I hope you know
to play it smart ♪
♪ See all the greatness
when we come ♪
- ♪ When the story is told ♪
- ♪ Yeah ♪
♪ Can't put a timeline
on greatness ♪
- ♪ It never gets old ♪
- ♪ Yeah ♪
♪ Come get the scope
when we hot and you not ♪
♪ And we pull up
and we come in ♪
♪ Taking everything
you got, ugh ♪
♪ See, it don't matter
what you thought ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ We taking everything
you want ♪
♪ Whoa, whoa, whoa ♪
♪ Now don't forget it, better
know we come to get it ♪
♪ And we with it
and there's nothing better ♪
♪ I hope you know
to play it smart ♪
♪ No matter what you thought,
you better believe ♪
- ♪ We coming ♪
- ♪ Yeah ♪
♪ And if you thought
that we was playing ♪
- ♪ Let me show you something ♪
- ♪ Yeah ♪
♪ So then we jump and we swoop ♪
♪ And we dodge every bullet ♪
♪ It don't matter
when they pull up ♪
♪ And they try to pull it ♪
♪ Pull it ♪
♪ Better know we on the clock ♪
- ♪ And it's time to go ♪
- ♪ Yeah ♪
♪ Everything is tactical ♪
- ♪ Now enjoy the show ♪
- ♪ Yeah ♪
♪ Then we skip and we bounce ♪
♪ And we hop
out of every situation ♪
♪ Best believe
that it's time to blow ♪
♪ See, it don't matter
what you thought ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ We taking everything
you want ♪
♪ Whoa, whoa, whoa ♪
♪ Now don't forget it,
better know we come to get it ♪
♪ And we with it
and there's nothing better ♪
♪ I hope you know
to play it smart ♪
♪ Smart ♪
♪ You know the heat melt ♪
♪ Better wear your seat belt
and strap up ♪
♪ You know we get
a little crazy ♪
♪ Every single time we act up ♪
♪ I know the way you see us
doing it to 'em ♪
♪ I think you really,
really need to shack up ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ It don't matter every single
time they really try ♪
♪ To trap us, and they come
from every corner ♪
♪ And they really try
to catch us, we're completing ♪
♪ Every mission no matter how
they attack us, and the fact ♪
♪ Is that we back and that
we never, never slack up ♪
♪ Better get up out the way
because we come and then ♪
♪ We pack up, and we taking
everything you want ♪
♪ You know you better back up ♪
♪ Let's go. ♪
Well, bye...!