Look up.
Let us see your face.
He's the guy that
killed your brother.
I'll always be grateful
that you covered for me.
Why are you taking the fall?
Song Woo-chul, I sentence you
to eight years in prison.
- Hey, friend!
- Bro!
Good job
toughing it out.
Ta-da!
I decorated it myself.
Have some more.
Isn't it good?
Yeah, it's tasty.
Here, you love cigarettes.
I'm going to quit.
- Are you sure?
- Yeah.
Really?
That's Kang Yoon-jae.
He started working for me
a few years ago.
Say hello.
Director Kang,
greet him properly.
You work for him, too.
It's fine.
Hello.
That's enough.
- Let's go, friend.
- Okay.
Here we go!
Are there only scumbags
in prison nowadays?
Why?
You were released early
for good behavior.
That's ridiculous.
You jokester!
You're a good guy.
There's a lot of work for you.
The gambling house, the bar,
money loaning...
The world is fucking big,
and there's a shit ton to do.
Do you want to
start with a bar?
Do-sik, I'm sorry.
But I want a quiet life.
What?
How will you
earn a living?
Who knows?
Woo-chul...
What was our dream?
Expensive cars,
big salaries, and...
- Sexy girls!
Cheers.
I want to live
as quiet as a mouse.
You bastard.
What will you get
if you live that way?
Nothing at all.
That's the point.
I have everything, except
for a good friend.
If you don't want this life,
why did you hang out
with me back then?
I was just...
- What is it?
- Director Kang called.
Yes, Yoon-jae?
What?
That bastard...
All right.
I need to get going.
Something came up.
Nothing serious, right?
Of course not.
This happens all the time.
You know what to do, right?
Make sure he has
the time of his life.
Yes, sir!
Woo-chul, enjoy your surprise.
I'll see you at
the office tomorrow.
- See you.
- Bye.
- Goodbye, sir!
Where's Do-sik?
- Go on up without me.
- Come with me!
- I'll go get some beer.
- Beer?
It's Room 1004.
The passcode is 1234.
- Room 1004, 1234?
- Yeah.
- That's right.
Yes!
'Woo-chul, she'll whip you
into a good worker.'
'Your friend Do-sik.'
What took you so long?
I was waiting forever.
Miss, I'm not...
Here's your welcome drink.
I'm Bom.
I think I'll just leave...
Sorry, but I already spent
the money I was paid.
My friend just went
to get some...
Hold on...
Let me do my job.
Miss, hold on.
Wait, my friend went to
buy some beers...
It's obvious what happened,
so don't stare.
I'll shower first.
He really went all out.
Is she breathing?
Yes, she is.
- Clean up this mess.
- Yes, boss.
- Did you call Madam Han?
- Yes, I did.
Why aren't you
answering your phone?
Hey!
Why are you screwing over
your man, you bitch?
President Jang, it's you.
It's so hard to
see you nowadays.
Why is my life
so meaningless?
I didn't help you out
to see you like this.
Fuck, why are you messing with
someone else's business?
Don't.
President Jang...
I know we're close friends.
But we promised we wouldn't
swear at each other.
Director Kang...
This situation is
shitty, right?
It's so shitty.
You're fighting the urge to
kill me, aren't you?
You shouldn't glare at
someone like that.
It's because
I don't have money.
That's what I keep telling you,
President Jang!
Don't be greedy.
We need to keep
a low profile.
If we get rid of the
North Korean defectors,
we'll make 10 times more!
How many times do
I have to tell you?
Let's just sell it directly!
Then, I'll be able
to leave Korea.
I'll spend all of my days
just doing drugs.
You want me to get out
of your hair, don't you?
Let's wait for
the right moment.
- Really?
- Of course.
Okay.
Okay, okay.
Just sleep here.
Where are you off to?
I'm going to find Bom.
Sex with her is
just amazing.
Stop that.
I've told you, she's
Madam Han's favorite.
So what?
Don't worry.
I love her, after all.
Watch yourself.
Bastard...
Get the product.
I'm leaving.
No refunds.
Yes, Madam?
Bom, Cho Jeong-gon
is looking for you.
He doesn't know
that I moved.
Don't go home.
Stay there.
Okay.
Can you turn off the lights?
- Do you have insomnia?
- Yeah.
Look up.
Let us see your face.
Take a good look.
He's the guy that
killed your brother.
Song Woo-chul, I sentence you
to eight years in prison.
Go to sleep, baby
Please find me work on a boat that
goes far away for a long time.
I guess you're
desperate for money.
There's a crab fishing boat that
departs three days from now.
I didn't think you'd
actually call me.
Who did that to you?
Did you call the cops?
The cops?
It would be hilarious
if I called the cops.
Do you know what's funny?
I willingly go see
that son of a bitch.
Because...
I quit that stuff.
For the tenth time.
Let's leave.
You won't be able to see flowers
on that crab fishing boat.
Were you a boxer?
Huh?
Yeah, for a while.
How did you know?
I learned it a little.
All boxers get
the same habit.
I'm going this way.
All right.
You want me tonight?
No, I'm just...
Sorry, I'm feeling blue.
It's fine, thanks for
drinking with me.
It was today.
You know,
Kim Ji-hwan...
More, more!
You're doing great!
You can do it!
Circle him.
That's it!
- Time out!
- That's a foul!
What the fuck!
That's foul play!
- That bastard!
- What's the referee doing?
Are you okay?
You're doing great.
He's quick on his feet,
so hit his body...
Shut your mouth.
Is the betting over?
Friend...
- You're the underdog today.
- Is that so?
Your opponent's a big guy.
Bookies from all over
the country are here.
They'll broadcast the match
and take bets until Round 1.
Betting time is almost
over, people!
That's it!
Keep going!
Fuck, this is bullshit!
- Okay!
- Great job!
What's that bastard doing?
We won!
Son of a bitch!
Call an ambulance!
Why would you go there?
His mom's remains
are there, too.
She just couldn't
move on with her life.
She got sick, and
died a few years ago.
Look up.
Let us see your face.
Were you a boxer?
All boxers get
the same habit.
- Come with me, bitch!
- I'm sorry!
Follow me!
Say 'ah'.
Stay just like that.
Here's something for your mouth.
Don't use your teeth.
Woo-chul, don't get into
any trouble for a while.
Bastard!
Who the fuck are you?
You bastard...
If you touch Bom again,
I'll kill you for good.
I'll remember your face,
address and name.
You're fucked, idiot.
Please leave a message
after the beep...
Detective Cho isn't answering.
That fucking druggie...
Hey, I don't see
Cho Jeong-gon.
Why did you bring so many men
for a business deal?
That's why people
call you gangsters.
I won't make a deal
without Cho Jeong-gon.
We're called gangsters
because we are gangsters.
And it's not my fault Cho Jeong-gon
isn't answering his phone.
We're all South Koreans now,
so we should trust each other.
Distrust is what's at
the heart of our profit.
You want to keep
waiting, then?
Do we have a choice?
Store the product.
- Goodbye.
- Get going.
Shit...
Hurry up.
Woo-chul, I'm handling
some business.
An accident?
I'll take care of it.
- What about you?
- Don't worry.
It's either money or life.
I'll handle it myself.
No, you'll end up
in prison again.
Stop frowning, idiot!
Didn't that bitch tell you
that he was a cop?
I went after him
before asking.
She's being foxy.
I'm sorry, Do-sik.
There is one way...
Never mind.
Leave before
I change my mind.
Get going.
What way do you mean?
It's risky, but
it might be worth it.
If we're going after Gak-su,
we need to be prepared.
One wrong move, and
we're screwed.
We'll lose everything.
But with you by my side,
we might have a chance.
He has guts and loyalty.
Isn't he a substitute?
In case things go wrong?
I told you, he's my friend.
Plus, I have plenty of men
that could become substitutes.
You're not loyal to me.
That's the problem.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Han Su-jin.
Detective Cho, you should spend
your remaining years in Thailand.
Get massages and
have sex all day long.
Okay.
I have a work life and
a personal life.
I can forgive him
as a police detective.
But personally...
I'm having some trouble.
Oh, geez...
Don't agitate our boss.
He seems to be
excited about this.
He wants to talk to you.
Let's think positively.
- Did you check out Gak-su?
- He's not up to anything.
Boss, are you sure
about this?
Why?
Are you worried?
Amateurs accept
the hand they're dealt.
But pros build
their own hand.
Perfectly.
That's the stuff!
Here...
It's your turn to drink.
Bottoms up.
There's a problem
with the product?
He's a long-time friend.
He's going to start
working for Madam Han.
Say hello to Director
Song Woo-chul.
Let me pour you a drink.
We should clink our glasses.
Someone from Lab 216
in Pyeong-yang contacted me.
The factory was raided.
What?
They can't restart production
until the end of summer.
Luckily, they sent all of
the finished product.
It's a lot.
About 40kg.
But the government is
cracking down on us.
I can't go get it
right away.
I'll go on May 1st,
since it's a holiday.
We don't have enough money
for that amount of product.
Come on, President Jang!
Why are you
worried about that?
Just buy your usual amount.
What a kidder!
You said your family
name is Song?
Which Song family?
The Yeosan family.
I had a good
feeling about you.
My mother is from
the Yeosan family, too.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Ri Gak-su.
- We're moving to an apartment.
- Good for you.
It's 43ã¡, with four rooms
and two bathrooms!
Stop bragging.
It's a good day, so
let me feel happy.
Whoa, bro...
Do I look okay?
You've still got it.
Why would a man
wear perfume?
We have to work
with ladies.
It's manners.
Want some?
Manners?
I'm Chae-ah.
- Ra-hee.
- I'm Ra-hee.
- Se-yeon.
- I'm Se-yeon.
- Ye-ri.
- I'm Ye-ri.
Ye-ri just turned
20 years old.
Bro, she's just my type.
Never mind.
Finally, there's Bom.
You two have met, right?
If there are any problems,
tell Director Song.
- What about Director Kang?
- You can tell him, too.
Ye-ri, Director Song
can solve anything.
That's why President Jang
asked him to work here.
Let's get ready.
Welcome, sir!
You son of a bitch!
You don't even have money!
Please stop!
Just one more bottle!
Can we go all the way?
How much do
I have to pay?
Stop playing hard to get.
- Come here!
- Where are we going?
Come on.
Do you really love me?
Of course, I do.
Lie down, like me.
The stars are beautiful.
What nonsense.
Don't do drugs when
you're supposed to work.
My mind is cloudy when
I don't do drugs.
When we were young,
we fought all the fucking time.
I guess that's why
I love you now.
What did he say?
It's his chance to get
revenge on you.
Of course he's in.
We'll go after
Cho Jeong-gon, too.
I'm Jang Do-sik.
I shouldn't take orders.
I told him that we'll make
you the victim.
Play along for a while.
People of Korea,
we're fucked.
Gangsters were fighting over
drugs from North Korea.
One of them had a knife, so
Detective Cho shot him dead.
That's not all.
We're even more fucked.
All of the drugs
have disappeared.
The police are trying
to track them down.
The end!
It's perfect, isn't it?
Don't try to act too much.
You know you're
a bad liar, right?
You're too naive.
Get going, then.
You have work to do.
Bye.
You bastard...
I know what you're planning,
you son of a bitch.
The weather's great.
Want to have a drink?
Which one should
I wear today?
This one's prettier.
You bastard!
Fucking moron...
Director Kang!
We love each other!
Stop with your bullshit.
No, wait!
Woo-chul...
Kang, what's going on?
This prick fucked
one of the girls.
No, we're dating.
You son of a bitch...
Brother, that's enough.
I'm asking you to stop.
Fuck, listen carefully.
If we get involved
with the girls...
They start acting like
they own the place.
Then, shit will hit the fan.
Get it?
Director Song?
- We're here.
- Is this the place?
Whoa...
Yang-gi, this place
looks expensive.
Have you got money?
Don't worry!
We'll get to moisten
our throats.
I want to moisten
my dick first!
You sick bastard.
Me, too!
It's about to get rowdy.
Director Song.
Whatever they do,
don't get involved.
Wow, this feels great!
Yang-gi, why are you
taking so long to piss?
Why do you have to
interrupt our fun?
Pretty girl,
we're not done yet!
Hey...
Where are you going?
You have to go
upstairs for sex.
Come here!
You still have your panties on,
so what's the problem?
- I'm shy.
- Is that so?
- Excuse me...
- Get lost, bastard!
What a mean chick.
Let's go have sex, then.
Yeah, it is better
when you're drunk!
You should drink, too!
You got free food in North Korea,
and you want the same here.
What did you say?
You fucking defectors are
living off of our taxes.
- Bom, stop!
- I'm telling the truth.
You fucking bitch!
What did you just say
with your dirty mouth?
You fucking...
You want a war with us?
Director Kang...
Director Kang!
Damn it...
I'm so sorry.
There must be
a misunderstanding.
Director Song,
let go of him.
Song Woo-chul,
you son of a bitch.
Stop acting like you're married
and let go of him.
- Are you okay?
- I'll kill him!
Son of a bitch!
You bastard...
You...
Just leave me alone.
Leave me alone.
Leave me alone,
you son of a bitch!
- Gil-tae!
- I just drank alcohol.
I didn't have sex.
I really didn't have sex!
Mr. Policeman!
Why didn't you call me
first, you bitch?
A customer called the police.
Fuck...
- Detective Kim, I'll handle this.
- Yes, sir.
Let's have a chat.
Follow me, you bastard.
Are you ruining our
business on purpose?
Fuck, just stay away.
You fucking
son of a bitch...
Fuck, let me look at you.
Stay still, you bastard.
You're young.
Who the hell are you?
Who sent you?
You killed my brother,
you son of a bitch!
If he presses charges,
it counts as attempted murder.
I'll just go to prison.
Even a murderer
only gets 7 years.
You brat...
We got Ms. Choi's statement.
Is she allowed to leave?
Yes, see her off.
Make sure she's safe.
Myung-joo?
It's you, right?
That bastard ruined
both of our lives.
It was a boxing accident.
An accident?
You of all people
shouldn't say that.
My brother fought with my mom
right before he died.
He asked for $5,000 because
he wanted to get you a place to live.
Before my mom died, she regretted
not giving him that money.
So, apologize.
Apologize for calling it
a fucking accident!
I'm sorry.
By the way...
Do you have some money?
There's someone
I feel guilt toward.
I don't know how long
I should feel this way.
It's because he died.
Could you go
buy me a beer?
Sure.
Get some snacks, too.
- Nothing else?
- No, thanks.
Look underneath.
Use it when you
take a shit.
It's a gift.
You want me to stop
bothering you, right?
Then, Ms. Choi Myung-joo...
You'll need to work with me.
This phone is the latest model,
so I checked it out.
Is that so?
I don't know much
about that stuff.
The picture quality
is great, too.
One, two, three!
He embarrassed me.
I can't stay still.
I understand.
But please think of
my situation.
If I embarrassed him,
would you do nothing?
I shouldn't have said that.
Please forgive me, boss.
We need Woo-chul
for this plan.
After I beat everyone
and sell off the product,
I'll leave this small
town for Seoul.
Don't look so shocked.
I'm bringing you with me.
Look at that happy face.
Let's go to Seoul.
Hyun-tae.
Park Hyun-tae?
Where did he go?
Bro, mind your manners!
Hello, Director!
You're dating one
of the girls, too.
It's not like that.
What are you thinking?
I want to sell drugs, too.
- What?
- Bro...
Ye-ri owes Madam Han $70K.
Please persuade Do-sik
to let me be part of it.
He does whatever you ask.
Dog meat is great
for your health.
We'll be healthy for
the whole year.
Did the smell of meat
bring you here?
Hurry up...
Why did you bring him?
Get lost!
Let him stay.
Director Song must think
he's trustworthy.
He's not looking so good.
I'm sorry.
I'm still getting
used to the job.
They wanted to kill you,
but I managed to stop them.
I'm in your debt, Mr. Ri.
I know you'll repay it.
Did you hear my offer?
I'll buy all of the product
at 150% the price.
Tell me the exact date.
I need time to prepare the cash.
Hey, aren't you going to
do business with me?
Excuse me!
Comrade Ri Gak-su!
I'm listening, so
stop shouting.
Geez...
Do you know what the first thing
I learned in the Special Forces was?
How would I know that?
Observation.
Reading every detail to
understand the situation.
That's the key to survival.
Do you like her?
It's not like that.
I did everything I could
to bring my wife here.
But she died of
lung disease.
If I'd known sooner...
Fuck, I'm talking
my mouth off.
You're old friends
with President Jang?
He's trustworthy and loyal.
Woo-chul...
Values can change
depending on the situation.
Are you interested in
working with me?
You seemed to have
a fun chat with Gak-su.
It was nothing.
Is it a secret?
He suggested
working with him.
Just drive, you bastard.
Do-sik, you should start
trusting Hyun-tae.
We go way back.
I guess Ri Gak-su has
taken a liking to you.
That's why I'm
telling you everything.
This is a good thing.
Maybe you can
fool Gak-su.
Let's use him to
handle Detective Cho.
We should get rid of that
bastard for good.
This is a good thing.
Maybe you can
fool Gak-su.
Let's use him to
handle Detective Cho...
Fuck...
They all want to
screw me over.
You've wasted your life,
Cho Jeong-gon.
Gak-su, we have
a hitch in our plan.
I told you.
He's become a sly fox.
We need Detective Cho
to round up Gak-su's gang.
They have more men
below the surface.
Detective Cho
needs to raid them...
That's why I'm racking
my brain, idiot.
So, if Song Woo-chul
approaches you...
Be careful.
It's going to be tricky.
Why?
Are you scared of
his punches?
No.
He knows when to fight
and when to stand down.
I need to be careful with
someone like him around.
Let's just kill him, then.
That would be a waste.
What the fuck do you
want me to do, then?
Shit, our entire plan might fail.
Hold on.
I'll take care of it.
I just remembered something.
You son of a bitch.
You don't even flinch a bit.
Fuck, I came all the way here.
Act surprised.
Let's go for a drive.
Kim Ji-hwan was
the favorite.
But Do-sik bet a lot of
money on you.
You'll win, for sure!
Do-sik did everything to settle
with the victim's family.
He wanted his body to be
cremated right away.
Then, who's the killer?
Song Woo-chul,
who punched him?
Are you okay?
Or Jang Do-sik,
who drugged him?
I know everything.
Let's stop discussing it.
What the fuck?
You knew?
You went to prison for him?
For 7 years?
Then, you must
know this as well.
Ms. Choi Myung-joo
knows who you are.
I won't ask why
you need it.
Thank you, Madam.
You can't do drugs.
That's not it.
Then, why do you
need so much money?
People always need money.
Sometimes, people
even die for $5,000.
Wow, that was fast.
No wonder lots of
women work at bars.
Sang-hwan, you
should go to school...
I'm off, then.
Let's keep in touch.
Myung-joo...
It's Bom, Director Song.
Call me Bom.
Why is everyone
spying on me?
I came because
I was worried!
Give me your phone.
Give it to me!
I'm going to
delete my picture!
Why?
Are you worried you won't
get your fair share?
We should talk it over before
we move on with the plan.
Woo-chul, you're
acting like a stranger.
One more thing.
What happens...
If our plan fails?
Don't jinx it.
What's going on with you?
Should I go to prison
for you again?
You're being
super weird today.
Back then, you
volunteered to go.
That's why I'm so thankful.
Woo-chul,
to be frank...
If it weren't for you and Detective Cho,
I wouldn't be doing this.
Is that so?
Then...
Maybe we should reconsider.
And teach this dick
some manners.
Son of a bitch.
What are you waiting for?
Strip down.
Hurry up, bitch.
I'm busy.
Why did Woo-chul
fall for you?
Damn it...
Oh, are you good at fucking?
Come here, then.
Suck my dick.
- That's enough.
- I'm serious.
Suck my dick.
Bom, put your
clothes on and leave.
You bitch.
You fucking bitch.
Are you disrespecting me, too?
Fine, Han Su-jin.
You strip down.
Shall I, sir?
Come here.
Fucking bitch...
Stay right there, bitch.
Come over here.
Step away,
and I'll kill you.
Learn from your boss,
you stupid bitch.
Harder, baby.
Do me harder.
More.
Jang Do-sik.
Shit...
Is that all you've got?
Let's see what those
bastards are planning...
What the fuck?
That bitch ruined
my plan again.
Fuck!
Get in here.
Get off of me!
- You brat...
- What's going on?
He lost his money gambling,
so he pulled out a knife.
You can't hit me just
because you're the police!
If it weren't for me, the thugs
would have killed you.
- Let me go!
- Wait, Detective Kim.
Yes, sir?
I'll handle this.
Yes, sir.
You trust Woo-chul, right?
Don't you?
Yes...
- I trust him.
- Good answer.
I trust him, too.
So, you have nothing to lose.
He would never betray us.
Right?
Don't just nod your head,
you rude bastard.
Yes, sir.
Check what's going on
and report to me, okay?
Yes, sir.
Hyun-tae, come here.
Come closer, idiot.
Hyun-tae, I'm not
like Woo-chul.
You know that, right?
Bitch, have you forgotten
what my brother did for you?
He treated you well!
He treated you so well,
you fucking bitch!
Shit, what has
this world come to?
She's dating the guy
that killed your brother!
It's all Choi Myung-joo's fault!
Die, you fucking bitch!
It's okay.
I'll make everything okay.
That bastard doesn't
even get seasick.
Don't look at me
so hatefully.
We need Cho Jeong-gon for
everything to go smoothly.
You must be prepared to kill
in order to save someone.
That's why being
a human being is so hard.
Yang-gi, turn the boat around!
Just act natural.
As if nothing happened.
Go to work, as usual.
Do you understand?
If anything happens, call me.
Don't go.
Please.
Myung-joo, everything
will be fine.
It's okay.
I'm fine.
So, don't go.
This is the safest place
to have a secret chat.
It's good for threatening
someone, as well.
Get to the point.
Well...
I've been thinking.
Who will do their
absolute best for me?
Ri Gak-su?
No way.
Jang Do-sik?
He can fuck off.
You.
It's you, you bastard.
They have multiple options.
But you only have one.
Choi Myung-joo,
the murder suspect.
You're responsible for it, too.
So? So what?
Do you want to
fight me, head on?
You're desperate.
I'm not.
The night of May 2nd.
I don't care who
lives or dies.
I just want the money.
Get me the money.
Then, you and Bom can
do whatever you want.
Okay?
Good luck, buddy.
Come on.
Fuck...
After this is over,
soften your edges.
Otherwise, Bom
won't love you.
Oh, right.
The night before, Choi Myung-joo
will be brought to the station.
You fucking idiot.
I told you.
This is the safest
place in the world.
But it might become hell.
Get up here.
Let's have a match.
Fuck it...
You're not wearing
a mouth guard.
Are you going easy on me?
That really hurts my ego.
Don't go easy on me,
you bastard!
Fuck...
Hey.
I don't owe you
anything anymore.
What went wrong
between us?
Woo-chul...
Are we still friends?
Are we not?
Answer me.
Are we friends or not?
Hey!
I'll start thinking of this
as business, then.
The world keeps spinning.
We all have jobs to do.
Right?
Director Song Woo-chul?
You trust me, right?
Better the devil you know.
We know each
other's goals.
Let's talk business,
and make it win-win.
Hmm...
There we go.
What do you think, buddy?
You don't care who
you work with, right?
We don't trust each other,
so let's make a detailed plan.
Detective Cho.
Director Song.
Think you can fool Gak-su?
I'll give you the locations, ledgers
and bonds of Do-sik's gang.
The moment they get the drugs,
Do-sik's men will attack you.
If you attack them first...
They'll all go down
in a single night.
In return, you want
a safe boat trip for two?
With some cash?
What do I get,
besides money?
I'll make sure she's safe,
then return to you.
Are you sure about this?
Don't worry.
All right, it's a deal.
Get everyone ready
before the boat arrives.
Stay quiet, okay?
Yes, boss.
Detective Cho.
Get the police on the scene
at the right moment.
Catch all of them, okay?
As soon as I get my money.
Who came up with this plan?
I don't think it was you.
Just find out where
Ri Gak-su docks his boat.
Just get me the money.
Cho Jeong-gon will
get the money.
I'll get the drugs.
You'll get to leave
with the girl.
In return, you want
a safe boat trip for two?
Fuck, how reasonable!
You have to come.
Promise.
I promise.
If I'm not there by 4,
leave without me.
Even if you get a call from
my number, don't answer.
I'm sorry, Hyun-tae.
You shouldn't be
involved in all this.
I'll see you later.
Good luck.
'The Wild'
Song Woo-chul.
3 against 1 is
easy for you.
Don't lose focus.
Otherwise, you won't get
to see your girlfriend.
It doesn't take much for
friends to become foes.
Fuck...
Let's see...
Sawasdee krap.
Kop khun krap.
Fuck...
Where's your girlfriend?
Hurry up, Woo-chul.
Shit, that must hurt.
Damn...
Song Woo-chul, you're
still a hell of a fighter.
You got the text, right?
That place must be
familiar to you.
Good job.
Woo-chul...
Goodbye.
Is everyone there?
- Yes, boss.
- And the other matter?
It's all set.
Let's go.
Open it.
You skilled son of a bitch.
Hey, hey...
Fine, fine.
I'll handle it.
Yes, sir?
Detective Kim.
Let Choi Myung-joo go.
She's innocent.
Yes, sir...
I was tipped off
about something.
Shit.
Buddy...
You want to kill me?
Should I do it myself?
Damn it, I was
aiming for your dick.
Fucking bastard.
Hey...
I really want to kill you.
But you let me
quit being a detective,
so maybe
I should let you live.
No, I should kill you.
You son of a bitch.
Do you want to live?
I'll die, then.
Do you want to die or live?
Look at me.
Come on, fucker.
Detective Cho isn't
answering his phone.
- Are the police on their way?
- Yes, they are.
Okay, okay...
Woo-chul is giving me
a big farewell gift.
We have to go, right?
Let's wait just
a little bit more.
- Thanks, Hyun-tae.
- Don't mention it.
Woo-chul must be
a really good person.
He has a loyal
friend like you.
Yeah.
He's great.
Damn it...
Check everywhere.
Are you okay?
Hyun-tae, thanks for waiting.
Where's Myung-joo?
I dropped her off
somewhere safe.
Where's the money
and the drugs?
We should hurry.
Myung-joo is
waiting for you.
Hey, President Jang!
What's that bastard
doing here?
Going somewhere?
When will you bring
your wife from the North?
This knife kept me safe
even before I left my hometown.
Take it.
Is Jang Do-sik gone?
Yes, he is.
I have to do
all kinds of shit.
I was afraid I might
kill Song Woo-chul.
I'm so sorry.
He took Ye-ri.
Jang Do-sik might
kill her for real.
I need to save her.
I'm all she has.
Shit...
You should have gotten on
the fishing boat and left!
What the fuck!
You're out of your mind.
Stupid bastard.
A dog never
abandons his owner.
It's always the owner
who abandons his dog.
What happened to Woo-chul?
Huh?
You're right.
I should have
listened to you.
I'm sorry.
Just...
Don't kill Myung-joo.
She's got nothing
to do with me.
Let her live.
Please.
Promise me that.
Thanks.
Hyun-tae, you're
a good person.
I know I can trust you.
You trust me, right?
You're dating one
of the girls, too.
Ta-da!
I decorated it myself.
I'm sorry...
It's okay.
Go to sleep, baby
Please don't crow, roosters
Please don't bark, doggies
What happened to Hyun-tae?
I got the money
and the drugs.
People who go
crazy over money
are doomed to live
a short life.
Has everything been
taken care of?
Not yet, boss.
Bastard...
Look into my eyes.
Don't pretend you're sorry.
You've learned
a lot, Yoon-jae.
Not letting others predict your move.
But fuck...
This really hurts my feelings,
you son of a bitch.
Ready?
Let's get to work.
Yes, Madam!
Shall we talk business?
This is for Woo-chul.
Go to sleep, baby
Please don't crow, roosters
Please don't bark, doggies
Baby, you're home.