khmermov.top
Official KhmerMov site:
what happened
Why doesn't even the TV signal?
What's going on, damn it
Is it debt collection?
Damn
What's wrong with my hand
Hello, this is the 112 alarm center. Is there anything wrong?
Hello
Hello, can't you hear me?
(Dahren Employment Agency)
It is currently believed that the suspect broke into Kim Jong Kyun’s home along the gas pipe
[The residence of the victim, Kim Jong-kyun] The security chain at the entrance and exit on the 5th floor and the balcony windows are not damaged. It is inferred that it is a planned invasion, and then fight
[the suspect’s expected invasion route]-extract the suspect's fingerprints-have been nearby Monitoring and parking vehicle driving recorder data
(under analysis)
What about the tools of the crime and the cause of death?
(Seoul Regional Police Agency, wide-area search team)
Has it all been found out?
That
[The home of the victim Kim Jong-kyun] [The victim Kim Jong-kyun has blisters-died]
According to the victim's autopsy result
A large number of paralytic shellfish toxins also known as PSP
Paralytic Shellfish Toxin
Yes
(Producing neurotoxins, magnify the cells with a microscope)
This is the most powerful toxin among paralytic shellfish toxins
The ingredients are said to be the same as tetrodotoxin
So... what about the real murderer?
The real culprit is the dead body three months ago
Dead body three months ago
The dead body killed people three months ago
Group leader
Seems to happen again
Weird case
Subtitle production: LLY
(only shared in apk, HD.Club intensive research)
Libel Law: Here it is
Hello, friends of "Current Affairs Showdown"
Guests invited today
It's a new book that wants to be hotly discussed
Author of "Disgust and Conjuration"
"Disgust and Incantation"
is also the co-representative of the independent news channel "Urban Detective"
I should call you representative Lin Jinxi
Or Lin Zhenxi writer
Which one do you think is better?
Call me reporter Lin Jinxi at will.
My job is a reporter after all
Okay, reporter Lin Zhenxi
(Current affairs showdown, live broadcast)
I was gossiped before that you were deceived by superstition
Want to describe the truth through this book
I can guess that I wrote a lot of exciting content
Come on, this so-called slander law
It’s said to mean the curse of alchemy, right?
Yes, this slander method is an alchemy to curse the other party...
What reporter Lin said
Check out the message board here
The audience is also very interested in it
Right?
Hmph... I really want to talk and stop.
D: It was cursed because of disgust.
H: I had expectations for the Lin Zhenxi reporter. I didn't expect to choose this path... I was very depressed.
R: I hate the times, hahaha, it seems that I have a lot of time?
K: This is a current affairs show, is it a bit conceptual, okay?
T: When a reporter writes a book, he will appear on the current affairs show. Is this mutual help?
R: Confused by superstition The reporter is still on the radio show now, almost crazy
Reporter Lin
Has the previously missing master slander contacted you?
No, not yet
It’s a pity that there are no strong witnesses
Can prove if what you said is true
It's really a pity
I hope that the master slander who heard this show can call
Then let's answer the call from the enthusiastic audience
Oh, already...
Ok hello
Hello
-Hello
-hello
Please tell everyone where you live and what is your name
Forget that, Reporter Lin
There was a weird case of dead body murder last night
(Dead body murder?!)
As long as you check with the police, you can understand what I'm saying is true
That... this listener
Keep me quiet, I'm talking to reporter Lin Zhenxi
This listener
The host here is me
Cut off
-Don't use these irrelevant topics...
-Wait a minute
Hello, please speak
I am the real culprit in this case
Two o'clock tomorrow afternoon
I want to conduct an interview with you live
(Dead body murder!?, interview at 2 o'clock)
-The address has just been sent
-cut off
I hope more people will watch this interview
(Tomorrow 2 o'clock in the afternoon, Mountain House Hotel, 6th floor banquet hall)
goodbye
That... this listener
G: The corpse killed? /H: Collusion, collusion
A: No matter how the book can’t be sold, it’s too...
J: The writers are too direct to participate in the show. Who are you?
S: Yes . Let’s go for the interview? I didn’t have much coverage, I’m happy now.
G: Change to a radio show that can be seen~
K: Absolutely. Please broadcast the interview.
We will come back after listening to the ad below
Hello
How is this going?
Is this a hidden camera
I'll call you later
What about representatives?
Senior, it’s not that important now
Don’t mention a lot of media calls
Asked if what was said in the show just now was true
Top in search list
I’m all asking if I’m doing this to sell books
But we are not that kind of people, are we
-Where is the representative?-It's
on the second floor
Please wait
Hello, come here
She is a new intern this time
Responsible for on-site shooting, say hello
Hello my name is Jesse Zheng
Hi, nice to meet you
Then please
I want to be brave and just like you...
I see, I respect seniors too
Go, go
Why are you still carrying that bag?
This greeting is a bit long
Then please
Seniors, come on
Have you found an intern?
Well, her name is Jesse
Have you seen it
The salary talk goes well and there is no experience
I heard she is an overseas Chinese
Have you inquired about the case mentioned on the radio just now?
Well, the relevant information is placed there
(The death case of Kim Jong-kyun from paralytic shellfish toxin)
Where is the victim?
The name of the victim is Kim Jong Kyun, 46 years old
Direct cause of death: The method is unknown, the victim’s drug reaction was tested, and the paralytic shellfish toxin component was tested.
Indirect cause of death: traces of fighting between the suspect and the victim
Used to be a researcher at Shengri Pharmaceutical
Divorced four years ago
-Shengri Pharmaceutical
-The cause of death was poison and bite marks
Look at the picture of the murderer behind
(Picture 4. I can’t confirm my identity because I’m a bone)
But the autopsy result of this guy showed
He has been dead for three months
What?
As the guy said
Dead body homicide
What about the identity of the murderer?
(Photo 8. Top of the suspect)
The police haven't found out his identity yet
Let me check that
(Photo 10. Suspect's palm tattoo)
Very special tattoo
Did you use that kind of sticker?
Is not
Oh, is it so
It should be a kind of tattoo that casts a spell
I'll call Professor Zhuo
I have handed it over to Professor Zhuo for identification
Hello
-Give me, give me
-husband, husband
Give this to me
How did you come?
Is today our wedding anniversary?
Whoops, I'm really kidding, ma'am.
Leader Zheng
Do I congratulate you on being transferred to the wide area search team?
How nice after going there
The couple can often work together
Have been transferred for a year
Wow, how can we find out so clearly the case information that hasn't been made public yet?
By the way, has this really not been made public yet?
Is it you again?
sorry
Anyway why are you here
Don't do the interview tomorrow
What are you talking about
Why, are you so uncomfortable with your wife’s career going well?
Chengjun, your wife finally started a company
I found an exclusive content for the first time, but you still said that
Hello, look at these books, look
To increase the number of subscribers and then sell these
-The monthly rent of the office has also increased... -This is
not a normal case
Maybe you will be in danger again
I also know this is not an ordinary case
But if the caller is really the murderer
Can he prove the killing technique?
What was the motive for the murder?
What motives are you talking about
It is said that the evidence is insufficient and the prosecutors can’t prosecute it.
If you want me to say, even if you want to catch it, you have to listen to him before catching it.
-Yeah
-Of course it must be like this
Okay, got it
Then listen to what that guy is saying
But our police will stand by around the interview venue
do you know
Got it
Go away
Give you
- This is for you
- Jin Hee understand?
No need, no need
Got it, got it
I listen to your instructions, don't worry
Whoops
-Don't you worry at all?
-Yeah
I'm not worried
Because my husband makes me feel at ease
Walk slowly
What about these books
-Put it on the first floor and go again
-Kim representative
The identity of the murdered corpse
You have to find out as soon as possible
Reporter Lin
This is what my junior found out from other magazines
You first look at the content sent by the other party
This is a scene of doing things in a haunted house in Shikoku, Japan
Look at the wizard inside
(The mysterious girl who appeared with the wizard)
Zhao Na
Yeah, it seems to be her, Zhao Nao
According to the younger generation, he disappeared after working with the Japanese wizard there temporarily.
Really
As long as you can find Zhao Yu, people can believe your words
Our books can also be sold smoothly
Can I call your sister?
-I am slandering the Master
-slandering the Master
That guy is a demon
This is a battle with evil spirits
As long as there is the picture of the evil ghost and the name in Chinese characters
You can use the slander law if you have used it
The fire of the fire word, the joy of joy
Let's use slander
Go to death
I still feel guilty about using the slander law to deal with that kind of guy
Sure enough, sister is a good person
Sister, I will always contain this evil spirit
Zhao Na
Don't
Go to death
(Tuesday, October 17)
Jinhee, just in case something is wrong
Be sure to end this show, you have to remember
(Urban Detective Independent News Channel)
(Later, the independent urban detective's live broadcast will start)
Senior, will he really show up?
Now the number of people online has exceeded 20,000
If this messes up, all the previous ads will also be cancelled
Rest assured
Will definitely come
Don't worry, it will come, it will come, it will come
Don't be nervous
Take your hand out of your pocket
Team leader, one person is in now
Fisherman hat, wearing a gray down jacket
I wore black pants underneath
Looks like a man in his forties
Come on, focus on me all from now on
Yes, got it
Confirm
(For passengers only)
Walking towards the interview venue
Should be the suspect
Jinxi, there is a person passing by you now
(Banquet Hall Lily)
Um... Are you the one who asked for an interview today?
(Urban detective)
Okay, please come to the front
Hello, I'm Lin Zhenxi
correct
Put a microphone on for you
Why is it so slow, really
Let me come
Very sorry
It's ok
(Urban Detective Independent News Channel)
(Later, the independent urban detective's live broadcast will start)
I’m Lin Jinxi from Urban Detective Independent News Channel
Today we are going to use live broadcast to interview
Claiming to be the real culprit in the corpse homicide two days ago
May I ask your name?
My name is Park Yongho
Hello, Park Yongho
Is this real name?
Do you want to read your ID number?
770303 10222150
Park Yongho
No criminal records
(Name Park Yongho, Yongin, Gyeonggi-do)
Someone reported that he was missing
I'm the spellcaster who manipulates the corpse
The case that happened the day before yesterday
It's also the murder case where I manipulated the corpse
Manipulate corpses to kill
This part is hard to believe
Will believe it soon
what
All right
We can talk about that part slowly
Can you talk first
Why voluntarily asked for an interview
I want to warn everyone
I will commit three more murders later
The first is
Two days later, two o'clock in the afternoon the day after tomorrow
I'm going to kill director Kim Min Seok of Seungri Pharmaceutical
Two more days later at two o'clock in the afternoon
I'm going to kill Lee Sangren, Seungri Pharmaceutical's chief executive
I'm going to kill Seungri Pharmaceutical's chairman Bian Seungri
The way to stop the killing is simple
I ask Chairman Bian Shengil to face reporter Lin Jinxi alone
Just make a very sincere apology
Other methods of apologizing are useless
Chairman Bian Seung-il must apologize
After reporter Lin judges whether the apology is sincere
Let's broadcast the show to the world
and also…
Interview is over
I want to leave here
Sudden situation, hurry to save
Put down the knife, Park Yongho
Park Yongho
Please put down the knife
These are all a process
Hello
Hello what are you doing
-To continue the live broadcast
-Hey, hey, hey
Eighty thousand...
It's best to stop now, Park Yongho
Park Yongho
If i get hurt
Interview with Chairman Byun Seungil
Who will do it
walk the stair
Stop
Hurry up and stop, Park Yongho
Where, where
there
Hey, hey, take a picture quickly
Put the knife down
Hurry up and stop, Park Yongho
You are surrounded, put the knife down
Put the knife down
narrow down
Fenced up
Park Yongho
Why did you contact me
You should find the reason by yourself
Jin Hee
(Katsuri Pharmaceutical)
I want Chairman Bian Seung-il to apologize
if not
Kim Min Suk
Li Shangren
Bian Shengri, I will kill them all
Put down the knife, put down
Put the knife down
Hurry up and put the knife down
Um... the president received the report of this incident, right?
Everyone knows that the chairman is recuperating in the villa because of high blood sugar
This matter is not yet clear
No need to report to him
What else to say about the incident, Executive Bian
As the madman said
If the president doesn’t apologize, it’s me
Mr. Lee Sangren, tell me
You are behind me
Calm down, Director Kim
Our company is now in cooperation with the American SF company
A sensitive period involving the success of the one trillion won contract
You should know the best
Executive Bian
That madman Park Yongho
He used to be a researcher at our institute...
You shut up, Director Kim
Shareholders are worried about whether it is unlucky
Calling one after another early in the morning
We have decided to remove that video from the Internet
Sure enough, Executive Bian did everything neatly and neatly
But you are still a director
Just because of the threat of a madman
Offer to apologize to the chairman
Do you have no guilt for the president?
what?
I have been assisting the chairman for almost 30 years
How long did you say when you came to the company
Feeling guilty to the chairman
Don't talk about it
Got it
Yes
The police are paying attention to this case
In addition, the company will also send guards to Director Kim
Come on, that's all for today's meeting
Ok
Director Kim is really...
It's okay, go take a rest
Executive Bian Meiying
Inauguration Ceremony of Shengri Pharmaceutical
I just said, I feel familiar
The female leader who changed the world
The next president of Katsuhichi Pharmaceutical, right?
Is there that kind of nonsense?
Mr. Lee is still here
Have you watched the show videos?
The late Park Yongho claimed to be an employee of your company
(Lee Shangren, Specialist)
Yes, he is the leader of our company’s new drug R&amp;D team
I learned later
He suddenly disappeared without doing the project handover
Leave the company in a short-term chaos
(Bian Meiying)
Park Yongho’s family reported that he was missing two months ago
That he didn't go home the next day after he was on the night shift
Can you confirm the monitoring of the day?
How to put it, that's a bit difficult
The research institute is in the old building of our company, which is now abandoned
Don't talk about that first
I'm curious what the police think about this case now
Manipulate the corpse
It's simply outrageous
Right?
Really outrageous
But Director Bian, what makes me really curious is
Why did Park Yongho use this method?
Let Shengri Pharmaceutical make a public apology
-I don't know
-We will also ask the inspection team to conduct internal investigations
I am also worried about my father
There are also Mr. Lee and Director Kim here
To me, they are all uncles
Inauguration Ceremony of
Kyungsungri Pharmaceutical Co., Ltd. Wish, September 19.9 (Tuesday) SL Kyungsungri Pharmaceutical
Anyway, I found out after investigating
A corpse manipulated by a spell corpse
Call it "here"
By the way, I didn't talk about the two of you
I am now a full professor
Here
is Zhuo Zhengxun
, full professor of Folklore Department of Sansong University
Congratulations, let's get started
Good
bring it on
Look at Xizhai Conghua
Here it refers to a corpse resurrected from the dead
It is said that there is wisdom in speaking like a human
There was a man named Han Jongyu in Goryeo, he used it as a joke
The black hand...
In other words, imitate this corpse whose hands and feet have turned black and come back to life
"Here, here" I sang the soul-suppressing song like this
That's right, Park Yongho is the same
-The first murderer's hand...-
Black
So put it together like this
It is certain that it is the corpse manipulated by the corpse of the spell
Does it mean someone treats the corpse, no?
Is this the case here?
Yes, I checked
There is only one country that uses this kind of tattoo
Indonesia
How can you be so sure?
(First Revenge)
This is Indonesian text
Sorry
I have analyzed
On the body that was killed for the first time
Written first revenge
On the body of Park Yongho you interviewed yesterday
Write attention
Who would do such a thing
Witch doctor
In Indonesia, there exists such a spellcaster who uses black magic and is called a witch doctor.
Not long ago
There is a politician in Indonesia
Hot topic Indonesia pays to curse 800 million rufiyah
, a professional witch doctor , and instigates the killing of mayoral candidates
To curse competing candidates
The witch doctor Santer was found during the campaign, so it became a hot topic
Have also been reported
Come, wait a moment
Sant the Witch Doctor
There are many ways for witch doctors to manipulate corpses
The first is in the soil where the corpse died
Mixed with the blood of the witch doctor who casts the spell into mud
Build clay figurines
Then cast a curse here
Park Yongho's face also collapsed like mud
Yes
Then if the caster wants the power to control the corpse
You have to dedicate what you cherish to the ghost
Place offerings here
In the surrounding guard zone
Place the adulterer who wants to manipulate the corpse
Clay figurines with hair or fingernails
Finally write down what you want to indicate
In this way, it will...
Equivalent to a contract
That's right
It’s a contract with instructions from the person who cast the spell
If the witch doctor really does this kind of thing
Tomorrow may use others to kill people here
Yes
The identity of the corpse who killed Kim Jong Kyun has been found
Is it? who is it
His name is Huang Zhenguo
My family reported missing five years ago
Huang Zhenguo’s
family reported missing five years ago.
Suspected of being a vagrant,
he joined the fake passbook organization two years ago.
About two years ago, I provided my personal information to the imposter bankbook organization
I checked this organization mainly sells the personal information of the homeless
The head of the organization is currently operating illegal casinos
Is serving a sentence
Then you go back to me after you meet the wanderers soliciting guests
Okay, got it, I’ve worked hard
Ok
Who
Jessie
What are you doing alone?
Considering the shooting tomorrow, I’m looking at the equipment
All right
-By the way, you did a great job yesterday
-what
Yu Can said
You finished shooting after you chased Park Yongho
thanks
But is the name of that slanderous master Zhao Nai?
what?
right
It seems you have read my book
Senior Woo Chan said
You must find a slanderer to avenge you
Books can sell well
Not exactly
How is that
This one
Because for Zhao Nai, I am equivalent to her family
I want to tell her even in the book
She can come back anytime
Jesse, who are you in your family?
Two dads and brother
But dad doesn’t care about us
Obviously incompetent, but self-thinking
Even when my mother died, she was not by her side
Reporter Lin, sorry
You should be very busy, but I just said something useless
Where
Are we teammates now?
Let's talk in detail after the case is over
Ok
Go back soon
Our representative Huang turned out to be operating a private casino
Was sentenced to four years in prison
But it’s too long, right?
Who do you say you are?
Although I am a detective now
But before that, I worked as a detective for 20 years
All my juniors are department heads and group leaders
As long as you answer my question well
I can also reduce your sentence
If you don't like it, then forget it
What do you want to know?
Do you know about the Shengil Pharmaceutical case?
You must have heard of the big reports on TV
But the perpetrator of the first homicide
It's actually a corpse that has been dead for three months
And when the corpse was still alive
I'm a wanderer who sold you personal information
So, what's wrong?
What did Shengri Pharmaceutical let you do?
Once in a national media
In the interview, the time to predict the killing was approaching
Here and now, Shengri Pharmaceutical Headquarters looks tense
Police Special Attack Corps
The police regarded the announced killing as a terrorist attack
Therefore, the police special forces of the two teams are arranged inside and outside of Katsuhichi Pharmaceutical
just in case
Turn off the camera for a while before recording
senior
is it going well?
I miss you
If seniors have good news, share them together
I don't know anything
Whoops, you should understand that even if you start your own business, you shouldn’t antagonize our mainstream media.
In the past, we could not do anything because of our competitors
We and Zhongzhen Daily are competitors
senior
The person you interviewed last time
Do you really don't know each other in private?
Give me a message
Where did so many flies come from
Ouch
They used to talk behind your back that you are a fake reporter
Now it's another friendship
Forget it, this is the way this circle is, and it’s not a day or two.
- is not it
- and
Nothing special for now, right?
Yes
But so many people gather and the police are ready
Do you say something will happen?
Wait and see
Where's Jesse?
I told her to buy coffee
It takes a long time to ask her to do something
Anyway, not clever at all, damn it
You were not clever at all before
Senior, why did you mention the previous thing again?
Be nice to her, she is serious in doing things
Yes
Chief, why are you here?
Come and have a look before going to the meeting
Because we want to appease our seniors
Have some coffee
Our police will protect everyone
Don't worry too much
Yes thanks
Chief, you have also seen that monster
Looks exactly like ordinary people
The police have a way to stop it
It's okay, isn't the special attack team coming too?
Just
I told the special forces, don’t worry
About six months ago
Shengri Pharmaceutical wants to conduct new research and development drug trials
Secretly recruited people for clinical trials
That's a lucrative job
Say you can divide my 30% of the agency fee
But there may be something shameful
Tell me to recruit only vagrants who have no relatives
But there are not enough homeless people who meet the requirements
So, I used illegal stayers to make up the rest
Illegal stayer
Stop, the idlers and others can't come near here
Sir, I said you can’t go near here
Occurrence situation
I'm about to grab it, leg
Come on
Attacked by unarmed personnel
What did you say?
Go back door support
Go to the back door right away
Second Squadron heads to the back door
I don't know what the test is
All those people died within a few months
How many people did you introduce?
that
How many people are coming
Please go back and not go any further
Please don't take pictures
Everyone can't do this
One
Two
Three
Four
Five
Six
Seven
Eight
Nine
Ten
Ten people?
Is not
Ten people in each group, a total of ten groups
A hundred people
(Katsuri Pharmaceutical)
Uyan
Yes senior
Whoa, who are those?
-What's the situation
-Snapshot
Take defensive measures
Fast, fast
Reporter Zhang
They broke through the defensive line, the defensive line
They are monsters
Kill them, kill them
Well, they are ordinary people who are unarmed
What are you doing, shooting them to death?
We have already positioned it, group leader
Please advise
Do you want to shoot, group leader?
Hit them in the leg
Team leader, they can still get up again after being shot
They rushed up the stairs
Block the stairs, block the stairs
We have to transfer before they come up
Min Seok, hurry up, hurry up
Turn off the light source and lead the way
Go to the underground garage
Yes, understand
shot
Turn left there and go straight
Go forward there, then turn left and you will see the backup elevator
Ok, now start the elevator
You have to leave as soon as possible
-Woo Chan, follow me.
-What?
Senior, where are you going
Chengjun, how are you?
Jin Hee
Jinxi, hide
Go
Sit firmly
Senior, wait, wait, wait
Section Chief
Go to the police station
Hello
What's up
What are you doing, what are you doing
Stop for me, that's my car
My children and wife are studying abroad now
I miss the kids
senior
Now the number of hits has reached 170,000, 170,000
It’s them, taking those taxis
Yes
Turn left
Over there
Brake, brake, brake
Continue to shoot
Ok
Help
Don't don't
No
Help
Naritoshi
Wake up
Chengjun, don't
ambulance
Hello, you...
sorry
Where did you just go?
How not to answer the phone?
Really worrying
Where are you going, you have to tell me before you go
Do you know what happened there just now?
(Access control area)
Forget it, what can you understand
A paralytic shellfish toxin called PSP that comes into contact with the skin
Now it spreads quickly to the whole body
The strange thing is that all patients are acute
So far, no treatment has worked
Although we are also panicked
But we will do our best
Why stand there, sit here
This wine is a free vaccine we provide
Wine from the Prime Minister of South Africa
President
Director Kim is dead
I know
I also saw the news
Director of the Institute, Kim Jong-kyun
And the cause of Min Seok's death
Okay, okay
It's okay, just tell me
Brother, the cause of death of two people
I heard that the death was caused by PSP
This must be related to this clinical trial
That was done because of need
Please apologize
Who do you apologize to?
Who else
Of course it’s for people participating in clinical trials
Are dead, let me apologize to the dead body
No, do you really want to apologize?
Hey, if it's my personal business, I will apologize
But I’m the general manager of a company
This is a company business, Shangren
Big brother
I will discuss it with my home
What did you say?
Do you want to discuss with your daughter about apologizing?
Shangren, our time is over
Now it’s time to nominate someone to lead the company
I'm leaving now, chairman
Shangren
Uncle, why are you leaving so soon?
You see how thin your face is, it really makes me sad
Yeah, why did you follow Director Kim?
It's raining hard outside, take this umbrella
You are leading the clinical trial, right?
What do you mean
Didn't Dad already get your autographs?
Until now, we have been making medicine to save people
But didn't you force the clinical trial for the money?
Don't you have any responsibility?
Uncle
I'm all for the company
A person who has dedicated his life for the company
Then you should always try your best
This is not your dad and my dream
We do our best...
Really
Why do you have a dream in my company?
What did you say?
Say that kind of cowardly words
Murderers look down on us
Anyway, I know how to make excuses when I'm old
That is to say, you will be the one who will lead us to Katsuhichi Pharmaceutical from now on, right?
Good
Uncle
I will work out a plan with the strategy team
Really
The reason why the attack on Katsuhichi Pharmaceutical is unnatural here
It might be because you manipulated too many corpses at once
And the pattern of the spell
The one on the wrist
I saw that after the shot was shot at that location
Someone can't move
So say witch doctors and those who are here
Is it connected by that tattoo?
Professor, the leader of Zheng
What do you think?
Didn't the hospital also say that there is no way to save him?
Not because of poison, but because of being cursed
What about the solution?
It must be lifted by the person who casts the curse himself
Otherwise...
Or kill the cursed person
correct
Anyway, thank you. If you have any questions, I will contact your professor.
Anytime, it’s hard work
Ok let's sort it out
Shengri Pharmaceutical recruited one hundred homeless people to participate in clinical trials
Because nothing will be a problem in the future
However, there are not so many qualified Wanderers
So even those who have stayed illegally used it
So are there any people from Indonesia?
Yeah
In short, all clinical trial participants died due to side effects
And the one who manages those hundred corpses
This is the Park Yongho interviewed by reporter Lin
At the time of the interview, wasn't it a corpse that had been dead for two months?
The Xuan Zhemin I saw told me this
All died just like that
Then it seems that a month or so has passed
A man from Southeast Asia came to our office
Southeast Asia?
Said that my family is doing part-time jobs in this company
I wrote myself a letter that can make a lot of money
Lost contact afterwards
Who is that person's family?
I don't know
Is the one who was in charge of the show
Park Yongho
Yes, Park Yongho, I told him his contact information
Tell him because I don’t understand well, so I went to that person
Do you remember what that person looks like?
Dressed like a Taoist priest
A bit weird anyway
Witch doctor
Later, Park Yongho disappeared
However, a hundred corpses also disappeared
So the witch doctor killed Park Yongho
Let him become one here
Then manipulate that guy
Transport the body to somewhere
Then I made a hundred more here, right?
No, there is no way to know the identity of the witch doctor
Want to find out the identity of this witch doctor?
We need a list of test personnel
Only then can we know who his family members are
How to steal the list from Katsuhichi Pharmaceutical?
Prepare the camera, we are going to interview
Now? What kind of interview?
(Urban detective, we will become the mouths of powerless people)
This time the project is from the US SFD side
From the proposal of the development and production of shellfish toxins
Starting from the raw materials of chemical weapons
So we recruited homeless and illegal stayers and conducted clinical trials
I don't think there will be any problems in the law
Not that there will be no problems, but that they will not cause problems
Because they are poor, because they are weak
It seems like that
The person the murderer wanted to kill
They are all people who finally agreed to the clinical trial and stamped it
Among the people participating in this clinical trial
Person in charge: Kim Jong-kyun Director: Kim Min-seok
Executive Director: Lee Sang-in Representative Director: Byun Seung-il
Are there Indonesians too?
I am not sure about the specific content
But in the information I brought
Participants’ volunteers and related documents
Please confirm
The interview you are doing now will also serve as evidence for the police
Specialist, you knew it from the beginning, right
This clinical trial is illegal
Clinical trials may have side effects at any time
And at the sacrifice of a few people
Will save many people
What is this clinical trial?
With a few sacrifices, make medicine that can kill hundreds of thousands of people
Is it this way
I already apologized to you just now
Yes, I will be responsible in my own way
What about President Bian Seung-il?
Is he going to apologize?
Are we President Bian?
That person he will never apologize
He is that kind of person
Because of your company, innocent people died
To protect you like that
Many policemen were injured today and are slowly dying
I heard that your husband is in the hospital
Really sorry
Although there is a list of test personnel
But the information is not credible
Can I know who the witch doctor’s family is through this?
Go to the illegal detention management station, you should compare them one by one
No, where is he?
Although I don't know where
But I should be with you here
Where the cursed corpse died...
…Mix your own blood to create clay figurines
The soil where the body died
Where the body died
Soil
Professor Zhuo said that the method of manufacturing here is
The soil where they died
Mix with the blood of the caster to make a clay figurine
Yes, that's what it said
Isn’t that the place where the clinical trial personnel died?
That institute is
It used to be temporarily built in the Shengri Pharmaceutical Building
Could it be that it is here?
Shengri Pharmaceutical Ninth Street, yes, this is the address
There may be witch doctors there
I will go there to see
OK, then I’ll go find out who his family is
Sister-in-law, let me go with you
I also sent the address to Professor Zhuo
Representative, are you going to the Illegal Stay Management Office?
Yeah
Long Xiu, let's go with the representative
Ok
hurry up
all these are…
Seems to be coming soon
right here
parking
Are you alright?
what is this?
Sister-in-law, wait for Professor Zhuo to come here and ask him again
Let's go up first
Sister-in-law
Here
Run fast
Are you alright?
I'm fine
Go here
Zhao Na
Sister, let's leave soon
Officer Liu
Sister
Come here soon
You go first
Officer Liu
Officer Liu, hurry up, hurry up
Come here
Can't go now
The right wrist is their weakness
Sister
Well come, Zhao Nai
Well come
I've been to the places that can stop the evil spirits from me
Stay in Japan for about a year and a half
And then went to a Chinese temple
Although I didn’t find a way to stop the evil spirits
But I learned a lot to use my own body
Alchemy with evil spirits
Try to stay there like that
Intend to avoid people's lives
But when connected to my sister’s dream
Obviously feel what happened to you
Zhao Na
Never go anywhere else
Definitely don't go
That, sister-in-law
Mr. Lee Sang-in, he committed suicide
What?
Yes i am
Ok yes
If you want to die, you will die in your own home
Dad, it's me
Uyan
Senpai, I just contacted Shengri Pharmaceutical
Chairman Bian Seung Il wants to do an interview with an apology
Exclusive to you
What did you say?
Director Lee Sang-in has also become like this
He thinks it's his turn now, so he wants to apologize?
Yucan, you are ready to interview now
Go to Shengri Pharmaceutical and wait for me
I'll go there right away
Ok
Just wait for Professor Zhuo to come and end the investigation here
Ok i got it
Zhao Na, let's go
Sister, I want to stay here and investigate
I think that witch doctor is here
Zhao Na
Sister
If you want to get rid of Uncle's curse quickly
You have to catch a witch doctor
Okay, got it
But never do dangerous things
Be careful
If you look so stupidly
Can you confirm your identity exactly?
What should our team leader Zheng do?
Long Xiu, do you know what my motto is?
God will...
God will bless the righteous
That's it
I'm tired of listening, and I've memorized it all
Is there a righteous person like Team Leader Zheng in this world?
God will bless
Yes
Please come inside
It's here
Are you the reporter
Thanks to the murderer this time
I’ve already promoted the company, so I’m very happy, right?
Okay, let's start the interview now
excuse me
I wanted to come early
But I ate kamabo sticks at the rest stop so I was late
This is a very rare opportunity as a researcher
I didn't expect to encounter such a powerful witch doctor
So nervous, he must be here, right?
Yes yes, got it
You take a look here first
This is not an ordinary tattoo
And amulets that exorcise ghosts or blessings
totally different
Is an invisible symbol
Stealth
Same as i did just now
If cursed, it will make people feel like there is nothing
(does not exist)
Yeah, it doesn't exist
So, in tidak ada
If you erase this tidak
But now you can’t just wipe it off
That will become the meaning of existence
Dear citizens, I am only thinking about the health of the people
For the past thirty years, as a representative of Shengri Pharmaceutical
However, recently due to unpleasant incidents
Let the people worry
Apologize for this
Dear citizens, I am only thinking about the health of the people. I have worked
as a representative of Katsuhichi Pharmaceutical for the past thirty years.
However, the recent unpleasant incidents
have caused the people to worry about it. We apologize for
that. Taking this as an opportunity, we will strive to become a more responsible company.
Thank you
, Bian Seung-il, Representative Director of Shengri Pharmaceutical
We will take this as an opportunity
Strive to become a more responsible company
thank you all
President
The murderer didn't ask you to apologize to the people
No, who should I apologize to
I have to apologize to the victim
Shengri Pharmaceutical Passes Illegal Clinical Trials and Causes 100 Deaths
And also hide this event
You are going to the dead victim
And apologize to their family
Well, I’m not sure about that
But you make me apologize
I should apologize
sorry
I apologize to the victims of the clinical trial
It was my fault
Everyone who died and became the souls
I sincerely apologize to you
thanks
That's it
No way
I won't broadcast such an insincere apology
Why do you judge like that
You just need to edit it and upload it to the Internet
President
Unless you really apologize
Otherwise this curse won't end
Can't you hear me?
curse
You're a junk reporter who got fired for talking crazy, right?
Really
Stop here
What?
Your dad will eventually die from the curse
Everyone withdraw
Meiying
I apologize
I will apologize
Senior, what is this
This seems to be a warehouse for corpses
Hello, everyone is on the ground carefully
symbol
(Date of change of residence place 2019.11.15)
That guy accepted reporter Lin’s interview because...
Don't
Reporter Lin
Does the person's apology now seem sincere?
My daughter wants to support her family
Did everything
Because of my useless curse ability
She did everything
But what about you
Can't say a decent apology
Jessie, don't
senior
Take care of the chairman
President
It's here
Get the equipment, hurry up
Got it
Zhao Na
Come on, Zhao Nao
Stop her
Fast
Here, hurry up
Please go in
I will block this monster
Isn't this the place where the accident happened?
Hurry up, dad
Scary
What are you doing in a daze, solve her quickly
Yes
sorry
Forgive me
sorry Sorry
Please, please, please
Please, please
Zhao Nao, Zhao Nao
Dad, are you okay
Where did you go and how did you show up?
Executive Li Shangren handed all the evidence to the police
Only the relevant person died
The company can survive
Dad, it took you a lot of hardships to get to this point
Your generation can take the responsibility to leave
To usher in a new world
Dad, thank you for your long-term care
You...
Dad, you can offload your important tasks now...
Have a good rest
Are you OK?
Dad, dad, please
Daddy
Please calm down and sit here
Reporter Ren, are you okay?
Daddy
Stop pretending
Bian Meiying Specialist
The mastermind of this case confessed himself
And the evidence
It's all recorded here
Do you think that kind of thing can be evidence?
That kind of thing can be forged
Do you think I will fall because of this kind of thing?
What did you do to your father
And let him leave with his sins
Is this telling him to die? Wait, wait...
Many comments
It seems that the live broadcast went out
You dare to treat me like this
Please come with us
let me go
In this way, have you helped justice again?
Our duty ends here
Zhao Na
Let's go
Don't blame yourself too much
Professor Zhuo once said
The witch doctor seems to want to be a sacrifice
I know
I'm afraid that witch doctor...
The final revenge is not Chairman Bian
But himself
When I touched him...
He called me
Don’t be like him, just clinging to the devil in your heart
Leading to the loss of those you love in the end
Behind
(3 months later)
Bian Meiying, the next president of Shengri Pharmaceutical
Acquitted on the grounds of insufficient evidence
News came out
So what?
Hurry up and hand over my car keys
Can't really apologize to the victims
Accept the sanctions of the law?
Really
What if I say no?
What can you do with me?
Items
Photo
and also
Chinese name
We don't want to make a bad decision
Law of slander: here it is
(there will be later, don’t leave)
Subtitle production: LLY
(only shared in apk, HD.Club intensive research)
Why... so few
Damn
Hey, you do less work and talk crazy all day long
Pull away
How can this be
Go, go
No, why are you doing this to me
Ask a fart, get out
Hey, don't come again
Worker name: Qian Zhoufeng
-I'll kill you again
-let me go
These damn guys
Master Taoist