No! No! No!
Yes.
No.
No, no.
Please.
No, I can't die again.
I can't. I can't do it.
Please, not again. I can't.
No. No, no.
No. No. No, please!
No!
It looks like rain.
Hey. So, what's the plan
when we get there?
Like, we gonna do some sort
of ritual or something?
I'm not prepared
for any rituals.
Not your "woo-woo"
kind of ritual.
More like a closing ceremony
thing, you know?
This is the last stop
of our tour,
and even though we've learned
absolutely nothing new,
we should probably
mark the occasion.
Like a celebration
of our failure kind of thing?
-Yeah. Sure. Whatever.
-Right.
I'm not really sure
what we were expecting anyways.
Closure. Isn't that usually
what people are after
in these kinds of situations?
We're not getting closure.
She's missing. Not dead.
No. Yeah, of course.
I was just asking.
Wait, wait, wait. Clover,
please don't delete. Just...
Just watch.
Look, I know I could've
handled our goodbye differently.
I could've handled everything
after Mom's death differently.
I just couldn't stay
in that house any longer.
But it's not too late
for you to join me.
I know it's not an easy decision
but, please, call me back.
I miss you.
Kinda eerie being here
a year later.
Max!
What?
He's right though.
It is. It's eerie
and it's kinda sad.
Sorry, Clover.
I think we should join hands.
-No.
-Jesus Christ, Megan.
We've done it literally
everywhere else.
It'd feel kind of incomplete
if we didn't do it here.
Clover knows I've got
special shit going on, so--
Special shit going on?
Your biggest psychic achievement
was when you "sensed"
that your dad
was having an affair
with Max's mom
before anybody else.
-I was right.
-Remember that one, Clover?
I mean, we all sensed it when
we heard them in the garage.
Gross. And that's still my mom.
But, actually,
can we try, please?
She probably disappeared
not long after that video
was recorded
and that's a pretty big deal.
And we all feel it.
So maybe we'll tap into
some of her residual energy.
Yeah, it's fine.
Let's do the hand thing.
Okay, okay, great. Great. Okay.
-Okay.
-All right.
It's fine.
Now, everyone.
Close your eyes.
And try to tune everything out.
You have to think of it
like an old radio or TV.
So sometimes you catch a signal,
but most of the time
it's just static.
Keep trying.
Slow your breathing down.
In.
And out.
-Oh, my God!
-Watch out!
Get out of the road!
Slow down!
-Jesus Christ.
-What the hell?
Okay.
Let's try again, okay? So...
Clover?
-Clover! Hey!
-Hey, Max.
Just stop. Just give her
some space for a second, okay?
Don't forget why she dumped you
in the first place.
She didn't dump me.
I broke up with her.
Because she wanted space,
which you wouldn't give her.
Since when have you
been the expert on space?
Excuse me?
What is that supposed to mean?
Ever since kindergarten,
you've always needed
to be in a relationship.
-She does? Do you?
-No, I do not.
Six months ago,
there was a guy just like you.
And three months before that,
there was a girl just like you.
-Julia.
-Julia?
How long have you guys
been together for?
-Three months.
Hopefully she waits to break up
with you till we get back.
-Max.
-Well, if she doesn't,
do you guys
still have Julia's number?
Fuck off.
Hey.
Just that.
Two dollars.
Thank you.
Excuse me, I saw you
and your friends out there.
What was that?
Like a prayer circle?
Yeah, something like that.
-'Kay. Thank you.
-Yeah. You bet.
Sorry, were you
working here last year?
Last year
and the year before that
and the year before that,
and on and on and on.
You know,
each year is the same...
but different.
Totally.
Well, then
can I ask you something?
Does she look
familiar to you at all?
Pretty.
She looks a lot like you.
She's gone missing, huh?
I didn't say that.
Well, you're not
the first one who come here
asking me if I seen someone.
Do a lot of people
go missing around here?
Here? No.
But up the ways a bit
in Glore Valley.
That's where people
get in trouble.
Glore Valley?
Yeah.
Stop.
-You're so grumpy today.
-Hey.
Can I say something real quick
before Clover comes back
out here?
-Yeah.
-You guys told me this trip
was like
a get-out-of-town kind of thing.
You know, I didn't realise
we were gonna be
retracing her sister's
final journey.
So I just have to say,
-as a psych major...
-As a psych major...
Yes. Thank you.
As a psych major, I don't know
if this is the best thing
for Clover.
I think the intentions
were great.
Exactly. And this could be
what she needs to move on.
Or this could trigger her to...
you know, again.
Then why did you come if
you thought it was a bad idea?
Just to spend more time
with Clover?
Because the way we get through
fucked-up shit
is by sticking together.
You know?
So let's not blame each other
for where we're at
right now, okay?
I mean, if we're gonna
blame anybody,
then it should be Melanie.
Their mom had just died
weeks before.
She shouldn't have left Clover
when she did.
That was
the selfish choice here.
Guys.
I think I know
where Mel went missing.
-Hey. It's okay.
-This is crazy.
The car is the safest place
to be during a storm.
Don't say shit like that, Max.
It's true.
Everyone knows that it's--
Max! Don't say shit like that.
Can we just turn around?
I don't understand
what I did wrong.
Because you're gonna jinx us.
Somebody says
something like that,
and then, wham,
Abe runs into something,
then we're all fucking dead.
So don't say shit like that.
Can we just turn around, please?
Not again. I've turned around
two times already.
So turn around again.
We're just gonna
keep turning around.
We're never gonna get anywhere.
Just stop the car.
We can't see out of the window.
I can't even fucking
hear myself think.
What the hell?
Holy shit.
What is going on?
I think I'm gonna be sick.
Yeah.
Megan?
Are you guys seeing this?
It's all around us.
There's a name for this kind
of weather anomaly.
-Really?
-Yeah.
What is it?
I don't know. I don't remember.
It's cool, though.
Cool, weird, whatever it is,
we should probably just
get back in the car
and keep going home.
No way, dude.
I'm not driving through that
fucking storm again.
We gotta wait it out.
Or we could
just find another way.
Fuck.
Is anyone getting a signal?
I am.
A bad one.
Great.
Oh, you know what? Waterwall.
What?
I think it's called, like,
yeah, a waterwall.
That sounds made-up as hell.
No, that's what
the song is from.
What?
Maybe there's someone inside
that could tell us where we are.
-We can start making a plan.
-Yeah.
-All right.
-Good idea.
It's crazy.
Hello?
Hello? Anyone here?
Damn.
Feels like we're
the first people here in years.
Yeah. Where is everyone?
Fun.
Clover?
Mel?
Clover!
Max?
Holy shit.
Clover.
Are you okay?
I thought I saw someone.
Okay, let's go inside. Okay?
Oh, shit.
"Oh, shit" what?
Look.
Oh, shit!
Guys.
You should see this.
There's no details on hers
or any of the others.
Like no date of birth,
no height and weight,
no last seen location,
not even a phone number to
contact if you have information.
So, what's the point, then?
I found something too.
"Glore Valley." This is it.
This is where Mel went missing.
That was her
I heard in the rain.
Wait, what? Look--
I'm so confused right now.
I heard someone call my name,
and it sounded like Mel.
But I didn't wanna
let myself believe that.
And then I come in here
and I see this.
Yeah, but, Clover,
it's weird, right?
I'm telling you it's her. Look.
Holy shit.
Yeah, I know.
Wait, did one of you guys
turn this over?
Max?
No. What does that
have to do with anything?
Because it wasn't
turned over before.
Wait.
Do you guys hear that?
Yeah.
Where's my car?
Shit.
Is that my fucking car?
Back inside.
Back inside. Go.
Is he just gonna sit there?
Better question,
are we just gonna sit here?
Well, what else can we do?
Can we do a phone check again?
Nothing's been working
since we got here, though.
There has to be a phone
around here somewhere.
You wanna look for one,
go ahead.
Not taking my eyes off this guy.
Shit.
Why are there
windows underground?
You guys, there's a phone.
There's a dial tone.
It's okay. It's just somebody
fucking with us probably.
-It's gonna be fine.
-Yeah.
It's not working.
Unless...
Unless what?
Unless this is what happened to
Melanie before she went missing.
Hello? Can anyone hear me?
Hello?
Guys.
I'm gonna just check it out,
and I'll be right back.
Okay?
Okay.
Hello?
Is anyone there?
Abe?
Is that Nina?
What the fuck?
-I'm gonna go check it out.
-Okay.
Go, go, go, go! Hide!
Go, go, go, go, go!
Please.
Mel!
Holy shit!
How am I still alive right now?
You were killed.
I saw it.
I died.
He got you too?
Wait. What about the others?
Let's go.
Are you guys okay?
-What just happened?
-We don't know.
Megan. Hey.
Wait, where's Abe?
-Abe?
-I'm back here.
I'm pretty sure
we're fucked, guys.
Holy shit.
It has a hold of us now.
What do you mean, "it"?
I'm not sure.
I just know that I can feel it,
stronger than before--
We need to get
the fuck out of here
while we still have the chance.
No! No!
He could still be out there.
We didn't see anyone out there.
And the Jeep is back now.
Perfect. Let's take it.
We need to go. Right now.
I don't think we can.
You don't know that.
None of us know anything.
Well, I know that
you were fucking murdered
about ten minutes ago.
And I know that
because I saw it!
I saw it right before
I was fucking murdered!
And now I'm here again,
and my name is in that fucking
book again just like Mel's,
but who knows
what the fuck happened to her.
So the night
is just starting over again?
Like in whatever the fuck
that movie's called?
Like, that shit's actually real?
There's been a bunch of movies
about that, but like--
I don't remember
that happening last time.
So it's not like those movies.
Good to know.
That didn't either.
Oh, fuck!
-Abe?
-Oh, shit!
Fuck.
Hey. Hey. Megan. Hey. You okay?
Tonight feels different.
What do you mean?
Worse.
Fuck.
Okay, okay. Well...
Just so you know...
you know the whole psychic thing
and you getting a signal
or whatever?
Totally believe you now.
Meg. Megan! Megan!
Megan!
-Hey, Meg. Hey.
-Megan!
What the fuck is happening?!
Megan?
-Megan?
-Where did Megan go?
Megan?
What the fuck?! Where is she?
Where the fuck did she go?
Listen.
Meg?
Is someone there? Hello?
Help! Please! Help me! Help!
Who's there?
This town was right to be
damned. We're all sinners here.
Make it stop. I just wanna die.
Please. Please just let me die.
Where's my mom?
Mommy?
And then all of a sudden
she started to attack me,
but it wasn't her.
Nobody is coming for us.
They're just gonna watch us die
over and over again.
Has anyone seen Tommy?
My hair. My bones. Please.
It's what it's doing to us.
Can it just be over?
What we're becoming.
I can't remember my own name.
Please just kill me.
I just want it to end.
Don't let it in!
Wait! I wouldn't touch her.
Don't touch her!
-Why?!
-Because whatever just
possessed her
might possess you next.
That's not how possession works.
People can't get possessed
by contact.
You have to be, like,
weak of faith or something.
Oh, I have faith.
I have a lot of faith.
Do you think it's still here,
whatever got her,
whatever did this?
I don't know.
She said something was coming.
Come on.
I don't see anyone out there.
Is anyone in there?
Melanie?
Clover! Oh, my God, is that you?
-Let me in. Please. Clover.
-Mel.
Hold on, hold on. Wait, wait.
Wait. Hold on. Hold on.
Megan just said don't let it in.
Please help me!
-He's gonna kill me!
-Melanie.
No, wait.
Something's hurting her!
We have to help her.
We can't just stand here.
Mel!
Mel.
Max.
Help!
Melanie.
What's that?
That house wasn't there before.
Clover!
Help!
Guys, please, help!
Max. Are you okay?
Clover!
No! No! No, no, no.
No. No. No, no, no.
No, no, no!
No!
Fuck! Fuck!
Clover!
Wait a minute! Wait.
Just hold on, hold on.
What are you doing?
-We need to go help Clover.
-Help her?
Max, she's gone. She just flew
30 feet in the air.
So we go and get her.
She can't be dead yet.
"Yet." You just said it.
And she might be.
You don't even know.
I think our best move right now
is leaving to go get help
like we originally said we'd do.
Megan said
it won't let us leave.
Megan just said
a lot of things, Max.
Nina.
Come on,
you can't be on board with this.
I mean,
we're clearly dealing with
some really
fucked-up shit here, Max.
Shit that we're not,
like, equipped for.
But the only way we get through
fucked-up shit
is by sticking together.
You said that.
Oh, yeah. Okay.
You think this is what's
gonna get her
to take you back or what?
Abe!
If you guys
do make it out of here,
you can both go
and fuck yourselves.
Wait, Max! Wait!
What the fuck?
We're not leaving, Nina.
We're just going to get help.
Why would you say that to him?
Because he's going to get
himself killed
right fuckin' now.
And, honestly, I don't know.
It sounded like something
you would say.
Yeah, but when I say
those things to them,
they know that I don't mean it.
Clover, Max, Megan,
they're like
the only consistent people
that I've had in my life ever.
I know. And you wanna
save them. Right?
We can't save them
unless we save ourselves first.
So, you think that
we could just drive
out of here?
That it's that easy.
I don't know.
But, you know what,
we won't know
if we don't try. Okay?
What I do know is that
if we just keep sitting here,
something else very bad
is gonna happen to us.
-So we try and get help.
-Yeah.
Hello?
...from the mine collapse
that tragically
struck the town
just two days ago.
There are still no confirmed
number of casualties
but officials
are fearing the worst.
No.
Please let me out. Please.
I want out.
Only one way out.
You either survive the night
or become a part of it.
Please let me out.
No.
No. No. No. No!
No! No!
Suffer.
Suffer like the rest
of this cursed town.
Suffer until hell opens up
and swallows you too.
Fuck.
Clover?
Wait, I can't do this.
I can't leave my friends.
-Nina, baby. We have to go.
-No.
-I don't wanna leave my friends.
-No. Nina, no.
What are you doing?
Unlock the door!
We have to go.
We're going to get help.
Abe, unlock the-- No, Abe!
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
What is that? What is that?
-What is that?
-I have no idea!
Oh, my God.
Go!
My door's still locked.
My door is locked!
Abe?
Clover.
Clover?
Fucking clowns.
Whoa! Fuck!
Clover?
I guess we died again.
Yeah.
Is this just
gonna keep happening?
I don't know.
"Survive the night,
or become a part of it."
There's no water--
What?
Anyone else?
Please.
Okay.
So you're sure
that's what she said
about surviving?
And it was like
a for-real witch?
I think it was a for-real witch.
I mean...
Yeah, I think
that's what she said.
That's like the only thing
I can remember.
Well...
The good news is that I think
this means there's a way out.
What's that?
"Survive the night."
Right? So, maybe
if we can make it until dawn,
then maybe this will be over.
Okay, but what about the rest?
"Or become a part of it."
Yeah, part of the night, right?
It means that
if we don't get out,
we're stuck here forever.
And shit like this and that
will just keep happening.
We're turning
into something else.
You guys get that, right?
Okay, so we'll just
stick it out in here
until the sun comes up,
like Max said.
But what about Mel?
She's still stuck here
too somewhere.
If Mel was still stuck,
then she would be here.
And all those people
on that wall,
they would be here,
and they're not, so...
-Where are they?
-Oh, my God.
We didn't come here
looking for Mel, okay, Clover?
We came hoping
to find you again.
Like, the old you.
We were hoping this
would help you move on.
Help you get back to,
you know, living.
Abe.
-Are you okay?
-Here, take some.
Abe.
Holy fuck!
Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
It's in my mouth!
Nina! Stop! The water.
-You saw him drink the water.
-Didn't we all drink the wat--?
Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
-What do we do?
-I don't know.
I need a second to think.
That was a lot.
Meg?
No.
-Megan?
-No, no, no. Please.
Please. No.
Megan.
-What do we do, Max?
-I don't know.
Oh, my God.
I don't know what to do.
Help me.
Megan. What do we do?
Megan.
Kill me, Max.
What? No!
Please.
All of our friends are dead.
And we drank the water,
and we're covered
in the same shit they were.
No, we need to start over
and come up with a plan.
Look. The sand
has almost run out.
It's almost dawn.
Okay? And maybe we'll survive.
We'll come back. Okay? Okay?
It's only been twice so far.
And you saw the other signatures
in the book.
Everyone else has way more.
We'll come back.
We need to try and save them.
Please do it. Please hurry.
Max, hurry.
I can't! I can't.
Max, no.
I can't. I'm sorry.
You?
You almost made it.
Almost!
But not quite.
You don't survive
by sitting still, Miss Clover.
What?
Is anyone else
growing new teeth?
Wait, how many
are we supposed to have?
I don't know,
but it's an even number.
Guys, clearly it doesn't work
to just wait it out.
I mean, there has to be
something here
to help us come up with a plan.
Holy fuck. This is the guy.
This is... Yeah, this is the guy
from the gas station. Look!
-What?
-He's Dr Alan Hill.
He's, like, somehow
connected to this place.
Why? What's so special about it?
Twenty years ago
there was a mining disaster.
Happened right here
in Glore Valley.
"Working with outside engineers,
"investigators confirmed
the destruction
"was caused by boring
too deep into the earth
"and too far under the town,
"resulting in the death
of over 1,100 people.
"Dr Alan Hill,
a trauma specialist,
"was brought in
to work with the survivors."
The whole town got, like,
swallowed up by the earth.
That's why there's
no other houses here.
And that's why
there's windows down here.
This whole floor
used to be above ground.
That means
that's the front door.
Guys, who gives a shit?
I feel like we really need
to just be getting
weapons right now.
Okay, but I think we need more
than just weapons
of brute force.
Like what, Max?
No, thank you.
I think we need the Bible
as a weapon.
Yeah, dude, not against
a masked maniac, though.
But we're not just up
against that psycho.
Every single night something new
is trying to kill us.
Yeah, but why?
Think about it.
If it was the same thing
over and over again,
you'd become
less scared over time.
But what's more terrifying than
not knowing what comes next.
Whoever,
whatever,
is doing this...
it wants to keep us afraid.
Yeah, well, it's working.
I think I found something.
I don't think that's gonna
help us. A VHS tape?
Knowledge is power.
Great, that's exactly
what we need
-right now.
-Wow.
Sorry, sorry, sorry.
Very powerful, Max. Thank you.
Just give me a second.
I have another one.
Do you want us
to leave you alone for a second?
-Just shut up. Abe.
-All right, all right.
Please.
What are you doing to me?
Why do I keep coming back?
Why do you have these things
that keep killing me?
Who are you?!
What do you want from me?! Huh?
The patient showed signs of
starvation and muscle atrophy.
What's happening to me?
But most importantly,
intense fear, anxiety,
feelings of hopelessness
and utter despair.
Fortunately for my experiments,
the trauma of the mining
disaster still lingers,
affecting both survivors
and visitors.
The longer he was trapped here,
the more desperate
and afraid he became...
and also the more monstrous.
Help! God, please!
Eleven nights. That's the most
in my experiments so far.
Soon, those emotions
began to affect his body
in more interesting ways,
transforming into
a creature known
as the Wendigo.
It is no coincidence
that in psychology,
the Wendigo represents
extreme hunger,
extreme want.
That's what's happening to us.
That's what we're becoming.
Yeah.
Now you're getting it.
Let us out.
Let us out!
Oh, there's a way out,
but not without a price.
-Ask him how.
-Abe!
How?
Someone always has to die.
Four of you can leave,
but one has to die.
No.
Nice try, asshole.
Wait, hold on. I think we should
at least just hear him out.
Why? Are you willing
to sacrifice yourself for us?
No.
We can't trust this guy.
Which means our only real shot
of getting out
of here is getting some answers,
and the one
with the answers is Hill.
He's here somewhere.
I can feel it.
How is this supposed to help us?
The whole town was destroyed.
He could be anywhere.
No. Not "anywhere."
He's there.
Was there. And Nina just said
none of this even
exists any more.
So we just need to try
to get him out of hiding.
I wanna see you. Face-to-face.
Clover, what are you doing?
He's the key to all of this.
That can be arranged.
But just you, Clover.
Not your friends.
-No.
-Clover, no.
This is a trap,
just like everything else here.
Actually, I think
it's a pretty good idea.
Abe, just shut
the fuck up, okay?
It's only night four. Clover,
-you're gonna have more chances.
-We don't know that.
All the other signatures
in the book go way past that.
Guys, Abe is right.
-This is our chance.
-No. Don't listen to him.
I'm out in the woods.
I'm here with your sister.
I might just let you see her.
-Clo.
-There you go. Yeah.
-Clover, come on.
-No.
I have to try.
-No, no, no. Clover!
-Let her go!
-Back off!
-Let her go, let her go!
-What is wrong with you?
-What? Hey!
Hey! Nina!
You fucking prick!
What?! I didn't think
she was gonna actually do it.
Yes, you did. You knew she would
and you took advantage.
Fucking coward!
Look, Megan,
we need to find Clover
before something
permanent happens.
-To do what?
-We're gonna go and find her.
And if she's dead already,
we're gonna kill each other
and start over again.
Sounds like a plan.
Abe first.
Wait-Wait! Just wait, hold on.
Say we start over.
What then?
We just keep running away
until we run out of chances?
Are you fucking serious?
I don't wanna live
knowing that I'm alive
because someone else is dead!
-Because Clover is dead!
-But look at us!
How many more deaths
do you have in you? Be honest.
I mean, didn't she try and kill
herself twice last year?
Isn't this just giving her
what she wa--?
What the fuck, Nina?!
You guys go find Clover.
Otherwise it'll be two people
we have to leave behind.
Let's go.
You better hope they find her.
I'm here!
You have me.
No.
Oh, no.
No, please, please, please.
Please! Sh-- Please.
No, no. No!
Please! Please! Please! Please!
Please!
No! Wait, wait!
Oh, my God.
You need to try
and survive, Nina.
I will.
Just not this time.
I'm scared of dying, Nina.
Like, really dying.
Me too.
But living without my friends
scares me even more.
Him first.
What?
Clover!
Clo!
Holy shit.
Clover?
Clover!
Over there.
The hell?
Run!
Max! Max!
It'll break if I move.
Okay, okay.
Just give me your hand.
Okay, okay, I got you.
I'm gonna pull on three. Okay?
Okay.
One, two, three.
Meg!
Clover! Clover!
Max!
You're here.
I got you. I got you.
Okay. Ready?
Okay.
I'm sorry. Aw, fuck.
Max. Max. Max.
Is that Melanie?
-Come on. Come on.
-Melanie! No, no!
I got you. I got you.
Melanie!
I fucked up, Max.
What?
-I fucked up.
-No.
-Yes. Yes. Yes.
-No, no, no.
Yeah.
Why did you come for me?
You all could have escaped.
No. No, no, no. We'll have
more chances to get out of this.
Okay? Together.
I'm not leaving you behind.
When we die, like...
for real...
you think we get the chance
to do it all again?
I hope not.
Why?
Just means more somehow
when you know
you only have one shot.
Yeah.
Are the others still alive?
I'm not sure about Abe and Nina.
What about Megan?
What are you doing? I just said
I don't know about Abe and Nina.
But we know that Megan is dead.
That's enough
for me to try and start again.
This next one might be our last.
But I think
we can all survive, Max.
So let's get started
by dying first.
I know. I know. It's okay.
Yeah.
Thank you.
Hey!
Fuck y--!
Just one second, Mel.
Mel. Mel.
Wait, hey. You should take this.
No, Clover.
It was Mom's.
You should take it.
No. You keep it.
Well, do you wanna
wait out the storm at least?
I just wanna get going.
It's a long way to New York.
But then it's just me.
Yeah.
I mean, I've asked you to come
with me how many times now?
Let's just leave.
I told you that I can't.
You can't sit still
for the rest of your life, Clo.
It's not living.
At least I'm not running away.
You think that's what I'm doing,
running away?
I'm actually running
towards something.
Towards what?
School. A new city. A new life.
I love you.
But I can't just sit here
and waste away
becoming something I'd hate.
Mel.
Mel, wait!
Hey. Hey.
Hey, hey, hey. Hey.
I had to drag you in here.
I thought we lost you.
Hey.
Is there...?
Is there something on my back?
-You look fine.
-Are you sure?
It feels like there's
something back there.
How long have we been here?
I don't know.
Three or four nights, I think.
Five, actually.
It's been five.
No, not five.
-Thirteen.
-What?
It's been 13 nights.
Go check the book.
Yeah, nobody has more than 13.
Tonight might be
our last chance.
I don't remember
any of these things.
Yeah, me neither.
We didn't do what we said, Max.
The next one wasn't the last and
neither was the one after that,
or the one after that.
Wait.
Where's Megan?
Shit. Megan.
She's not in there.
Maybe something
already happened to her?
Or it got to her first.
What? What got to her?
The night.
Survive the night
or become a part of it.
There's nothing that says
it would happen
to all of us at the same time.
Because there's nothing
that says anything, Abe.
I know, but different people
could have
a different number of chances,
like it's random.
You could be right.
Okay. Okay, great.
So then what do we do, huh?
Megan is just-- She's gone?
Fuck. Why can't we
remember anything?
Why didn't we write
anything down?
Would it have mattered?
It'd be gone once
the night starts over anyway.
-Your signature isn't.
-But that's all that's in there.
Didn't I record something?
Holy shit. Guys, come here.
Look.
There's so much stuff.
What?
Okay. All right.
Don't worry. We'll get it.
Okay.
Just don't move.
I'm gonna grab it.
-Oh, my God.
-Okay.
Abe? Abe, be careful.
-Please get it.
-Abe?
What?
Is it gone?
Yeah. It's gone.
Did it fall off?
-What the fuck?!
-What?
-Holy shit.
-Is it still on my face?
-It's fine, it's fine.
-Clover, it's okay, it's okay.
Is it still on my face?!
Oh, my God.
Fuck. It's locked.
Fuck.
What's that?
What the fuck?
What the fuck is that?
Is that a person?
Holy shit, holy shit.
What the fuck?!
Max. We should turn back.
Look at all this shit.
There's fucking blood
on the walls.
Just be quiet, Abe.
What the hell?
Max!
Abe!
Die! Die! Die!
Max!
Die! Die!
Why won't you fucking die?!
Oh, shit. What the fuck?
-What is that?
-What the fuck is that?
What is that?!
-Nina!
-What the fuck?! No!
-What is that?!
Abe! What is that?!
Holy shit!
I'm gonna follow him
and see if I can find out
anything that will help us.
I have to try.
-Fuck.
-Oh, my God. They're coming.
Fuck. They're all coming.
We need to run.
All we've been doing
is running away.
So let's start running
towards something.
What do you mean?
I'm going into that tunnel.
Clover. We don't even know
what's over there.
You realise this could
be our last night.
Good.
It means more
when you only have one shot.
I'm sorry I got you into this.
You're all here because of me.
Melanie was my family,
but you're my family too.
So I'm gonna save Megan,
kill Hill
and then get us
the fuck out of here.
I'm done with death.
Clover.
We stick together.
Oh, fuck.
Come on.
Oh, my God.
Holy shit.
This place is huge.
Hey, careful.
Watch your step.
Come on.
Is that...?
Don't move.
Go, go, go!
Go! Go, go, go!
-Nina! Nina! Go! Come on!
-Go, go, go!
Come on, guys!
Go, go, go! Go!
Guys, right here, right here!
Right here!
Go! Go, go!
Wait! Wait! Wait!
Oh, fuck.
-Max. Max, Max!
-Go! We'll find another way!
Max, no!
Go! Go find Megan!
Go! We'll make it out of here.
Hey, asshole!
Oh, fuck.
Please don't do this. Mel.
It's m-- It's me. It's me.
I love you, Mel.
But I'm getting the fuck out
of this hellhole.
Max!
Fuck.
Fuck you, asshole. Die!
Aw, fuck.
Help!
-Megan!
-Help!
-Clover!
Watch out!
Megan, I'm gonna find a way
out of here.
I'm gonna get a key, okay?
Hurry!
You have been
an intriguing patient, Clover.
Far more interesting
than the rest.
Severe depression,
two failed suicide attempts,
extreme anxiety...
You've lost control, Clover.
And that's evident by every
monster you've encountered here.
You see, they each represent
a unique manifestation
of your psyche.
What are you talking about?
Being chased
by a masked psycho is common.
Everyone feels powerless
in some way.
And the witch is, of course,
a personification of repression.
Now, the spontaneous combustion...
Very rare, Clover.
I think it's a nod
to your more
self-destructive tendencies.
Fuck you.
I am getting my friends
out of here.
Well, you're the only one
who can, Clover.
This place...
is drawing on your insecurities
and your fears.
I'm sorry, are you telling me
that this was all in my head?
Is none of this real?
Of course it's real.
But you are the engine
that makes it run,
just like Melanie
and all the others
made it run, run, run, run.
Help! Help!
You hear that, Clover?
Your friends
are all about to die again.
Tick, tick, tick...
Why? Why are you doing this?
Why?
Because this is what I study.
Fear is my trade.
People with trauma,
like yourself, Clover...
And places with trauma,
like Glore Valley...
When I put
the two of them together...
trauma becomes terror...
and sparks...
ignite.
Help!
Shit, guys, I'm fucking stuck!
And it creates...
the perfect...
horror.
Fuck, they're coming!
Please help! Please!
But to make this
truly effective
like I've said before,
someone always has to die.
They're fucking coming! Hurry!
Yeah.
But this time...
it's you.
Clover!
Hurry!
Go.
Go, go, go.
The ladder.
Come on!
There's a way up!
Come on, get up.
Clover!
No! No!
-Clover!
-We got you, we got you.
Megan!
What's happening?
Look. Look. The sky.
We did it.
It's over.
Jesus!
You guys planning on staying
another night, or what?