The trial for the chairman
of Kwang Industries
is set to begin in high court.
The trial is a culmination
of a year-long investigation
of Korean seafood tycoon,
Kwang Gim, or "King" Kwang.
Chairman Kwang faces charges
that range from selling
counterfeit carbon offsets
to violating bans
on net fishing.
Ladies and gentlemen,
I'm here to apologize
to the true victims today.
The Kwang family,
and our 200,000
hard-working employees.
For them, I look forward
to proving my innocence.
Thank you.
- What the hell was that?
- Kwang.
The charges are bullshit.
You control trade routes.
Distribution centers.
You're a billionaire, and what,
they come up against you with
fishing charges?
- Get out.
- Oh, okay.
Where's my wife?
Good morning, madam.
May I help you?
Just looking.
Please.
- Hmm.
- A brand-new model.
The Ferrari 488 Pista Spider.
It is the most beautiful
thing in this room.
Hmm.
Second only to you, of course.
- Can I look inside?
- Yes, for sure.
No, inside.
Of course.
Behold, Ferrari's most
powerful V8 engine.
Twin turbocharged, 3.9
liter, over 700 horsepower.
Let's try it.
Yes.
Ready?
You know how...
how to drive, huh?
Yeah.
Whoa!
Thank God.
Oh! Oh! Oh!
Whoa!
What the hell are you
doing? This just came in.
We haven't even
calibrated it yet.
Oh, I'm sorry, Ms. Kwang.
I didn't see it was you.
The timing's off.
How long would it take
to adjust the timing?
Two days.
Fine, for you, just one hour.
Thank you.
Joey, my love, you're home.
Champagne?
What are we celebrating?
Just another day with
my beautiful wife.
Cheers.
Where were you today? You
didn't pick up your phone.
Bad signal. Bad battery.
Just, my trial started today.
How did it go?
Officials want an investigation.
Board members want my head.
Other than that, just great.
I'm sorry. Who's the snitch?
That's an excellent question.
You don't think it was me?
Oh, darling, your
imagination is priceless.
You do know that a
wife can't testify.
Then it's a good
thing we're married.
Is it?
Of course it is.
You know, there is a thing
I want to discuss with you.
Is it necessary for you
to buy everything you see?
Where does it all go?
Oh me, darling.
I'm merely asking.
Do you need another Ferrari?
I bought it for you.
Happy birthday.
Sweetheart.
Thank you.
Shares of Kwang dropped over 30%
after today's allegations.
The stock had already
dropped to its all-time low
earlier this month,
after officials assembled
a task force to
investigate Kwang...
Mom! It's knock,
wait, then enter.
You can't just barge
in. I'm not a baby.
You'll always be my baby.
This is the best part of my day.
Yeah. Love you too, Mom.
Oh...
What are you doing?
Unpacking, Mom. Getting out.
Stop for a second.
What's going on?
Kwang has just made the
list of all-time assholes.
Right next to Freddy
Krueger and Leatherface.
- Not funny.
- Sorry. Bad joke.
But he's gonna be in jail
by the end of the week.
And I don't want to be here when
that happens, and neither do you.
And where will you go?
Paris. The Ocean Outlaws
is docked there right now.
They're starting a
new mission next week.
Heading to Milagro.
Kwang has boats in Milagro.
How's that going to look?
Like I have the will for
revolution and change.
Like somebody's finally
standing up to Kwang.
He's destroying entire
marine ecosystems.
Shhh!
Mom, no.
Just because you like
spending Kwang's money
doesn't mean I
have to stay here.
Hey, stop it.
You don't know what
you're talking about.
Fine.
I know you and Kwang
don't get along.
- He's gross.
- He's not.
I don't know why
you married him.
Because a long time
ago, I needed help.
We needed help, and
Kwang was there.
We can't forget that, no
matter what you think of him.
Do you understand?
I'll take you to
Paris next weekend.
Okay?
Do you miss Dad?
Of course I do.
Then why don't you
ever talk about him?
Because sometimes it's
easier to forget the past.
- Besides, I told you everything.
- He was a pastry chef.
He died in a car
accident. The end.
Seems there's a lot
more to fill in.
All you need to know
is whatever happened,
he brought me you.
And I wouldn't
change any of that.
Any of you guys got a cigarette?
Hands up, dirtbag! I'm
not gonna say it again.
Yeah, I heard you
the first time.
- Hands up. Now!
- All right, officer, please.
Come on. I will comply.
Just give me a minute.
All right?
You're scaring the fish.
- Wait. Whoa, whoa! Come on.
- Let's go.
Officer, get those
cuffs off my agent, now!
Your agent didn't have any ID.
Because he's undercover.
Where do you suggest he
keep his badge? His ass?
Up yours? Get out!
- Give me the key.
- Get out!
Look after the fish.
John, you okay?
I will be, once I
get a cigarette.
- Where's Santiago?
- He's fine.
Santiago?
Everything's gonna be fine.
You were supposed to observe
and report, not crash and burn.
What the hell happened?
Our shift was going
really smooth.
We were getting through
a lot of Kung Pow orders.
They're very good, by the
way, here, you should try it.
John, stop stalling.
All right, fine.
I was finishing a
tray of crème brûlées,
and the perps showed up.
We were getting it all on
camera, and then Santiago...
- Hey!
- Is it yours?
No, it's a fake. No, it's a
fake one. It's a fake one.
You know, yesterday was a
party, and... with my kids,
and I was police, you know?
No, tranquilo.
Tranquilo. No, no, no.
- Tranquilo, por favor.
- Hey, hey, buddy, buddy, buddy.
It's a friend of mine.
He... it's a joke, dude.
It... it's not even
real. It's not even real.
♪ Love is a burning thing ♪
♪ And it makes a fiery ring ♪
♪ Bound by wild desire ♪
♪ I fell in to a ring of fire ♪
♪ I fell into a
burning Ring of fire ♪
♪ I went down, down, down ♪
♪ And the flames went higher ♪
♪ And it burns, burns, burns ♪
♪ The ring of fire ♪
♪ I fell into a
burning Ring of fire ♪
♪ I went down, down, down ♪
♪ And the flames ♪
So, I just want
to stop fighting.
- What do you want?
- I just want to eat.
Well, you know I
don't like spicy.
♪ I fell in to a ring of fire ♪
Oh, man.
♪ I fell into a
burning Ring of fire ♪
Oh, my God.
All right, just hang
on. All right? Hold up.
♪ And the flames went higher ♪
♪ And it burns, burns, burns ♪
Huh? Dude, please.
Come on. Give me a minute.
Oh, man.
Okay.
All right.
Sorry, man.
Ah!
I'll kill you!
Unh!
Fire! Ah!
This way. This way, please.
All right, buddy.
Come on, up you get. Let's go.
- Ah! Oh!
- You stay here.
Just stay here, all right?
I'll be back.
Oh, no.
As an agent of the DEA,
I'm authorized to offer you
asylum for any information
you have on Kwang Enterprises.
No.
I can offer you a green card,
at an apartment in Arizona.
It's very nice.
No, no. Ai!
Come on, come on,
come on, come on.
Come on.
And that's when they
put the bracelets on.
I suppose you want to go see?
Let's go.
Watch your step.
Ah! Is that a fish?
John, what the...
Six months of undercover
work up in smoke.
Please tell me, how am I
supposed to build a case on this?
You can't. There's absolutely
nothing useful here.
I don't know. Maybe
you can use this?
Sir! Sir.
With the help of
local law enforcement,
we were able to recover
nearly 400 kilos of heroin.
Estimated street
value, $300 million.
But there is still
much to be done.
Every day in the United States,
120 people die
from drug overdose.
We are committed to fighting
this problem at its source,
and stopping those
who would profit
from this death and suffering.
Don't care who you
are, where you are,
you cannot run, you cannot hide.
We will find you.
Damn it!
Oh!
Oh, you scared me!
I'm sorry about earlier.
I wasn't mad at you.
Hard to tell these days.
It's just this ridiculous trial.
Let's go to the summer
house for the weekend.
- Get out of here.
- Oh!
Sure. That will be nice.
Thank you for my
birthday present.
I like it a lot.
But you know what
I would love more?
Let me go freshen up.
Joey, let's just talk.
- About what?
- About us.
About love.
I don't know if I
have any love to give.
Of course you do.
You love Raymond.
You love shopping.
You love me.
Do I?
No.
Joey, it's been 15 years.
15 years since I've taken
care of you and Raymond.
Whoever broke your heart
is not coming back.
Don't you think it's
time to move on?
Together?
I love you.
What is it, Lawlor?
Hey, um, I've been going
over this tip sheet,
and there's a confidential
informant that's come forward.
Kwang Industries. Why
am I not surprised?
Illegal net fishing.
Killing dolphins.
You want to take
Kwang down for this?
We put away Al
Capone for tax fraud.
I mean, the C.I. wants
to give us his ledger.
No one with real information
is gonna rat out on Kwang.
They're all too scared of
him. This is chicken shit.
What if it isn't?
What if this is everything we
need to finally take him down?
- What's the handoff?
- Taipei.
No. Absolutely not. After
what happened last time.
That was 15 years ago.
And look where it's landed you.
15 years of bouncing around from
field office to field office,
and doing mostly desk work.
Look, we all want
to take Kwang down.
- You stopped the shipment.
- One shipment. One.
Take your wins as they come,
and leave the rest alone.
Charlotte, it's one weekend.
Just a couple of days, to
finally take him down for good.
Even if we wanted to, I can't
send an agent down there,
and certainly not you.
I will go deep
cover. My own assets.
- No one'll even know I'm there.
- No.
I am literally going
to pick up a ledger.
- No, absolutely not.
- Charlotte, think about...
No!
All right, thanks.
- Thank you so much.
- What is wrong with you?
You're like a dog with
a bone. Let it go.
Here. To be perfectly clear.
A leave of absence? You're
sending me home now?
No, John. I'm sending
you on vacation.
It's what happens when
people do a good job.
Actually, a great job.
It was a solid bust.
Now, go relax.
The drugs will still be here
on Tuesday, and so will Kwang.
- Just, so, it's a long weekend.
- Yeah, John.
Go drink something fruity
on a beach somewhere.
All right.
Okay. Thanks.
Um, I will definitely
make the most of it.
- Oh! Can you do me one favor?
- What?
- Could you just watch my fish?
- Get out!
Hi, I'm checking on
Flight 726 to Taipei.
- You're George Washington?
- Yep, that's me.
Welcome aboard. Walk
this way, please.
- Uh, excuse me, miss?
- Yes?
Can I get a bourbon?
Two doubles.
Oh, after take-off.
Raymond. Good morning.
Can I help you with something?
Oh, I'm just looking
for a pencil sharpener.
Hmm.
You know, I'd love to see
your drawings one day.
Hey, how about we go play
golf together sometime, huh?
No.
Raymond.
You know, I'm trying my best.
Why do you hate me so much?
The Austrian women's volleyball
team will face off this weekend
against Chinese Taipei in
a preseason exhibition game
that will test both
team's new lineups.
Austrian head Coach Jaime
Newsome had this to say.
How long have you been a team?
We've been, uh, together...
say. How long have
you been a team?
We've been...
Mm! Hey! Yo!
Over here.
You don't look like
a George Washington.
Yeah? You look like
you gained weight.
Hmm! Haven't you heard?
Dad bods are cool now.
- Say hello to Freddie.
- Let's get to the hotel.
Welcome, Mr. Washington.
I see we have you
for the weekend.
- You do.
- Any luggage?
Yeah, three pieces.
Now, welcome to
Taipei Marriott Hotel.
Ooh la la.
I'm here to pick
up a ledger, man.
Pray for the best.
Pray for the
worst. Yeah, yeah.
- Hey, what time's the drop?
- Five p.m.
Ooh, we've got time for a
late lunch or an early dinner.
- Which one you prefer?
- Shower.
- Shower. Hey, but this is good.
- Yes.
Yeah!
Come with me now.
No!
What are you doing? Stop it!
Stop it! Don't
have him killed!
Enough.
Enough!
W... Why?
Because our beloved
son is the snitch.
No.
- I don't believe it.
- Well, believe it.
He's trying to ruin me.
Destroy everything we've built.
You're wrong. You're wrong.
You promised to protect us.
Sweetheart, I am
trying to protect us.
You think you're so
clever, don't you, huh?
- Now, where is the ledger?
- Raymond!
Is this true? Give it
back! Give it back.
His tuna boats are
killing dolphins.
- Dolphins?
- His processing plants...
You did this because
of some dolphins?
You're destroying our ecosystem!
I had to do something.
Good for you.
Taking initiative.
But where is my ledger?
Because the rest of it has
nothing to do with any dolphins!
Leave me!
Kwang? Just give me a
minute. I'll talk to him.
Please?
Okay.
Just tell him. Hey, it's fine.
Just tell him what's
going on, hon.
Please, Mom. Five minutes.
I just need five minutes.
I need to get the
ledger to Lawlor.
What?
Some agent, John Lawlor.
John Lawlor.
He emailed me back. I just
need five more minutes.
- What are you talking about?
- Mom, please.
Five minutes.
What?
- Please, Mom.
- No. No, what... what...
Oh my God.
Oh! What are you talking about?
Please, Mom.
Okay, that's enough, now.
All right.
Five minutes.
- Hit me.
- What?
It's the only way he'll
talk. Now, hit me.
I won't hit you.
I hate smoking.
It's filthy.
And a burnt smell
gets into your hair,
your clothes, your fingernails.
No matter what you do, you
just can't get rid of it.
It's awful.
But when we got married,
I had to start.
The smoking smell
is nothing compared
to the smell of my husband.
The smell of sweaty
desperation. It makes me gag.
No matter what he does or
how much money he spends,
or how much he scrubs,
the putrid stink...
never goes away.
- Funny?
- Ah!
Ah! Ah!
Die!
No!
Now, you tell me.
Where is my ledger?
Stop! Stop!
- Don't touch him!
- Hmm?
I gave you everything.
And you do this to me?
Don't touch...
Stop. Stop. Please, stop.
I'll tell you where the
ledger is. Just stop it.
Stop it!
I had a friend take the
ledger to the Marriott Hotel.
It's Room 2018.
What do you mean, "had"?
Hey, John. Get involved.
They ain't got chicken feet
like this in Minnesota.
You got xiaolongbao?
No. We got shumai,
though. You like shumai?
I got it.
I don't believe it.
- It's all here.
- What's that?
All this for a little red book?
You took too many guns.
Go find the ledger.
Yes.
You! Keep her.
You! Come with me.
- And as for you...
- Mom.
During the Joseon Dynasty,
anybody that would
break the law...
Mommy!
-...was forever marked as a criminal.
- Mom!
- No! No! No!
And depending on the
severity of the crime...
No! Oh, no! Please!
Please! Stop! No! No! No!
They were cut into quarters.
Stop! Stop!
Ah!
And they would start...
with the limbs.
- Oh no!
- Oh my God!
No, Mom! No!
Don't worry, son, we'll get
you the best prosthetics
- that money can buy.
- No! No!
No!
Let him go.
Sweetheart.
What, you're killing people now?
Let us go!
You're not gonna shoot me.
Who's gonna protect you?
Who's gonna love you?
- Ah!
- Oh!
What?
Mom, slow down.
Where'd you learn how
to drive like this?
Gotta get to the hotel.
- Warn him.
- What? Warn who?
Wipe your nose.
Help!
I can't believe you're still
on Kwang after all this time.
With all this, I can put
him away for two lifetimes.
This way.
Take them out.
Ooh! Dessert is served.
Hello, boys. Are you
my club sandwich?
Thank you, sir.
A little bit of sugar ain't
gonna ruin that six-pack.
- What?
- Kid lied to us. No one here.
Well, they have to be somewhere.
You go check the rest
of the hotel, okay?
Can I help you, sir?
I'm looking for my American
partners. They check in today,
I take it.
- Hey.
- Joey?
We need to talk.
It's an emergency.
What are you doing here?
How did you find me?
Hey, what happened to your face?
Mom, who's this?
- "Mom"? You have a son?
- John, you're in danger.
- Wait, wait. His name's John?
- Shh! Quiet. Mommy's talking.
- What... what's going on here?
- Listen, they know you have the ledger.
Kwang is sending men right
now to kill all of you.
- Go to the bathroom.
- Okay.
How do you know about Kwang?
Because I'm married to him.
Wait, wait. Okay, Mom,
seriously, who is this guy?
- Why is he looking at me like...
- Quiet! Both of you!
If you want to know more,
we have to leave right now.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. Hold
on a minute, all right?
I'm just gonna need a minute.
I haven't seen you in,
what, like, 15 years?
Just give me a
minute. All right?
- Get in.
- Okay, okay.
Come on!
Cover us! Get to the bathroom.
Cover us, please.
Get under the sink.
Open the door.
- What?
- Yo, boss. We found them.
- Your wife's here.
- You bring me my wife...
and you kill everyone else.
What about the kid?
Hello? Hello?
Hold on.
Stop, stop, stop, stop, stop,
stop, stop, stop, stop, stop.
You guys have the wrong room.
You have the wrong room.
Go find them.
Shoot!
You all right?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
Follow me.
Follow him.
Go.
Stairs. Stairs.
Step away from the door.
Stairs.
Open it!
No, no, no, no. Come
this way. To the bar.
What are you doing?
We need to go.
It's just the cops.
Just let them go past.
So he's really Kwang's son?
- No.
- Definitely not.
Raymond, meet your son,
John. John, meet your dad.
What?
Raymond, meet your dad.
John, meet your son.
Any questions?
So you're not a chef?
No.
Come on, let's go. Come on.
Hey! Excuse me, sir.
Hey! After them! Hey!
- Is this yours?
- Yeah.
- There's only two seats.
- Get in here.
Stop him, hurry!
Stop the Ferrari.
Stop looking at me.
- Are we going to the police?
- No.
- Why not?
- Kwang knows every cop in town.
And I'm not even
supposed to be here.
What? Why?
I was going after Kwang.
I'm not officially here.
I came alone.
So you came back after all this
time for Kwang, but not for me?
How was I supposed to
even know you were here?
Because I live here, remember?
You're supposed to be dead.
Yeah, well, give
it another minute,
kid, and your mom will
take care of that.
I see you haven't changed a bit.
Thanks. I moisturize.
- And no sugar. It ages you.
- I meant your driving.
Sir.
The guest name is George
Washington. He's American.
And what is George Washington
doing with Kwang's wife?
All this time
I've been taking cooking classes to
get close to my dead pastry chef dad,
and he's not even dead.
- Pastry chef? Seriously?
- Shh. Quiet, please.
And why am I a dead pastry chef?
- Yeah, Mom, why?
Everyone, shut up
and let me drive.
Actually, uh...
I was a pastry chef
for about a month.
I make a mean crème brûlée.
Well.
Sir.
You go find my wife.
Mom, I'm bleeding.
- What?
- No, it's not you, kid. It's me.
Raymond, put
pressure. Right there.
No, no, no, no, no. Down. Yes.
- We have to get to a hospital.
- No. No hospital.
- Mom?
- I've got an idea.
What the...
- Hey, hey!
- Hey, I'm so sorry.
Driving a sports car, so what?
Who do you think you are?
So sorry.
Once you've hacked in,
check all the traffic cams.
Flag anybody in a red
Ferrari. That'll be her.
Get off the car!
Hands, hands! Show
me your hands!
Watch out of my car.
Don't scratch my Ferrari.
My car!
She gave my Ferrari
to a pizza guy?
What did she say?
Ha... happy birthday.
"Happy birthday."
Let's go.
Hey, this one.
This one. Come.
Ew, Mom, gross.
What are you doing?
Shh!
Hey, guys. What
are you doing here,
Ah, man, we... we
forgot our keys.
Can I just borrow your
flashlight for a second?
What?
Take that.
Get in.
Who are you people?
I mean, you're stealing cars
and he's punching everyone?
Are you really my parents?
Your will for revolution and
change had to come from somewhere.
Get in.
Listen to your mother.
Why didn't you tell
me you were pregnant?
You didn't give me a chance.
What do you mean?
Now's not the time
to rewrite the past.
We need to figure out how to get
us out of this shit you put us in.
- Me? I put you in this?
- Yes.
You clean this up. You
better have a plan.
All right.
That's it? That's
your plan? Sleeping?
No. I think better when I sleep.
Who is going to
believe that things
can be figured out
while sleeping?
You just showed up from nowhere
after 15 years and gave me a mess.
And now I have to fix
all your shitty things.
You better have a plan
when you wake up...
I told you no hospital.
It's safe.
We're in my village.
The fishing village?
Things have changed.
Doctor said you were lucky.
But you lost a lot of blood.
They had to give
you a transfusion.
Lucky for you, your son
has the same blood type.
Raymond.
Where is he?
So he's really my son?
And Kwang's been raising him?
Kwang was around. I
raised him myself.
Yeah, well, you didn't
have to, if you'd told me.
The last time I saw you,
you told me to run away.
I didn't tell you to run
to someone like Kwang.
No one else was here for me,
so you don't get to judge.
There are many things you don't
know and you'll never understand.
No, no, no. I
understand completely.
Love your bracelet.
What is it? Tiffany's? Cartier?
Yes, John. You
understand me completely.
I ran to the one person who gave me
the riches and pearls that I deserve.
And Raymond, stop
pretending you're asleep.
You two do anything but fight?
- Yes.
- No.
Mrs. Kwang? Some of our
patients wanna say thank you.
Oh, thank you.
Why all the flowers?
Mrs. Kwang is our
biggest donor.
Actually, the only donor.
Thanks to her, we have the
best hospital in the area.
She saved countless lives.
I have to go.
Let's go.
Yeah, Raymond.
Thank you all.
- Thank you.
- Appreciate it.
Granny?
I left him. I did it.
Mom, who's this?
Come here.
Raymond!
How much you've grown.
My grandmother. Your
great-grandmother.
Granny, we're going
to change our clothes.
Let's go clean up.
Sorry.
Whoa.
Mom, is this where you grew up?
I know it's not much.
Are you kidding?
This is awesome.
Why have you never
brought me here before?
Sometimes it's easier
to forget the past.
Get out of those stinky
clothes. Dinner soon.
Hey, uh, do you have some water?
Water?
Fridge?
I see you still know
your way around.
I don't remember this.
Po Po hates Kwang's money too.
But she likes cold
beer more. Change.
Oh. Hi, Joey.
Hi!
Mom, anything else you wanna
tell me about our family?
Say hello to your
cousin, Raymond.
- Hi.
- Oh, hi.
- Hi, Po Po.
- Put it there.
You're not eating?
Not until I get some answers.
I just found out that I have
a great-grandmother, a cousin.
What else aren't you telling me?
You never talk about family.
You never talk about the past.
I know nothing about
you, both of you.
So please, no more lies.
I deserve to know.
He's right.
Fine.
When your mom was young,
I wasn't exactly who you think.
Both my parents died
in fishing accidents,
so Po Po refused to
let me near the water.
So, I have to find
something else to do.
Joey!
- It's dangerous.
- Can you slow down?
Turns out I was a
really good mechanic.
I could do anything with cars.
Which was fun, but not
very useful in the village.
Wash up. Dinnertime.
-[Joey in Chinese] Okay.
Until one day, something
terrible happened.
Put them into my garage.
But Po Po was smart.
If she went to the police, they
might arrest the villagers.
By hiding the drugs, she
could keep everyone safe.
Until the day the gang
came to get them back.
Joey, wake up.
When these men came
to the small villages,
they would not just take
back their merchandise.
They would also take
away all the young girls.
But lucky for me, I could drive.
Ugh!
And then what happened?
I was offered a job.
A job? What kind of job?
Only thing I was
good at. Driving.
And then a few years
later, I met your dad.
These are really good dumplings.
John. Your turn.
All right. What
do you wanna know?
How did you two meet?
Can't remember. It
was so long ago.
John. Tell the truth.
- It was a work thing.
- What kind of work thing?
I was a cop. A DEA agent.
I was sent over here undercover
to track a drug shipment.
And, uh, I was pretending
to be a client,
following the mule car that
was transporting drugs.
And it turned out that
the driver of the car was
none other than your mother.
What?
These are really good dumplings.
-Yeah, they are, huh?
Yeah, you should
get you some more.
Now, she thought I was a competitor
trying to steal her drugs.
Playing hard to get.
I remember her hair
blowing in the wind,
and as soon as our eyes met...
that was it. I was hooked.
No, no, no. That's
not how I remember.
- Oh, yeah?
- No.
Well, how do you remember it?
First, I remember his shoes.
Can't really remember his
face. I don't know why.
But, um, I do remember
our first kiss.
You sure that was
our first kiss?
Yes, I remember
it. Why don't you?
- Oof. You're in trouble now.
- No, no, no. Hold on.
Um, okay, I may not
remember our first kiss,
but I definitely
remember our second.
And our third.
And our fourth.
And our fifth.
No. That's our sixth.
No, no.
I'm talking about...
our fifth.
Oh, yeah.
How could I forget?
Oh. That one sounds
less romantic.
- More dumplings?
- Yeah.
I don't understand. What
happens? Why did you break up?
Some people just... they
can't make up their mind.
Some people care only about
one thing, their career.
Yeah, but some people's jobs
are about saving people.
And for some people, that's
easier than raising a family.
It's a little difficult when no one
tells you that you have a family.
Excuses. Weasel out of it.
It's not an excuse!
Whoa, whoa. Guys, guys, guys.
I think I've heard enough.
- It's been a long day.
- Yeah.
Okay.
- Help me clean up.
- Sure, Mom.
You too. Please.
Yeah, of course.
Why are you so awesome?
Such a good job.
Thanks.
Hey. You seen your mom?
- Morning to you too.
- Sorry, man. Good morning.
Peel peas there.
So, uh... you like cooking?
Not really.
So why are you studying?
Oh, yeah. I'm sorry
to disappoint.
That was a brave thing you
did, stealing the ledger.
Just wanted Kwang to
stop killing dolphins.
Yeah, I hear you.
Actually, I saved some fish the
other day. There was this big fire...
Dolphins aren't fish. They're
mammals, just like you and me.
Yeah, yeah, of course.
Well, these were definitely fish.
You know, that little cute ones.
I interned for
Kwang last semester.
That's when I found out
that his fishing boats kill
over 650,000 dolphins a year.
They get caught up in the nets.
And the fishermen actually chop
them up and used them as bait.
Kwang's a piece of shit
dickhead dolphin killer.
Hey, hey, watch
your language, kid.
Okay, Dad.
Sorry, I meant John.
Or is it "Agent Lawlor, sir"?
Cut me some slack, huh?
It's not that I
don't wanna be Dad,
it's just, you know, it's
just... this is all new to me.
Yeah, well, I'm not
really an expert either.
Pretty good at these
beans, though, huh?
- Stay here.
- All right.
Hey. I've been looking for you.
I was in town getting some
spare parts for the buggy.
We're meant to hide, remember?
Don't worry, I know how to hide.
But you, you're the expert.
You're really good at it.
All right, can we, uh, take
some time out for a minute?
There's a lot of details in
your story that are missing.
Just fill me in.
What happened to you after I left?
-My past is mine, not yours.
You know what? Don't tell me.
Just, you know, keep all
your secrets to yourself.
But just know that one day
they will come around and
they will bite you in the ass.
Do you remember the last time?
What?
Do you remember the last
time we saw each other?
Yeah, of course I do.
All I ever do is
remember that night.
- Hey!
- Hey.
I got something
I need to tell...
- Oh, sorry.
- No, you first.
No, you go. Yours
sounds more serious.
Mine can wait.
I'm not a buyer.
I'm not even a client.
I'm an undercover agent.
I work for the DEA. My
real name is John Lawlor.
I was sent here to dig
into Kwang's operation,
figure out the players,
who he's working for,
who's working for him.
The worst part is, uh...
they want me to bring you in.
I... I don't understand.
You were using me?
Yeah.
At first I was.
But then I fell
in love with you.
Deeply.
I thought, uh,
when the time came,
I could just protect
you, protect us.
The system is rigged.
They just need someone
to blame, and, uh...
it's never the shark, you know?
It's always the little fish,
and that's not gonna help.
Listen to me. Listen to me.
Listen to me.
You're gonna get up from here,
you're gonna walk
to the bathroom,
you're gonna crawl
out the window.
- No.
- You're gonna take my car,
and you're gonna drive away
from here as fast as you can.
Where should I go?
I... Just go wherever.
Wherever you want.
Just disappear, okay? Use cash.
I will scrub your records.
Don't leave a trace.
- No way for anyone to find you.
- How will you find me?
I won't.
- No. No.
- Please. You have to go.
No, John.
No. No.
Joey, please, go. Now.
That's not exactly
how it happened.
Well, that's how I remember it.
You never wondered
what my news was?
Never wondered
what I had to say?
Congratulations.
Thank you.
So you knew?
You knew you were pregnant
and you didn't tell me?
You said go, get out.
But if I knew...
Then what? You arrest me?
Raymond is born in prison?
- No, thank you.
- So, what, you...
You run to someone like Kwang?
You don't get to
judge my choices.
I did what I had to
do to protect my son.
I sacrificed everything.
So did I.
I sacrificed you.
The one thing in my
life that meant a damn.
Okay, okay.
Fine.
You want to be part
of this family?
- I do.
- You sure?
I'm sure.
And no more secrets,
everything out in the open.
I can do that.
If it doesn't work, we stop.
I don't want Raymond
getting hurt.
Neither do I.
And we take it slow.
That's fine by me.
- What?
- The police want
to talk to you about the
shootout at the hotel.
Kwang, this is serious.
What do I tell them?
- Yes.
- See?
That's how it's done.
Knock, wait, then enter.
Good. What's up?
Just looking for John.
- Huh?
- You know John.
Tall, grumpy guy, hates smiling,
not dead, not a chef.
Yeah, I'm sorry. Um...
I haven't seen him at all... no.
- You all right, Mom?
- Yes, I'm fine. Yeah.
Why are you looking for John?
I was pretty harsh
on him yesterday.
Just wanted to say sorry.
Don't worry. He's a tough guy.
Yeah, I know.
Still thought he'd
want to hear it though.
He's probably in the mountains,
getting his work out.
- Okay. Thanks.
- Yeah.
I do not hate smiling.
- I love smiling.
- Really?
Yeah. Show me.
All right. Well, this is my
"Pizza for dinner" smile.
And this...
is I found passports and
$10,000 in cash smile.
Give me that.
You said no more secrets.
Fine. It's our escape plan.
Some traveling cash,
fake passports.
Everything we need to get away.
- Except...
- Except what?
I only have passports
for me and Ray.
Don't worry. We're
not gonna split up.
I'm not gonna lose you again.
This incident at the hotel,
six of your bodyguards
were found there.
What time was the incident?
Around, uh, 5, 6 pm.
Hm.
That is hard to explain,
But, Deputy Liu, you know,
this doesn't seem like
any of my concern.
But as you can see, my
employees clocked out at 4 p.m.
and what my employees do
on their personal time
is their business, not mine.
How do we know these are real?
Deputy, the real question
you should be asking is
who killed my poor employees?
Why question me
when there's a real murderer
running out there free?
Makes me think of
the Chinese proverb:
Why kill the chicken
to scare the monkey.
Are you a chicken or a
monkey, Mister Kwang?
You know, it sounds to me like
you're dealing with a real pro.
Someone that is trained
with a unique set of skills.
You know, if anyone
should be a suspect,
it's this person, not me.
You mean the American,
George Washington.
George Washington...
Not George Washington!
Meet Agent John Lawlor.
My men sacrificed their lives
trying to stop him from
kidnapping my wife.
Why would he do this?
Because this John Lawlor
conceived a child with my wife.
The very child I've
been raising as
my own son for
the past 13 years.
His first case here in Taipei
was here to investigate me.
We will see.
Please look into it.
Any news?
Looking everywhere.
Finding nothing.
Check their airports,
train stations.
All staked out.
Try her village.
She said she never go
back, but you never know.
Listen to me very carefully.
This is really important, okay?
Kwang's ledger. Were
there any others?
I don't know. Maybe.
I didn't see any other ledgers.
There's only one.
He's in control if we
can't find hard evidence,
Kwang's not smart enough
to keep all that
information in his head.
Well, I was in his
study one afternoon.
Maybe it was the rhino.
He has a rhino
sculpture on his desk.
What if it's not a
sculpture at all?
- It's a hard drive.
- I can go get it.
No.
- It'll be easy...
- No.
- We'll find another way.
- What other way?
You said it: without any
evidence, Kwang wins.
We will find one. Don't worry.
We got this.
Hey, don't go too far.
Did you find her?
- No.
- Then why are you calling me?
Huh?
Good boy.
Don't drink beer that much.
Your hands are cold.
- Drink some hot tea.
- No... No beer, no enjoyment.
It's time to go.
What's wrong?
What are you doing?
No, you promised.
We're only gonna split
up for a little bit.
I'll create a secure email for
us to communicate, all right?
It's a shitty plan, but
it's the only one we have.
- Raymond!
- Po Po, where is Raymond?
Raymond. Where is Raymond?
Hanging out with his friends.
- Hi, guys.
- Where's Raymond?
He took my motorcycle.
Said he has something to do.
Hi, Raymond.
Need another pencil sharpener?
- Did you find her?
- It's me, Kwang.
Joey, darling, you okay?
- They hurt you?
- Where is Raymond?
You don't have to worry
about Raymond, sweetheart.
He's here with me.
He won't escape this time.
Kwang, it's me, Agent Lawlor.
Agent John Lawlor.
Nice to finally meet you.
Kwang, let him go.
- And what do I get?
- What do you want?
What do I want...
What do I want?
What I want, Agent Lawlor,
is for you to go away and
leave me and my wife alone.
Go back to where you came from.
Okay, then we swap.
Me for Raymond.
Ximending District,
American Alley.
American Alley?
You sure you don't want
to try some delicious
Taiwanese food before you go?
Noon.
- What are you doing?
- You said you would do anything
to protect our son. So would I.
He's going to kill you.
We'll see about that.
Trust me.
Okay? Go.
Where's Raymond?
He's in the car.
Mom!
- No. No. No.
- Mommy.
Let's go.
No, that wasn't the deal.
Deal?
Don't talk to me
about some deal.
Joey, remember the
first time we met?
Oh.
She didn't tell you.
Let me tell you about our story.
Tea?
Looking for some
lost merchandise.
Easy! Get your hands off her.
What did you do to her?
No, don't worry about her.
Worry about you.
There are consequences
for what you've done.
For one, you killed
my best driver.
Good help is hard
to find these days.
Sorry.
I'm sure you are.
You like?
Porsche.
RWB 964 twin turbo.
Why don't you come work with me?
What are you gonna do?
Rot away in this
little fishing village
for the rest of your life?
You're way too smart,
beautiful for that.
- You killed her.
- No,
- I'm not some kind of...
- Po Po!
Po Po!
Shh. Stop. Calm down.
Calm down.
Shh...
It's okay.
Hey.
See? You can trust me.
I'll never lie to you.
I'll always protect you,
you and your family.
And I'll give you the
life that you deserve.
We could make a
great team together.
What do you say, hm?
Deal?
It's a new deal. Now.
Come on.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah, I'm fine.
Get down.
- Go.
- You sit down!
You do this to me?
We're supposed to be family.
Huh?
After everything I've
done for both of you?
You do this to me?
Everything's gonna be okay.
We start over.
We'll be a family again.
Don't worry.
You all right?
Kwang, he still
has the USB drive.
Stay here.
Get out of the way, man.
Hey, watch out.
Kwang, hold it there!
Don't move.
Keep your hands
where I can see 'em.
You are under arrest.
On the floor now, now.
No.
People are leaving.
It's over, Kwang.
You're under arrest.
This has nothing to do
with your fishing case.
- This is between you and me!
- This is nothing personal.
Of course it is.
I've waited 15 years for her to
love me, and then you show up.
What can you give her
that I can't, huh?
You can't even take
care of your own son.
I'm just doing my job.
It's the last time, Kwang
Get on the fucking floor.
Go ahead, shoot me. Huh?
I'm unarmed.
Is this a 3D movie?
They fight for real.
- Don't watch it.
- Just a bit.
Oh my, it's too violent!
- See, I was right.
- About what?
You want her.
You're fighting for her.
But you're gonna
have to kill me.
'Cause she needs me.
She needs no one.
Good fight, I like it.
In shocking news,
business tycoon King
Kwang has been arrested
for illegal possession
of firearms in Taiwan.
Which has some of the toughest
gun-control law in the world...
Cigarette?
Anyone? You got a cigarette?
Quit smoking.
You want a lollipop?
Yeah, all right.
I made bail?
Someone wants to see you first.
Hey, thanks for bailing me out.
It wasn't me. They
want a million for you.
Way too much for the agency.
- Thanks, boss.
- I told you to go on vacation,
a weekend escape.
Instead, you went rogue.
You couldn't even
bring the ledger.
Yeah, well, I got
something better.
All of Kwang's records,
shipping manifests,
supplies, buyers,
illegal carbon offsets.
- This is real.
- More than real.
Okay, let me handle
it from here.
Until then, you
better disappear.
For real this time.
- Vanish. All of you.
- For the weekend?
Make it a couple of weeks...
couple of years.
All right, what's next?
You leave Taipei, immediately.
Robin Hood, thank you
for bailing me out.
- Not, my money.
- Here.
Thanks. So what
are we doing now?
Um...
Family vacation?
Ooh, yes. Yes.
No, you still have school.
Come on, a couple of
days isn't gonna hurt.
What do they learn
at this age anyway?
Plus, I already aced
my last math test.
- No. Nope.
- There you go. Come on.
This kid has been through a lot.
Yeah, I'm emotionally
damaged for life.
Absolutely not.
I got this. Come on.
Hey, Joey, listen, I just
got my passport back.
This is a really nice time for us
to go on our first family trip.
- No.
- Come on!
Come on, you're
such a taskmaster.
I miss school, months at a time.
Look how I turn out.
How you turned out... Huh...
You like it?
Oui.
Come on, Ray.
Ease up on the photos.
We have 13 years of empty
scrapbooks to fill in.
Oh, that's for
me. I'll get it.
- I have some...
- I got something I want to...
No, it's okay. You first.
This time you first for sure.
I have a present for you.
Now you cannot say
you didn't know.
Wow, that was... fast.
How can you? I mean...
You sure?
What...
Is it...
- Is it...
- Is it yours?
Does it matter?
No.
Bonjour.
Madame, you want croissant?
Merci.
Hell yeah.
♪ Ooh-ooh-ooh-ooh,
ooh Ooh-ooh-ooh, ooh ♪
♪ It's been a day in my head
I'm hanging on my last thread ♪
♪ There's things
I gotta forget ♪
♪ I'm catching up
with it lately ♪
♪ Spinning out a bit crazy ♪
♪ Know you're feeling
the same thing ♪
♪ 'Cause we've been
driving and riding ♪
♪ Just killing the time
♪ And it's like we
got nowhere to go ♪
♪ So meet me underneath
the moonlight [Ah-ah] ♪
♪ Light the fire, get your
mood right [Alright] ♪
♪ Must be something in the air ♪
♪ 'Cause I don't even care ♪
♪ Gonna dance until
the sunrise [Alright] ♪
♪ Ooh-ooh-ooh-ooh,
ooh Ooh-ooh-ooh, ooh ♪
♪ Ooh-ooh-ooh-ooh, ooh
Ooh-ooh-ooh, ooh, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ I'm waking up in a daze,
get it outta my face ♪
♪ The sun is shining on
every move that I make, so ♪
♪ Let's get to forgetting
everything that went wrong ♪
Everybody here, we
been crying too long
♪ We can dance about it to
our favorite song, song ♪
♪ So meet me underneath
the moonlight [Ah-ah] ♪
♪ Light the fire, get your
mood right [Alright] ♪
♪ Must be something in the air ♪
♪ 'Cause I don't even care ♪
♪ Gonna dance until
the sunrise [Alright] ♪
♪ Ooh-ooh-ooh-ooh,
ooh Ooh-ooh-ooh, ooh ♪
♪ Let's get to forgetting
everything that went wrong ♪
♪ Everybody here, we
been crying too long ♪
♪ We can dance about it to
our favorite song, song ♪
♪ So meet me underneath
the moonlight [Ah-ah] ♪
♪ Light the fire, get your
mood right [Alright] ♪
♪ Must be something in the air ♪
♪ 'Cause I don't even care ♪
♪ Gonna dance until
the sunrise [Alright] ♪
♪ Ooh-ooh-ooh-ooh,
ooh Ooh-ooh-ooh, ooh ♪