Thank you.
Champagne.
Traveling to Taipei, Taiwan.
We are happy to...
Grab the guns.
You guys got the wrong room!
Stairs!
Stop him!
Get in the car!
Go after that Ferrari!
Sports car? So what!!
What is wrong with you?!
Get out of the car! Get out of the car!
Get out of the car!
Hands!
Believe me! It’s my Bobo.
Bobo!
Sleep can help come up with solutions!?
Only ghost will believe you!
Haven’t seen in decades
and you left me a mess!
Now, have to clean it for you!
Thank you!
Thank you, everyone.
I left him. I did it!
Raymond!
You grew so big now!
Grandma,
we are going to get changed.
Joey!
Come and have lunch!
Okay.
Put all these in my garage.
Joey! Get up and run!
You did a really good job
deshelling them.
Thank you.
Really good.
Go over there
and deshell the beans.
Don’t drink so much cold beers.
Your hands are so cold
Feels awful if I do not drink!
Where is Raymond?
He went out with Biao.
Let's go, quickly!
A shocking news for you...
Business Tycoon...
Good morning!
Ma'am, croissants?